This is Agent Leland Turbo.
൧൧ 2ല? 2 ല്‌ക്ഗറ്‌ "ഥാ.
1 have a flash transmission for Agent Finn McMissile.
ടകു൭ ദറ്ദ ഗാടടലല്‍ ഗഗ4ധഥല 7൧ഥഗ 77ലി77ട5൭.
Finn, my cover's been compromised. Everything's gone pear-shaped.
൧൧, ടദണക7ഥ ടദ൮൭9 ?ലധഗഗനവ്വഷ. ലാഥദ 7ദഗഗകോറ്റഗ !ഗ്ദ 9റദ.
You won't believe what I found out here.
൧ ലയ ഒ്യാദ ഒറ 5൭൭ റ്ദ7 ൧0൮൮൭൧.
This is bigger than anything we've ever seen, and no one even knows it exists.
ദ ?ക4ലാലനകഗ 0ദ9 ടെ ടലഠടക7 ദ്‌, റ്ദഗ ടട'ദ്വാദ ഥന 7ദല്കഗ 4ഹ!ദഗന്സഒ.
Finn, l need backup, but don't call the cavalry, it could blow the operation.
൧൧, ടദ്ൃഒ ാലഥ്്‌ഥ ഥക൧!ല൭൧ഥ, ?ദ്[ദഗറദധ ഗ്ഗ! ദട4൭൧, ഗദ 7 7ഒഗട്‌ദ !ഗദ വാക.
-And be careful. It's not safe out here. -Let's go.
-൧ദഥ 7ദ77-ദഥ്‌. 2 540 49% ടല്ദ്നദ?. ഡി.
Transmitting my grids now. Good luck.
ക്കു ഗദ ഗാദ്ധധസദ 704൯൭5 ടക ടലദ7ഒഥറ. ടലാഠറ്റദ ൧2ല്‌ക)൭.
All right, buddy, we're here.
ചിറ, 0൭ 90 ട്വാലി.
Right where you paid me to bring you.
൧ ല്പാമതഥറ മയി ധാമ ടമ്മ ധധിധഡ്ധ.
Question is, why?
ലാ ടഠമിമബയ, 'ഭബല്വാമ?
I'm looking for a car.
ടമൃ൭ നലല ടലാധമ ലല.
A car? Ha!
ടലാധമ ഘു? 11൭
Hey, pal, you can't get any further away from land than out here.
ലി, മഗ, ല്വാമ(ബി മനാധ്യദധി ദ്ദ്0ി മ്മ.
Exactly where I want to be.
പഠി ബിമ സ്പാ.
I got news for you, buddy. There's nobody out here but us.
വനധിധാലുല്ഡമ മധ്യം. 11 ബര നമ്വാലഠ്ധാ ടദ്യദ റി ട്ബ്‌.
What are you doing out here?
൧3 മഗ്യിവാധമ ഠി ട്ബി?
What does it look like, genius? I'm crabbing.
൧3 901? ടൃ ടലഠ്മനാ മററിത്വ രണ.
Well, turn around and go back where you came from.
ഉടന ദ്മബവാമമ്വാല॥
Yeah, and who's gonna make me?
൭, ടിലാദ ലാലി മദാ ടമ്മ?
All right. All right. Don't get your prop in a twist.
82110൨. 310ലി. ല്ലാ നദ്വി ഖ്വലാമടമി-ാദടലി.
What a jerk. Sorry, buddy. Looks like it's the end of the line.
1ലഡിനസ൭. നീല, മഗ. വ1സ്വാമിസ്മ ടലല്‍മിരമ്ബി ടല.
Buddy?
ദ്ധ?
Incoming. All workers report to the loading dock.
€ക൧൭ ഗാദടഥ്‌. ടസഥദ ധ൧ലഘ്ദ ൨774ദ ഗഃല്ദ്യഠല്ദ്ഗ ന്ഥ്‌ ന്‌ റ്വലാഥാറ്റഗ.
Leland Turbo, this is Finn McMissile. I'm at the rally point. Over.
ല്‌ സ്ധലാം, ബ്‌ 0 ഗീഗസ്സ്ടടില. ൭൮൭ ഠി റ ല്പാമലാനലസ്ധമ. ലല.
All right, fellas, you know the drill.
810൭, ടലസ്ധമ, ഡമി്ഡ ദ്വ ൮൭0 ലധ ദ്ലാധമ.
Leland, it's Finn. Please respond. Over.
ലിറ, ബ്‌ ല്ബ. നിംബ. ഡല.
Come on, guys. These crates aren't gonna unload themselves.
കൃധി, ടല്ഡമ. ഉലല്പ്ാലി ബി ലിറമബാലറലയ ടലി.
Too many cars here. Out of my way.
7ലിദ്വല ഗകഗൃഷ്വഘല്ദ ന്‌ ടല. (൭൦ ലാ.
Professor Ziindapp?
൧ഠ൦൭ട൦॥ 200ഠ്ലാാ?
Here it is, Professor. You wanted to see this before we load it?
ബി ഠി. 7ഠലടം। ഗല്ധ്നമലം ടലാല്ധന യ്‌ നലന്ധഥറയ്്സുര?
Yes. Very carefully.
൭. 1130-90.
ATV camera.
(ണല സ്‌.
-What does it actually do? -This camera is extremely dangerous.
ഹ്യ ദ ലാംില്ഡാധാാ “രണലട ബി ണമ്ധാലാലിമത.
What are you up to now, Professor?
൧്വാ3 നമ്മ ലഠ്ടടം?
This is valuable equipment. Make sure it is properly secured for the voyage.
ചിലി മനാധാനമല്ഥാാ. മടടഥിര്ഥ 19 ടല്മനാധനധിലാല്ദയമമ ബി.
-You got it. -Hey, Professor Z!
-ഒറകഗ. ച്ദ്ല്‌, £7707൦507 ൧!
This is one of those British spies we told you about.
1 0൭൭ ലാലിട॥ല്ിട 09 ബി ലേല്ഖിത്ഥ ഡ.
Yeah! This one we caught sticking his bumper where it didn't belong.
6 1111:11:111:-111:111-1111111॥ [:11:11111:11 2-11-11
Agent Leland Turbo.
ല്ല ലിറ സ്ധനാം.
It's Finn McMissile!
1ധ ലബ നീണി്ടടില്‍
He's seen the camera! Kill him!
൧19 ദമ ാമ്പാലിലണനലമ [ഡധ! 3ഒധഥ്ധി ദില
All hands on deck! All hands on deck!
&ഹോദടകഗ! (ലോദടദഥ7
What?
൧്പാമ?
Get to the boats!
ുചിധാംറ്‌
-He's getting away! -Not for long!
212 നലില്ലിര്ഥ ഠി! -ടലദ്ല്ല്ലാ ടദ്യഡ!
He's dead, Professor.
൧ദ റ്൭൧ 7)ദ, ൧07൭൭ 07.
With Finn McMissile gone, who can stop us now?
00 നീണ്്ടട॥ം 20 മഠ, വിഠ്ദ ടലടില്പാ വാല മദ ൩൭.
Mater, Tow Mater, that's who, is here to help you.
ീമല, "ഗഗ [ഗീമല, ഠമ൭0റ൮0 ധനധി൦ണലമ്പാബ്വ.
-Hey, Otis! -Hey, Mater.
ചിലി, ഠി! ചലി, [മല
I... Gosh. I'm so sorry.
൭൭൮൭... വമനമി സീമലിര്ഥ ടമ൭.
I thought I could make it this time, but...
1 [11:1:1 ടമ വാല്‍ ടബ്വാലി യി ബി, ദ്വ...
Smooth like pudding, huh?
ഒല്ലല്ല്ലേ, ത്ന?
Who am I kidding? I'll always be a lemon.
൧്വാലി്പ്വത്ഥാ ടു നിന്നിതു? ടമൃ൭ നലനഥ9 4 ലോധി.
Well, dad-gum, you're leaking oil again. Must be your gaskets.
ിബമമഗയലി നല്ഴിലമി. ീലട॥ി റുദടി മഗ്യിദ്ഖ്പാംഠേ.
Hey, but look on the bright side.
ചാ ൪ 01102 ടധ്ധലംട!.
This is your tenth tow this month, so it's on the house.
ബി യ 1൭-10 മഡ്യിറിധഥ്മ ധി, 4901 ൪ ബി മ ലാലഗേനമ.
You're the only one that's nice to lemons like me, Mater.
നീല, മധ്യ ടല്യലില്വത്ാധാലി ല്ലാ ഖല ലോധിധണമമേണ ടമ ബി.
Don't sweat it. Shoot, these things happen to everybody.
പ്‌ ല്ടധ. ല്ലി 0ാഠ1ലവ൮൭ഠി ശ്വാമഠ്ഠ ടടട।ല്വാദ ട്വ.
-But you never leak oil. -Yeah, but I ain't perfect.
“ട്വ ബ്ന മഗ്യിറല്ലാലനമ നല്ഴിം ഥമ, ലവ ടമ മഠ ടലമ്പാധ്നമ.
Don't tell nobody, but I think my rust is starting to show through.
പ്ല ടടടില്ാമ, 'ല്വാി ൭ ടമ്മ ൭0 ണമിന്ന ഖമ.
Hey. Is Lightning McQueen back yet?
ല്‍, 101000 ഗദ്വേംഗ റ്ഖ്പാല॥ദ
Not yet.
ഒല്ധണ 91.
He must be crazy excited about winning his fourth Piston Cup.
1 മടി ല്പാന ടലാലാനലണാ ലച ടം ധനധ്ലരി! 1ലസ്പാമ!.
Four! Wow!
സ്വാദ്‌ ഗ7ഠഗ്‌
Yeah, we're so dad-gum proud of him, but I wish he'd hurry up and get back,
൭, അമ മനമലാനണനമേ ലമ, 'ല്വാി ടയ ലവ വിലാ ലോ
‘cause we got a whole summer's worth of best friend fun to make up for.
ടധ്യാമയമ ബി ദ്ഖ്ലാമലാലടലഠന ട്ല്പാല്യമററ സ്ധടന്ാനമട ബ.
Just me and...
11ബ്മ ടയ ഠ്‌...
McQueen!
ീദ്ധേലലബ്‌!
-Whoa, whoa, whoa! -McQueen!
1101, 0൦1, 0൦! പ്ഥീദ്േധേലല്‍!
-Mater! I'm in no hurry! -Hey, everybody. McQueen's back!
പിള്‍ിമല! ടമ ഖിധ്ാല്ധ ഭട നമ-ണമല! ലി, ടല്ധമ. ീദ്ധേലല ദ്ദ്വാല॥റ്‌
McQueen's back!
ീദ്ധേലല ദ്ദ്വാല॥റ
Lightning! Welcome home!
1:11 11111:1- 11-11: 711:111:1
-Good to have you back, honey! -Congratulations, man.
-8മറൃധടിമ മഗ്യി്പ്പാധിനു, ടമ്മാ! മല്ല, മമ.
Welcome home, soldier.
ടല ധി, ലാല.
The place wasn't the same without you, son.
“ലമ്വാമബി ലിം ടാ ബാ ഡ്മിപ്ല്ം.
What? Did he go somewhere?
1ലമ്വാമ? ൧3 മഠ ലാല ൨ നനന?
It's good to be home, everybody.
ടൃ റലമ്പാമ പരാധി.
-Mater! -McQueen!
്‌ഥിമല! പ്ഥീദ്േധേലല്‍!
Hey, how far did you make it this time, Otis?
ല്‍, ാലഘ്വാമ [ധി മധ്യം ടമ്പാമി ശിബി, ലട?
-Halfway to the county line. -Not bad, man!
-ടല്ലാ്ധ്വ്വ[മിമ ര ടല്പാമഠ്മ ദ്ദലയ. 1-1 ::111:111
I know! I can't believe it either!
11]! ൭൭൮൭ ടലി ാധന ഖി ടിയ
-McQueen! Welcome back! -Mater, it's so good to see you.
പരീദ്ധേലല്‍്‌! ടലമണമ ധി! ിഥിമല, ടമ൭ റലമ്പാനമലാല്ധമ്പാമ മഗ്ലിം.
You too, buddy.
ടൃ ലാധന ടമന൭.
Man, you ain't going to believe the things I got planned for us!
എഗ്യിമിനത്ഥാല മേ ലാ ടമ 50 മഥ ധനധിലഗ്മാലര്‍്ധമ!
These best friend greetings get longer every year!
സീമിഗ്ന മനമ, ഖി്ധ-ഖ്ധമ നലല നലിന്ന ബ്ന!
-You ready to have some serious fun? -I've got something to show you first.
-5ലറി൭ ധനധിധാലലമ്പാന്മു? ടമ 021 ഡബ്ധിമഗഘല ടട ഠ്വ.
Wow.
7ഠഴ.
I can't believe they renamed the Piston Cup
121 ടിയ നലല നമ ണമിത്ഥ ലച ടല
after our very own Doc Hudson.
ടലമ്പാല ൧൦൦ 0ധഠ്ടം൩1൦൭.
I know Doc said these things were just old cups,
ടമ ഡം രര മിമി ബി ഠ്മ്ലി്ലനമ,
but to have someone else win it just didn't feel right, you know?
'ല്വാി ടയ ഒട ലിം ടലഠ്ലാ ൭൧ 0॥ വല ല൩ നനണനലറിസത.
Doc would've been real proud of you. That's for sure.
ഉംം മടി ലാലാ ട്രോമ ഗ്മ
All right, pal. I've been waiting all summer for this.
ചിറ. ടമു൭ ദ്ധ ടം ടം ട്ല്പാല്യമററ സ്ധടന്ലാനമട.
-What you got planned? -You sure you can handle it?
ഗ്വാ ഗമി? ഛഡ്യിറയിന്നാംില്‍ നാ ബ്ബരത?
Do you know who you're talking to? This is Lightning McQueen!
ടലി ഖി മധ്യ ലിയ്വാ ലേ ടില്വാമ? ബി ബ്ന സീദ്ധേലബ്‌
I can handle anything.
൭൭൮൭ 1ഠ01ല ലിന ഖാ ട്വ.
Mater?
ഗി?
Just remember, your brakes ain't going to work on these!
003, 10ല മഴ്യി്ലാലന ഒട ലാലി ബി!
-Mater? -Relax.
പില? ഒല.
These train tracks ain't been used in years!
ഉബാല്ല്ഡനമഥ്ന 111: :1-::11111 1:11:
Faster, faster. Come on. Here we go!
ലേ, ലാല്‌ സൃയഡി. ബി ഠി!
Faster!
ലി
Wow.
7ഠഴ.
Yeah, I don't know. Do you think?
൭, ബര്വമ൨. ഡാ ലാലാ്ലാമ മഡ്ല്റ
This is going to be good!
ബി ടി ടല
Did you see that?
പ്പാ
This ain't going to be good.
ബി മടി ലിം.
Boy, this was the best day ever!
വിമി വമാ മിന ടലി
And my favorite souvenir, this new dent.
ഉമ ൫301൭൩ ശഭാലനമമ്ഥ ടയ, 1ലമ്പിവത്ാ ടമാ ഠ്ല്വാദബി.
-Boy, Mater, today was... -Shoot, that was nothing.
ച്ഗിമല, 0൭0 ബ്‌... ഡാല്ധന ല്വാ-ദ്വാ 1൭1.
Wait till you see what I got planned for tonight!
ധാ ടല ിഘ്ധത്ഥ 09 ടമു൭ മഥ ധനധ൦നല്മണ ബി!
Mater, Mater, whoa! I was thinking of just a quiet dinner.
നില, നീല, ടാന്‍ ടയ 00% 1-111-11 1111111411 11:11:
That's exactly what I was thinkin’.
1ധ്ധപ്വത്നാ ടര മഥ ഠമേോേ9ിത്ന.
-No, I meant with Sally, Mater. -Even better!
“121 നലിദ്ധധ്‌ ടമ്മ, ലററ ടലി. ഡ 139 ാമ്ധട!
You, me and Miss Sally goin’ out for supper.
ഗ്യ, ടമ്മ ദ്ദ ലല 1ല്ധല നലിത്ഥ നമിമന.
Mater, I meant it would be just me and Sally.
നീല, നമിദ്ധഠ്‌ ടയ, ധനാ ടമ്മ ദ്ദ ടലി.
You know, just for tonight.
11ബമ ധധിംനമിദന ബി.
We'll do whatever you want tomorrow.
5ടഠ।ധിന്മാധമ£ വാദ ടല] ൮൭൧൭൮ മയി ലിം.
Okay.
വിവ.
-Thanks for understanding. -Yeah, sure.
“ലിനാ 1൭ടിഷമമ നലനമിലി. ന, ട്ട നമടമമ൩.
-Y'all go on and have fun now. -All right, then.
ശ്ഡ്യിധാലഠി॥!മ്സാലടെല്‍ന1 ടല. 1:11 1:11: 1:11
See you soon, amigo.
പ്ധമ്പാട 1൭9, ര൭ഡമ൭൨.
This is so nice.
0ദ്മ൩൩൫൭.
I can't tell you how good it is to be here alone,
൭൮൭ ൩൭ ലബ്ബാ ാലറ്മട ഠി ടബ്‌.
just the two of us, finally.
ചന്ത, ബ൭ന്മവാല്ധമ.
-You and me. -Good evening.
ടമ റിമ ഗമി -ടലമണമ നമിമണ.
My name is Mater,
പണട ടവ [റില്‌
and I'll be your waiter.
ദമ ടമ ലാലിയ മഡ്ലിധനമറ ബി.
Mater the waiter. That's funny right there.
നില, ടി ലമ. ധധേബുമ.
Mater? You work here?
നീല? ഗസ്ലിലഷ്ദ ഠി ടലി?
Yeah, I work here. What'd you think?
൭, ടധഠ്ട ലവ. യിനി ല്വാമ?
I snuck in here when nobody was lookin’
ടയ ഥേി-ധേോി നട
and pretended to be your waiter so I could hang out with you?
ദ്മാല്ലാധ്്പ്ാധമ ണലബ്ദഠി ാല്മയമ്ഥ ടധ്യാമു ദ്ദ്വാമലാലടമനാ മഗ്മിറ
Oh, yeah. How ridiculous would that be?
൨൩,൮൭. ടമ ലഡഡ ലിണടടധിലിരയി.
Can I start you two lovebirds off with a couple of drinks?
൧3 ൭൭ ടമ സന്ധി ബ്രമ്മ ഠ്ലാമന ടലല്ടട സ്സ്ധണന?
-Yes. I'll have my usual. -You know what? I'll have that, too.
൭. ടമ നമിലാടടമഥ സ്ഗ്ധനമഥ മട. ടമ്മ ാധ0 ടണമ.
Right. Your usual.
൫൭. ഗിസ്ധണമന ത്ഥ മഗ്യിലാിമട ലാട.
-Thanks, man. -Grazie, Guido.
ലന ശട, മഗ. ലനാ മട, ധേഠ്ം.
Guido, what's McQueen's usual?
ധോം, സ്ബ്ധണമ്ഥ ദ്വാമ ൮൭0൭ നീഗദ്ധേംദ ടല്ല്ധ ബ്ന്മ?
How should I know?
സിലി ടമ ദ്ഡ.
-Perfect. Give me two of them. -Quiet! My program's on.
-8മറുധട. 5൮൭ നലിഠദ്ധ സ്ധ്ധണമ് ഡ. -21ബസ! മഥ ഠ്മ്വാലസ്ധിദ.
Tonight on the Mel Dorado Show...
൧ക!ദഗ £ദഗഗകേോറ്റദഗ 77ല ൧ഠ7ദറ്ഠ 73ദ!ദന 70...
His story gripped the world.
7ട൭70൧)9 ഗ)ുലദഗ്‌!ഥധലഗദള്‍കഗ ടല്ഥഥി വ്ഥ്ഒ.
Oil billionaire Miles Axlerod,
പ്ഥ്ദഒഥ 770) ഒ൮ഥ്‌77൦5 ഷ൧റ്ലാ൦്‌,
in an attempt to become the first car to circumnavigate the globe without GPS,
റ്ദ'ദ7? ലടകഗദ ഗാലവദന്‌ 4ഘലല്ദ ാല്ദനദ 39൧9 നല9്ല7ഥ്‌ വ്ഥദ !ദഗാദ ൭൧.5,
ironically ran out of gas, and found himself trapped in the wild.
൧൭-൧൭ ൧ഘികഥ്‌ടകഗ റ്ടട, റ്ദഗ 7ലാലക്ഥവ്ദ്വ റ്മദഗ7 70ല7ഒഥ.
Feared dead, he emerged 36 days later,
ട്ല്‌ല്ഒ ന്ഗഥദഥ്‌ 77, ന്ദ നഥഥ്‌ 36 ഗദഥ്‌ ്നലന്ദഥ,
running on a fuel he distilled himself from the natural elements!
റ്ദഗ 77റഥ റ്ലാറ്റക്ഗ ൧ദഗദഥ ദ്)ഒഥറ ൨ദ 7ദ57൭൧ റ്ദധഗ്ഥാദറ്ദ 52ല” ദദ7?7
Since then, he's sold his oil fortune,
ക്ലാലദ്്‌കല്ഥ ന്‌ ഗാല്വ്‌ഥദ് ലാലഗദറ്ദദഗ7)ഒ,
converted himself from a gas-guzziler into an electric car
ഗാലഥ്വഥവാ ന്ഗ്ലുദ ഗ7ാലദധ്‌ 7£ഘലദ ല്ലന്ഥ
and has devoted his life to finding a renewable, clean-burning fuel.
റ്ദഗ ൧ലഥധടദ്ധദ ഗലഗദഥ്‌ ൧കഗ0ദഗ ദ്യ 39൧0 2൧7ല ന്ഥലാഥകഗക്ഗ്‌.
Now he claims to have done it with his allinol.
€൧0 ന്ദ ഗുഹറ്ലസ, ലടക്ഗദഥവദ ൧ല്‌ദയദ റ്ലാറ്റകഗ ധാലാലാഥഗദഗ ൭7901.
And to show the world what his new super fuel can do
ഗ്രധ്ധഗാലശഗ്വ്ധലഗ ദ്ധദ 39൧0 ൧൧7ല ൨ദ്യോക്‌ 0ല ൧ക൧ദ ദ്വയാ7 77!,
he's created a racing competition like no other,
നദ ?ലക7 ഗാലാഥ്ദ്വഷ ടല ധല്‌ഗ്ണാഥദക്ഗ ൧2൭൦൧.
inviting the greatest champions
റ്ദഗ ഗുല്വലന്യാഥ്‌ വല ഥദഥ ?ലഗലാദ?
to battle in the first ever World Grand Prix.
ഗഗ4ധഥംസകഥന്നറ റ്ദ'ദന ദഥഠ്‌ ൧നഥഗഥ്സ്‌ദ )ഒഥറ ഥാലഥ്ദണട.
Welcome, Sir Miles Axlerod.
ടല മു, ടു ഗീ॥ിടട ഷഠിലഠഠി.
Thank you, Mel. It is good to be here. Listen to me.
ലിന 1൭ട॥, നീല്‍. ടയ റല്പാ്മ ാലമഠ്ദ റി ടബ്‌. ലല്ല ടിബി.
Big oil. It costs a fortune. Pollution is getting worse.
ിബമഗണലനമിര്ിരട വാ ന. ലേലേനമമറ ണമിന്ന ടലിധട.
I mean, it's a fossil fuel. “Fossil,” as in dead dinosaurs.
പാമ ദ്വി ൦ട॥. "ംട॥”ാലയടമി ദ്മ്വാഠ്ദ ദ്നംടധലയമ ററ ഠ്ക1ണനി.
Alternative energy is the future. Trust me, Mel.
സീമടമ ഠ്ലാബാലഡനാ മ്മ ലമ മലനാ. ലല, നീല.
After seeing allinol in action at the World Grand Prix,
ട്ല്ലാദടട നല്‍൫൭ലലല്വപോല്മ മിനം॥ മ്മ മമാ ലാഗഥധബ്മ,
nobody will ever go back to gasoline again.
൧35 £7ദറ്ദ ട4ദ്ഠദ )൧റ ഗാദഗഥ [ദ്‌ ഗാലറ്ററഥദദദ 9ദട07൧7.
What happened to the dinosaurs, now?
൧്വാ3 ൮309 ൦൭൦ ഘ്വാമഠ്ദ ദ്നഠടമ്ധ?
And on satellite, a World Grand Prix competitor
ഉമ്ഥ ടലലവേ ഥാടഥന9, ഗ്മ ദ്ദ ലാലധസ്പാ മമ ലാബ്‌
and one of the fastest cars in the world, Francesco Bernoulli.
ദമ ടമ ടലാധ്വിഷഘല ലാമമട ഠി ദ്ധബാ, നേട 8൩൦.
It is an honor, Signore Dorado, for you.
൧ഡ്മിലല മട ലാലാടടല 0൭0, 50. ൦൫൭ഠ൦.
Why not invite Lightning McQueen?
1ലദ്വാ 'ഖിധ്ുല്പാധ 1101 ബ്ണ നീദ്ധേടണ?
Of course we invited him,
കറ്‌ 7ല?ഥദഗ്മ്‌ റ്൭൧ല്വാഥ്‌,
but apparently after his very long - racing season
'ല്വാി ടലല്‍ലിദമ്വ്ലനമലാലിധമ്പാമ ടലഠമേലാലലലടാറ,
he is taking time off to rest.
ഠി ന0൩ നാമാ! നട ധധിധാലല്‌.
The Lightning McQueen would not have a chance against Francesco.
100ബ്യാ നീദ്ധേം റിതം നലമിദ്വ്ര്ഥ ്ഥടേടഠ.
I can go over 300 kilometers an hour.
ടൃ ാഠിലി ല്വോല 3090 01ംണലല്‍ല൦ ദ്മീമന ണടട ടലദന.
In miles, that is like... Way faster than McQueen.
ഉലമാ, 9 ടലാബയിം.. 1 ലാവവ്വാമനമട ഠ്3റ്വാഠ്ഠ ദ്വേ.
Let's go to the phones. Baltimore, Maryland, you're on the air.
നീച നഅ൯ ലിന ലാമണാഠ॥മന ടില്ം൩. ചിനം, ഗീബിമ്‌, മഗ്‌! ധദ്ദ.
-Am 1 on? Hello? -You're on. Go ahead.
-5ദ)ദ റ്‌ വ്‌ ലറ്ദഗ7ദ? 7൧്ല്ഠ? ൭. ലബടിത്ഥ.
-Hello? -Go ahead.
-ഥ്ലഠ? ലട.
Let's go to Radiator Springs. You're on, caller.
സിലി ലിന ഉഥറ॥!മ ദ്കലി മഠ ട്വാഥനാട. ഗലി ധഠ്മമ.
That Italian feller you got on there
2 ലക്‌ 207
can't talk that way about Lightning McQueen.
ദ്വലാദ4ഥ്‌ കേദ്വ ഗല്‌ ല!ഒഥററ 2.0701079 77൦ ഠേലംലാ.
He's the bestest race car in the whole wide world.
൧19 ലല ലലാ ബേബി.
if he is, how you say,
പദ ന്ദ ടലാല്‌ )൭൧റ ദഷ്വവഷകഷഥം,
“The bestest race car," then why must he rest? Huh?
1ലല്വാദ ഠിദ്ാല്ധാലലിമറ 100
‘Cause he knows what's important.
ട്ലാദ്ഥ ന്ദ ?ദ്ധഥ ൧൯൦ ദ്ദ )ഒഥ0 2ല209.
Every now and then he prefers just to slow down, enjoy life.
ടല7-ടല്ദ!ദ വദ 7൨ ൧്ലാകഥറ റ്ദഗ ഗുലഗാദല ലറ്ഥദഥ.
You heard it! Lightning McQueen prefers to be slow!
ഗ്യ ലഡു! 11011 ബ്ണ ഗനീദ്ധേം ടധിര ലാല!
This is not news to Francesco.
ബി ാധിത്ഥ ാലിവ്്യാമബ 39 അ്ഥടേടഠ.
When I want to go to sleep, I watch one of his races.
8112 ടമ നല്ധിഠ്േ, ടമ ൦0ബാലിധപാമമബുമ.
After two laps, 1 am out cold.
ടല്ലാദട റ്ലദ ൧ാഥടററ്റണഗം, ടദ൮൭ റ്‌ 7ല്ല്ക്വാ.
That ain't what I meant.
8ധിരബഡവത്ാ ടമ്മ നലിദ്ധഠിത്ഥ.
What's going on over there?
൧൮09 ട൦ഠ്ബാലാലില്വ ഡാ?
He is afraid of Francesco.
൧ദ 7ദഡ്‌ റ്ലാറ്റക്ഗ 77൭൧൦൦5൦.
That's that Italian formula car.
ഡല ം്ധിമ ചിയ.
-His name is... -Francesco Bernoulli.
പ്രസ... -്ഥടേടഠോ 8ലന൦ധ॥.
-No wonder there's a crowd. -Why do you know his name?
ദധി മണലി ധാലിവസ്പവാധി. 1 ലല്വാദ മഗ്യി മധ നന?
And don't say it like that. It's three syllables, not 10.
ഉമ്മാമ ടലാധ്ധാല്ധ. 1൭ ഡേനദ റി ടധിവ ൭, ലാധിത്ഥ ടലാധിധി.
What? He's nice to look at. You know, open-wheeled and all.
൧൮3? ൧3 ൭൨ 1 മൃന്വ ല്ലി മില്ല.
What's wrong with fenders? I thought you liked my fenders.
1ലദ്വാ ്ലാമന റ്ല്വാഭ ടമ്മ? ടൃ നാമിത്ഥ മയി ടധിരാ?
-Let me tell you something else. -Mater?
-ടദുദ ഗദ്ധധഥല്‌ദഗല ദമ ടടഥദല. പില?
McQueen could drive circles around you.
൧7ഠേഥംല ൧൧ലിാദ്ധറ്ല ഗാലാറല7ഥഗമ്‌ ദ്വ
Driving in circles is all he can-a do, no?
1 ടല്യമാ ഠിാംല്ഡാധറ
No.
70൭.
I mean, yes. I mean, he could beat you anywhere.
ഗീലിദ്ധഠ്‌ ടമ, 1101ല്‍ നലദിദ്വിര്ഥ ഗമി! നമനമ-ണമനട ടദ്യമ.
Any time, any track.
ച്ധിന്നു നട മധ ലം.
Mel, can we move on?
സില, ലാഠില നന ലധടിത്ഥ?
Francesco needs a caller who can provide
മേട നനലിധിത്ഥ ലാനാ! ൮൭09 0൦1൭൨ നല്പാലലിത്ഥ
a little more intellectual stimulation, like a dump truck.
7ദഥറടദഗകഗ ഒ ഗലമഹഗല ല്ലം, ടലാലസ്‌ !ഠ7്‌ ൧ാലാഥഥദഥറ ടദസ്യാദഥ.
That shows what you know. Dump trucks is dumb.
1ധ നല്വബ്ധിധമ്ബാലാല്ഖ്ഡാമ മയം. ഠി ലാല്പാധഥാ ടദമ്പാമ്ാഠഠ്ം.
Hey! Whoa!
ല്ലി! 11൦1!
Yeah, hi. This is Lightning McQueen.
ര, മ. ടമ 00 ബ്ന൭ നദ്വേ.
The Lightning McQueen, huh?
1101 ബ്ണ നീദ്ധേടണ?
1 don't appreciate my best friend being insulted like that.
ക്കു 7ഒ0 ടഥ്ദ ദഴലഗാലറ്ഥദ 7ദ്്ഥ ദഥ്ഥ ടദ്യ൭ ടലാലസ്‌ 770.
McQueen, that was your best friend?
സീദ്ധേലല, ഡമി മഗ്ല്ന
This is the difference between you and Francesco.
വിദ്വാനെ റയ ഗമി മ്ഥടേടഠേ.
Francesco knows how good he is.
മേട യ്ഡ ലലാമ്മുമ.
He does not need to surround himself with tow trucks to prove it.
൧൭ ലിധ്ാല്ധാലിരമല ്ലറമ്ന ലിഡന്ദേ ധധിണലമ്പാധിവിത്ഥസത.
Those are strong words from a car that is so fragile.
ധര്മ്മ ഷടട ദ്മ്0ി ടലാധാിഷല ഥറ 1ല൩൭൨.
Fragile! He calls Francesco fragile!
1ലണമവ്‌ ൧0 ൭൪ മഥ േട൦ ലന്‌!
Not so fast, McQueen!
പഠന ലില്ധാമറമട നലഡുലേണ, ീദ്ധേലലബ്‌!
“Not so fast." Is that your new motto?
"ചിറ്റ ലിദ്ധ ലാമ.” ധന ഗമി നാഥ?
Motto?
ഗീ?
This sounds like something that needs to be settled on the race course.
പ1സ്വാമിസ്മ, [ബി ടലടധമധവനാലാല്ഡ ഠിടലിടടലിന ഠ്ലേറബവാലിധസാമമ്.
What do you say, Lightning McQueen? We've got room for one more racer.
ഒമറുല്നമറമ, ദീഗ്വേലലറ? ബി ലാല ലിന ടമ 09 ലാട.
I would love to, but my crew is off for the season, so...
ടൃ ലാലമ്പ്നമ ലവി ലാലു ടമ്മ ലോ സ്ധട്ന ബ്‌, മഠ...
Pit stop.
ദിലി ലി.
You know what? They just got back.
സീലല്ര്വാദല ടദ്യദ ടാസ്വാല്‌.
Deal me in, baby.
ഉച്ധ്വിദ്ഥ നണട ടമ൮൭.
Ka-chow! Yeah.
1(൭-0ഠഗ്‌ മ.
I know, I know. I just got back, but we won't be long.
ടൃ പ്ഡ, ടമതവാലപധാാല്ം "ജ്വാല! മലമ.
No, don't worry about me. I've got enough to do here.
“ച്ധപ്നറമന ല്ടധ മററ ടമ. ൭൮൭ 9ഠിലാബയയ്ലാലഠ്ദ നല്ലാധമ.
Mater's going to have a blast, though.
നീല വ ഠലമ്പാ മ.
You're bringing Mater, right?
൧ഡ്മ മിതാ സീല്‌, മന?
You never bring him to any of your races.
ഗ്യ മിലാലനല്സപാമ ഠി 1ലരാലിധമ്പാമമറ മധ്യം.
Just let him sit in the pits. Give him a headset.
- 11:11: 11:11 11-11:1:111:11% ാഠ॥ ഠി ടല വാമി.
Come on, it will be the thrill of a lifetime for him.
പാടി നലബ്മഠി ാലറമിമണമ്ഥ 021൩9 ലാലല രാമസ.
-Your drink, sir. -Mater.
“ബി സ്ഥ്ധനറ ലം. 1ഥിമല.
I didn't taste it!
൭൮൭ ൭0 ഥി-ഗഥേോ സ്ധബ്ധബ്‌
How'd you like to come and see the world with me?
വലി മ്ധിയ ടമ നലാല്‍॥ന9! ധേബ്മ?
-You mean it? -Yeah. You got me into this thing.
ഡയ ടലിധട? ൭. ൧ഥ്യി്മ്പാധ ടര ലലല.
-You're coming along. -All right!
പിമഠി, മഗ്ര ॥ഡ. -83110൨.
Ka-chow!
1(൭-ലഠഗ്‌
Hey!
ല്ലി!
Excuse me!
1111 :):111:11:111]
Domo arigato!
ലിന മട്വാബതി്ലാബുമിറ
Yeah!
വച
Guido, look. Ferraris and tires.
ധോം, 10. ലല 0ലന്മി മഥ യയ.
-Let's go! -Look at this.
്ഥീ്ി ലാല. ്ലാഠബി.
Okay, now, Mater, remember, best behavior.
വയില, നം 19092 ഭിമിവമ മധ്യം.
-You got it, buddy. Hey, what's that? -Mater!
-831109൨, ൭൨. 11ലി, ലാമ ഡ? ്‌ഥിമല!
Hey, McQueen! Over here.
റല, നീദ്ധേലലവ്‌ (൭ നമി.
-Lewis! -Hey, man.
-1ലഡിട! ചലി, ഗ്ല.
-Jeff! -Hey, Lightning.
പില! ല്‍, 11൫ബന൭.
Can you believe this party?
്ലാമബലാിബി?
Hey.
ലി.
You done good. You got all the leaves.
ട്രൃയ്വാമട. ൧ഗമി്ലാമവ്ാ ടലസ്ധ ദ്ദ.
-Check out that tow truck. -Man, I wonder who that guy's with.
ലാം സ്ലിഥഠ്ദ ഡ. -212 റിമ൭0റ൮ റ്റു ടിദ്യാ മിസ.
Will you guys excuse me just for one little second?
ീലിര്ഥ ടമ൭ ടലാലഘ.
Good job!
ട്രൃത്ചാമട!
Mater! Listen, this isn't Radiator Springs.
ീമല ഥലാല ട്ബി, ബി ാധിര്ഥ മറി ട്രാന്ന9ട.
You're just realizing that?
ള്‍ഗ്യിലാമബ ടലി?
That jet lag really done a number on you.
ലഡിധാലധി ശട ലാലലാനാമ ൭9 1 മട മഡ്യിം.
Mater, things are different over here.
സീമല, മമമ ഠി ടിവി ലാലാല.
Which means maybe you should, you know, acta little different, too.
ഒലി, മഗ്മിലാലിധ ധാമ നായ്പലിവ മം.
-Different than what? -Well, just help me out here.
മ റ്പ്രാഠ്മ ലാമ? 1010091൨, രഥ.
You need help? Shoot! Why didn't you say so?
൧ഗ്യില്ാലിധിത്ഥ ലാലി? 1ലദ്വാ ഖി ലിയാ?
That's what a tow truck does.
ധി ഡാടട ച:ധഥട്േ.
-Yeah, I mean... -Looky there.
ട്‌, നലിദ്ധഠ്‌ ടമ൭... ്ലാഠ1ഡ.
It's Mr. San Francisco. I'll introduce you.
1൧5൨. ടാഥ ഞ്ഥപഠ്ടഠ. ൭൮൭ മിര്ഥലാലിഭലിത്ഥ മമ.
-Mater, no! -Look at me. I'm helping you already.
1:11! ലാഠ10൭൨, ടമയമ നല മഡ്യിം.
Hey, Mr. San Francisco, I'd like you to meet...
ലി, 50. ടമ നഥഠ്ടം, ടമ ലില്വാലിശ്ലമിത്ഥ...
Lightning McQueen! Buona sera.
110101 ബ്ണ നീദ്ധേംംബ' ടിന ണമിമണ.
-Nice to meet you, Francesco. -Nice to meet you, too.
-ടലഠ0ഠ1ധാല്വധ്വാ മധ്യം ്ഥടേടഠ. ടൃ ടലഠ0ഠ1വാല്ധ്വാ മധ്യം.
You are very good-looking. Not as good as I thought, but good.
ഗയിം മണമല്ല നലിടലരലവറുെ ടമ ടായിര്ഥ, ഖ്വാി 01൦൨ ലമ.
Excuse me. Can I get a picture with you?
നീല. 83൦1ല്‍ ടമൃത്വാലറ്റമമ്പാല ലാ ഗ്ല
Anything for McQueen's friend.
൧്വാ3 ട്വ ധബധഡിംന്ലിര്ഥ നീദ്ധേ.
Miss Sally is going to flip when she sees this.
ലട ലാ ലഡ്വ 1111411111):
She's Lightning McQueen's girlfriend.
൧19 നാഥ ഡാബ്മ 90ബ്നാ നീഡ്ധേം.
She's a big fan of yours.
31:11: 1111111111
Hey, she has-a good taste.
റല, ാമാധട വ്ര മട.
Mater's prone to exaggeration. I wouldn't say she's a "big fan".
നീല ടധിര നല്പാലാടടലിത്ഥ ലേ. 31:11: 1:111-11:1111-111111:110- 1:10
You're right. She's a huge fan!
ലഡഡ. ൧1 ല॥-0॥മമ0 മധ്യിറ
She goes on and on about your open wheels.
19 ലിഷ്വാ മിലി മററ മയ ഡല ലാട ധ.
Mentioning it once doesn't qualify as going on and on.
01 ഡാ ടലാധ ടല്യി। ടല.
Francesco is familiar with this reaction to Francesco.
മഥേടഠോ റ്്വാ!മടമ ലാ ലമി രാല്ധ.
Women respect a car that has-a nothing to hide.
ഗ7ബ്ര നന്നി ലട ൭09 ഖിവാലടലല്‍നഠ്ോ.
Yeah...
൮൭...
-Let us have a toast. -Let's.
പീലി നമ ധല്ലോ ടല ണമ. ഥീ.
I dedicate my win tomorrow to Miss Sally.
ടമ൮൭ ഡ്ധിത്ന നനാ ടമ ലട നാട ഘ്വാഠ്മ 6 ടല.
Sorry.
ല്‌.
l already dedicated my win tomorrow to her.
ടമ റ ഡ്വധിത്ഥ നല ടയ ടടം1ധഘാമ്ദബത.
So, if we both do it, it's really not so special.
പിര ന്മവാലദ്ധോ നല്ധ്ധ്ത്സത, 19 21 ലിധടന്കെ ൭91.
-Besides, I don't have a drink. -I'll go get you one.
19൮10൩, ടമ൭ 0309 ബ്സ്ധണമന. ടൃ മിഥ ഠ്ല്ാമിദ്ഥ ധന്ധി മമ.
Do you mind if l borrow a few bucks for one of them drinks?
8ഠിലി ഖി ടമ്മ ലബ്ധി ധധിലാലല്‍! ബ്ഗ്ധണമന?
-They're free. -Free? Shoot, what am I doing here?
9 ്ാല ധേന. ല്‌ ധേണമ? .്വാഠ 19൮1 ടമയാധമഠിട്ബി?
I should probably go keep an eye on him. See you at the race.
ടൃ ലാല ഇാഠ1ലഘും1റമ്ഥ ഠി. പ്ധന്പാമ ഗമി വാലിധ്പാമമ ടെ.
Yes, you will see Francesco, but not like this.
൭, ല്വാ॥ ഗമി മിറ മ്പാമ മഥ ൦േടഠോ ബി.
You will see him like-a this as he drives away from you.
ഗ്യ ല്ത്ഥ മബ്വാലിറ റിദ ലാബ്‌ 1ധി൪൭ ഠി നലഠ്ദ്ധിധി ഗമി
That's cute.
11:11
You had one of those made up for all the racers?
൧ഡഗ്യിലാധമലാലറ്റിഡ ധ്യ ടലസ്ധ ടമ മഗ്ല്ന
No.
110൭1൦.
Okay.
വിവ.
-Ciao, McQueen! -He is so getting beat tomorrow!
1൭൦, ീദ്വേലലല്‍്‌ 212 ലി യില ലിം ടം!
Ladies and gentlecars, Sir Miles Axlerod.
7ഥദഥ-4ലഥ റ്ദ്ഗ ൧ഥഗദഗ്ാലമഥ, വ്ഥാല5!ദ൮൧ഥ 57 7747൦5 .ഷറ്ലാറ്‌.
It is my absolute honor to introduce to you
ഉലാബാടെല ൫൭, ടമ 090൩ ണല്പാലിശലിര്ഥ
the competitors in the first ever World Grand Prix.
റാല്ധമ്പാമ്പാല്ധ്പാട ജ്‌ ലാഗഥ്ധബ്ദ ൮൭09 ലാലന്മനമ.
From Brazil, Number 8...
ഉമി ഒലി, ലംമ്പാം 8...
-Hello.
-11ല॥൦.
A Volkswagen Karmann Ghia has no radiator.
011 ഷൌറ്റയനനമബ്ണ ബ് വി9ഠ് 301൦൨.
That's because it's air-cooled.
ടലാദ്ാ റിമ റിടല്ധിറമ്റ ലീ ധഠ്മമ.
Great. I'm Agent Shiftwell. Holley Shiftwell from the Tokyo station.
വട. ടയ ല്ല ടവ്ഡയല।. ൦ ടവനധലി॥ ലവി ദോഷ 7൦1൨൦.
-l have a message from London. -Not here.
ടൃ മഠ നടല്‍ ഠ്ഖ്ലി ॥ഠ0ഠഠ൦൩. പ്ഥാമന ഠി ടബ്‌.
Try the canapés on the mezzanine.
ധാമില നലിത്ഥ ദേശല്വാടട ൮൭0൭9 01 ാലമട ണലബ്ന.
The lab boys analyzed the photo I sent?
ലിഷ നിന്നി ൭൩൨ മഥലിടദ മ്പാല മനാ ടയ മല ഡാ?
What did they learn about the camera?
൧൮3 നലല ല്ഡ മറന ഡാ?
It appears to be a standard television camera.
1-1 1111-15-11 11-18] വണലമ ല്ലധിടുലാ!മടമ.
They said if you could get closer photos next time that would be great.
സിലലല്‍ര ൪൭, ലാബാലില്॥ിത്വാം1ല്‍ ദ്ദ്വാമിദഥ ്വാലഥറ ലാ ലേവ.
This was London's message?
1ധഡ നടടല്‍ ഠ്ഖലി ॥ഠനഠ്ഠന?
No. No, sir.
11021൦ നില ഡാ.
The oil platforms you were on,
ലമ സ്ബര൭ ഠി നാമ ഡാലാലമ്മ ഡം,
turns out they're sitting on the biggest oil reserve in the world.
ലില്ലി മട ണനലഠ് സ്ബതിലലനാടടല് ഠി ദ്ധബി.
How did we miss that?
ാഠലനാനാ ന്മ ാഠിലഖ്ധലാലമടമ?
They've scrambled everyone's satellites.
സീലലര റ൦ഠ്മണ ടലസ്ഡാ ടമല॥1.
The Americans discovered it just before you did.
ലിം ഡണലിര ദ്ലാദമ്ഡ ടലാല്ധന ഗമ
They placed an agent on that platform under deep cover.
സില്ലി 309 ലാലിട॥ റി ലാല്ല ഡ.
He was able to get a photo of the car who's running the entire operation.
൧1 ദ്ദ്വാ% റമമ്പാല ലമ 09 നാഡ ംലടട। ബി.
Great.
വട.
Who is it? Has anyone seen the photo yet?
ടല്വാദ 1൭? ൧03 ടടടില്വാമ 09 ചേ ലമ്പാലിറുമമ്പാല ഡയ?
Nope, not yet.
1മിപാല്ധന 1൭91.
The American is here tonight to pass it to you.
ലിം ഡണലിര മ്രാല 1ല്ാഠ്ദ മഗ നലിമണ ബ്‌.
He'll signal you when he's ready.
൧19 മിരബാലി ട്യയ 01 ഠി ഠ്ഖ്വാലടലഠിഒ.
Good, good.
വട, ാമറുധട.
Oh, no.
൨. ദിട്ചം.
-What is it? -Change of plan.
1ലലല്വാമ? “ധിവ്വ ദേ.
-You're meeting the American. -What? Me?
ഡയ ലിരബ്ധ്പാദ 010ലഥണലിയ. ്വാമ? ടമ്മ?
Those thugs down there were on the oil platform.
ലബൃദ്ഥററമിറി ധാമ ഡ ഒറ ഠി ലാല സ്ബതിണമിമന !ധ.
If they see me, the mission is compromised.
പ്ര നലല സ്പാ ടമ്മ, മ്പ്ടി ന ലോ.
No, I'm technical. I'm in diagnostics. I'm... I'm not a field agent.
൭൮൭ റ്മല്വാഠ്ദ മാറി ല്൩്പിവി, ഠിദ0൦ട0ി൦ ഒധിരാലിമറിലാലിടിവന.
You are now.
ട്ല്ദ്ധമാ, ൭.
I'll take one of them. Thank you.
൭൮൭ മട. ലിനാ 1൪൭51.
Never know which one McQueen will have a hankering for.
ട൮൭ മഥമ്ഡ നമ ടമധ ൭൫൮ നീം നലം
Hey. What you got here that's free? How about that pistachio ice cream?
റല, മ്മ ഠാ ലാലഡനാഠിട്ബി? ഒലലിത്ഥ ടു ല്ടിന്ന ല്ട്മടിം ഡാ?
-No, no, wasabi. -Same old same old.
റമ 1൭ ഡ്൭ടഖാ!. ടമ ഡഖ.
What's up with you? That looks delicious!
൧൧3 നടി മധലിന  നബ്വാടി ടലഠ്ല്ാ!
Little more, please. It is free, right?
ബാമ0 19൭1. ലാലാ, ത്ഥ?
Keep it coming. A little more.
1:11: 1411-11 111:1:]
Come on, let's go. It's free.
॥:11111:111-::11:11:1111:11 11:
You're gettin’ there. Scoop, scoop.
ീമിന്സാദബയയിം ൦൦%, ലേ.
There ya go! Now that's a scoop of ice cream!
-1:11111111:111 ീമമേണ ഡധിമ്വാലധ ധേഡോ!
My condolences.
ടമ ധല്വോ മിയി.
And now our last competitor.
ഉമ്ഥ ദ്ലാലടിമ്ര്ഥ, ാല്ധമ്പാട മഥ ലയ്ചിമ്പ.
Number 95, Lightning McQueen!
വമ്പ 95, 190ബ്നാ നീദ്ധേലംബ്‌
Ka-chow!
1(൭-ലഠഗ്‌
Thank you so much for having us, Sir Axlerod.
ലിന മടി ലയ നലവ്ലസ്പാധയി, ഷഠിലഠഠി.
l really look forward to racing. This is a great opportunity.
൭൮൭ ൭1 ടലാല ധനധിവാലിധസാമ. ബി ാലധാാ ൭09 ലാഖ്‌.
The pleasure is all ours, Lightning.
ബി ലാണാടടല 0൭, 100൩09.
You and your team bring excellence and professionalism
൧ഗ്യിം്മലാദടധിറ മ്മി ണലമ്പാമയ 1ലേനലിമററമന 0 0ഠ്ലടിംലി്ടനല
to this competition.
1ലരാല്മഥഠി നമ ബി.
Somebody get me water!
8ലലിത്ഥ ടയ ഖല
Sweet relief. Sweet relief.
1൭൦റ്റമ൬൭. 1൭൬൫൭.
Whatever you do, do not eat the free pistachio ice cream.
പ്ല ടടടലരി। നലിര്ഥ ഖിടിന്ന ാിടടിം ൮൭09 ലാലഗധേനമ ഡ.
It has turned.
19 ടമ
Sir Axlerod, I can explain.
51 ഷഠിലഠഠി, ടമ ാഠിലി ല്ലി.
-This is Mater. He's... -l know him.
“ബി ീമല. ൧12... ടമ 1൨൭൧ ഠി.
This is the bloke that called in to the television show.
2 11:11:111::11:1:10:11:1:1:1:11-11] 1 മന്മഥ ലിലധിടുല്്ഡ.
-You're the one I have to thank. -No, thank you.
ലിനാ 1യ൭ടിവിഷ്വാമഠിട മധ്യം “11021, ലിന ര൭ടിിശ്വാമര്‍ിട മധ്യം
This trip's been amazin’.
ഗമ ബി ടമ ലാമ.
He's a little excited, isn't he?
൧൭ 2റുമിറലഡ്യദ, മന?
-Mater! -But wait, I... Shoot.
്‌ഥിമല! “ലവി, ടമ... വിന
-Mater. -Has anyone got a towel?
1ഥിമല. -ടലട।മ്വാ ഠി ഡല?
Mater, get a hold of yourself. You're making a scene!
നീല, 1൦ ഗ്യ 0. ഗ്യിറ്മ്പാധാധലംംവല്‍
-But I never leak oil. Never. -Go take care of yourself right now!
“1 ല്വ। ബ്ന൩൭ ടര മലാലനമ നലബ്ഴിം. ലു! ധബടിര്ഥ റ്റി മയ ടലര്മാ!
Comin’ through! Leakin'’ oil. Where's the bathroom? Thank you.
1 ധന്വാഥറല്ധ! ന്തി നലബ്യി ഗീ ാ॥॥!॥ല്ഥ നലനട 1൪൭51.
I gotta go.
ടൃ ലാലിധ ലാല.
Sorry, ladies.
സീമ, ടമധഠ്മി ടലസ്ധമ.
I'm leakin’. I never leak. I never leak.
ടമ 000. 5൭൮൭ മധാനണമ്ലാഠഠ.
I never leak, I never leak, I never leak.
ടൃ മിധ്ാനണമ് ലാം, ടമ ഖിധ്ാലനമ്ാഠഠേ.
I never leak.
ടൃ മിധ്ാനണമ് ലാം.
I never leak, I never leak, never...
ടൃ മിധ്ാലണമ ലാം, മലാല...
Wow-wee!
ഗ7ഠസ-ഡലല്‍
What in the...
൧31...
Hey, that tickles!
പ :1-1111112:1
Okay, McMissile. I'm here. It's time for the drop.
വ്യ ഗീഗീടടില. ടയ ൭ ടാസ്വാല. ീടടമ ധധിലാലമ് നടടല.
Okay, so, the American has activated his tracking beacon.
വവ്യപാല്ഥഥണലിര ദേവ ല്വിര്ഥ ടമ ലാലടമന.
Roger that. Move in.
810൭൨. 3ലലമ ടല.
Stop! Hey!
ലല! ലി!
-You've got to be joking. -What's the problem?
[11111 ഗ്വാ ണടടമലിമ്ബത?
-He's in the loo. -So, goin!
212 റ്ദിമന മ0ഠ്൭ടെ. ചീദ്ദടഥ്റ ടക4കദ൧൨
-I can't go into the men's loo! -Time is of the essence.
ടമ ൭10 നലിംണമടധി മട്ട ല്ലി. (ദ 4ടെഥാധവഥ ഗുദടദ.
All right.
8110൭൨.
Whatever you do, I would not go in there!
ലി്ധിന്നു ലാമ ഗമിലല്ലാധല ടമ 'ഖിനത്ഥ ണടടധിലട ടട ഡി!
Hey! A Gremlin and a Pacer!
ലി! ലല ലേ ഠ്‌ ലോ
No offense to your makes and models,
ടമൃാധിന്ഥ നിലവിലു മ ണംഠ്ല മഴയ,
but you break down harder than my cousin Betsy
'ല്വാ മഗ്ലഠടല്ല്ലാ।॥ ലം ദ്മല്വാമഠ്ദ ടലാധ്വാധ ടയ, 8൦൭
after she got left at the altar!
ടലിലാമട റിമ ്ധുമറി വ്ഗ്ബ്‌
What the... Whoa. Are you okay?
൧31... 0൨. ഗയിം മല്വാമ-ല്വാമ?
-I'm fine. -Hey! Tow truck!
ടമ 9൮% ല്വാമ-ല്വാമ. “ലി! നലിഡധദ്ദ!
We'd like to get to our private business here, if you don't mind.
ദ്രിദ്ധധാഠില, വമി ദ്ദ ലി ാലാമഠി ൮൭09 നലം ഠിടലടടലിവഥ.
Yeah, sorry.
മ, നമ്‌.
Don't let me get in the way of your private business.
ടൃ മല്ലേ ൫9 രാലലിാമഠി മധ്യം.
A little advice. When you hear a giggle and see that waterfall,
ട൭൮൭ 909 മട. 819 മഗ്യി റ്‌ ടാ മ്ജയ റമ ഗ്വാ മ ലനം
you best press that green button.
ല്ദബാധമാ ല്വ്ദ്ധ.
-Thank you. -It's to adjust the temperature.
ലിനാ 1൭ട॥. 19 ധധിംണലല്ടടിര്ഥ ടധ്ധ ൨.
-Got it. -And it's in Celsius, not Fahrenheit.
-83110൨. 19 ഠ്മ്മണന ഠലീട്ധട,ലാധ്യ്ഥ ൦മ്വലവില്.
Get out of here!
1ല്ധല ഠ്മ്ലി ടിബി!
All right, then. And when she starts gigglin’, prepare to be squirted.
810൭൨. ഉമ ലാലാ! റിദ രമ്യ, ാലടലറിദ ധന്ധിലാണഗ്മ് ൨.
‘Scuse me, ma'am.
7 ധസ്വാമററ।പ്ധ, വമ.
Dad-gum pistachio ice cream.
ചിടിന്ന ലട്മടിം ലിവ.
-This cannot be him. -ls he American?
1111111111: -2ദ ഖഥറദ ൧ാലസ്ഷ?
Look out, ladies. Mater's fittin’' to get funky.
പിഒ, ടധഠിലി ടലി. ീട്ലലാലടലഠി ധനധിധാലലമ്പാമ.
-Extremely. -Then it's him.
-ടധഠിമ ബഡ. 30, ന്ദ7൭ ലാലല്‌ടല്ല.
-Hello. -Well, hello.
-11ല॥൦.
A Volkswagen Karmann Ghia has no radiator.
011 ഷൌറ്റയനനമബ്ണ ബ് വി9ഠ് 301൦൨.
Well, of course it doesn't. That's 'cause it's air-cooled.
ടറി ലിം. ടലാദ്ാ റിമ റിടല്ധിറമ്റ ലീ ധഠ്മമ.
Perfect. I'm from the Tokyo Station.
വട. ടമ റ്ദലി മേഡ 17൦1൮൦.
‘Course, Karmann Ghias weren't the only ones.
ചാ ലാധിദ്ഥ നമ ബദ ടല ൭0൭ ാലറ[ഡ.
Besides the Beetles, you had Type 3 Squarebacks with the Pancake motors.
ടല ഒലലില, സല 3 ടറ്ധലാദം ലാമ ണം മിഷ ടമണമ.
-Yeah, okay. I get it. -And before both of them
മ, വ്വ. ടൃ ലമണ. ൧൭൨0 ടലാല്ധന
there's the Type 2 buses.
മാട സല 209൭ ടമന൭.
-My buddy Fillmore's one of them. -Listen!
രഥ ടമു൭, 0॥നം ഉന ടമ നമ. ലല ടലി!
We should find somewhere more private.
1പ്മാല്ധ ദേ॥ി ലസ്വാമ(വത൭ഥാ ലാ ടി.
Gee, don't you think that's a little...
110൭ മഗ്യിലടടമ ധം...
You're right. Impossible to know which areas here are compromised.
ഒലഡി ൭൭ ഥലധ്മ ലിസ നമ ല്വാമവഥാ ടല.
-So, when can I see you again? -Well, let's see.
-ിമഠി।,ാ॥മ 19! നമ ാംല്ഡാലിധമ്പാമ? 1:11 1:11
Tomorrow I'll be out there at the races.
5ടഠ%, ടമ്മ മിരാലറ്ട ഠി പ്പാ ാലിധ്പാമമ.
Got it.
8110൭൨.
We'll rendezvous then.
1പമാലലന്ധ വിടി.
-There you are. Where have you been? -What's a "rendezvous"?
ഡാധന മഗ്ലിറ ൭ നമാ മഡ്മി്ലാലയി!? ഗ്വാ ണമിദ്ധഠ ാനലസ്ധ്‌?
-It's like a date. -A date?
“19 ടലാലി മലി ലസ്ധ. പില! ന്ധ?
Mater, what's going on?
നില, ലാറ ലാലിലിവ?
What's going on is I got me a date tomorrow.
ട൭൮൭ ഠവല ലസ്ധ ടട.
Guido don't believe you.
ധോം ല്ധ്ാലമേയ.
Believe it. My new girlfriend just said so.
ലെ മൃയമില. 7ഠി, ണമാ ടര 1മ൭വാലറ്്ധ.
Hey, there she is. Hey! Hey, lady!
റല, ഡാന ഠി. ലി! ലി, ടദ്ധഠ്മ്ലി!
See you tomorrow!
പ്ധനമ്പാദ 1൭9! ടടം1൨
Guido still don't believe you.
ധേഠ്ം നട മലാല മേ ദേശ്വാ മധ്യം.
I got to admit, you tricked us real good.
൭൮൭ മിഡി, മ്യി്ലഘല്ലബംനാ മ് ലാമി
And we don't like being tricked.
2111 1111-11]: :11111::111:1
What's so funny?
ലാറ?
Well, l was just wearing a disguise. You guys are stuck looking like that.
൭൭൮൭ ടലി നസബമണല. ൧ ടനസ്ഡാ ലിലാംല൨ ധാമ സ്വാ മഗ്യിം.
Allinol? Thanks, fellas. l hear this stuff is good for you.
൧0? നല്നട 1൨൭ട॥൨. ഉലാ താട ധഡയിലന്മ.
So you think.
൧്യിറിഗ്നാലറയ.
Allinol by itself is good for you.
൧൩൦ ടല്യ നനണമനാ വാട [11] 1:11
But after microscopic examination
ലവ ടലിലാമട നലപല്മബിത്ഥ ധി ലമ ബിനാടി,
I have found that it has one small weakness.
ടമ റ്ല്വാമി 15 നലസ്വാധബയി ടവ ഷിലനലീമ.
When hit with an electromagnetic pulse,
811212 റി്ലിര്ഥ ഠിലധ്മറ ല്ല്യംനദഗണലം
it becomes extremely dangerous.
19 നല്വമഠി। മണമ്ധാലാലിമത.
Smile for the camera.
8ലടലഠിമ ധന്ധിധാലയമമ്പാല.
Is that all you want? I got a whole act.
1 ടല്വമ? ടമൃ൭ റിമ ടലി ല്മബാബതിറുമുത.
You were very interested in this camera on the oil platform.
ഗയിം മണമലാല്സ്നമ്ലോമ്ബിതണനലട ബി ടലനട3 ഠി ലാല്ല ബ്ബ
Now, you will witness what it really does.
ട്ല്യവ്ഥമറാ, ഗ്ലാ ഖാ ൮മനാ [വാംലവാധമ്‌.
-Whatever you say, Professor. -You talked up a lot of cars last night.
ധ% ടധിര മ മ്മി, ലഠ്ടടം. ഛഡ്യിലാധ്വ] ലാബിലെ ടലനലിമണ.
-Which one's your associate? -Your mother.
-11:111:111:1-111 111111: വാ മഗ്യി
No, I'm sorry, it was your sister. I can't tell them apart these days.
൨, ദില സീല്‌, 30॥ലാലലസ്വാധാഥ മഗ്ലിം. ൭൭൮൭ ൭0നലമ്പാമ്ലാലാലമമത.
Could I start it now, Professor Z?
ഒലി ടയ സ്ധിലിര്ഥ ടല്ഷയ്ു, ൧0ലട൦ 2?
Go 50% power.
0്റിയ്ിര്ഥ ഷ്ാമഠ്മ വടമ 50%.
This camera is actually an electromagnetic pulse emitter.
ടലാലാബസ്മ, മണലടയ ബ്‌ ാണമറലേ ഠിബധമറ ല്ല്വംണനദഗണല.
What about her? Did you give it to her?
- 1.15]: 11111:111-1[-111:]:11111:0 ൧ഗ്യിലാലിത്നസ ഷ്വാമഠ്ദ റിമ?
The allinol is now heating to a boil,
ട്ല്വ്ഥമാ, നം ല്ലാ നല്ലി,
dramatically expanding, causing the engine block to crack under the stress,
15 നലാല്ബാമറ, നബലാലാത്ഥ 01൦ ലവിന ല്യിം ലിനാ ഭട,
forcing oil into the combustion chamber.
ദമ നലണല്ദ സ്ബതമിംണമടധം 1൭ റ്മിമണ ഘാധിലാല്പാലിത്മ.
How about him? Did you talk to him?
- 1.15]: 11111:111-1[-111:]:11111:0 ഗയിം ഠ്മാലി്ഡ ഠിമ?
What do I care? I can replace an engine block.
ടൃ ്ധ്ാലഠ്ധ!!. ടൃ ാഠില്‍ റമി 100 ബന.
You may be able to, but after full impact of the pulse,
ഗ്ധനാ1ന്ന, ജവ ടല്ലാദട നല്ല്ല ടമ റി ബധ്മ്ബയ ടലാദധ്ബും
unfortunately, there will be nothing to replace.
നമി, മദ ദ്വ 9 മിഷ ഗാല.
How about him? Does he have it?
- 1.15]: 11111:111-1[-111:]:11111:0 ദലറഠ്മഡ 2ഠ്ദ ഠ്ലറ്മ്ഥ വിമ?
That's him. He's the one.
ഉ॥മിമവഘലലല്‍്മത.
-Roger that, Professor Z. -No!
മന, 70ഠ്ലടം॥ 2. റമി
Yes, sir.
ച, ഡല.
We believe the infiltrator has passed along sensitive information.
(ബി ലാല മേ ലാലല്ധ്ധോ ദമ നല്ല നല്റഡണമ ടട.
I will take care of it before any damage can be done.
൭൭൮൭ മിര്ഥ ബട ടലാല്ധന നമടമിമ്വാടടദ്പലാലില്വ.
The project is still on schedule.
൧0൦]ല്ധബി നാട്ാല്]ല്ട നലാറിവ്ധുദഠ്ധല.
You will find the second agent and kill him.
മലി ലിബു ദ്ധ ദ്ദബാധഗ്ധി ഠി.
Japan, land of the rising sun,
പ്ല്യാഥഥ, ഗ൦്റദഗദ 7?ദ4കഗാദഥ്‌ £ലഥ്‌,
where ancient tradition meets modern technology.
൨ ഗാദഗദ ൧2ലിദഥഗുദ ൧ല്‌ലാാഥറ്റഥ 73൨൩5! [ദഗാദ റ്കഥ ?ല്ഗഠഠ൫ 7?ഠറ്ലാ.
Welcome to the inaugural running of the World Grand Prix.
ടല്കഗാദ! റ്ദ!ദഗറ ൧൭ ൭൧7ക൧റ്‌ ൧ഗനഗഥഥദ)ഒ0 ഥലക്ഗദ.
I'm Brent Mustangburger with racing legends
൭൮൭ 8ലവ്ധടമററാധാല, ദ്മബാലടാണമ-ടമനാ ടമ്മ,
Darrell Cartrip and David Hobbscap.
ഉല ല്ല റമ ദധി 0ിവാടമ്വോ.
There's never been a competition like this before.
-1111-11:1] ഒറ ാലിധമ്പാമമ ടലാലി ബി.
First, allinol, making its debut tonight
ഉലമണട ടല്യി॥, 20൦ ഠിേലിത്ഥ ധറധിധ്ധ്ഥാപ്ധ്ധനാ യ,
as the required fuel for all these great champions.
ടലാഠറ്റലി ലാലി ദ്വ 0991 ടലസ്ഡല്ധലപ്ധമ്ത ബി.
Second, the course itself.
14ലദ്ധാ,ലാലിധമ്പാമമ് ബി ടലി.
And it's like nothing we've ever seen before.
ഖ്൩ ്ദേ്ലാ്ട ൮൭0൮ 1൩.
David, how exactly does this competition work?
൧൭൨൨, ൧ദറ്ദഗാദഗകഷഗ ൧ല്ഥ്ാഥദക്ഗ 777 ഒഥ നദദഥഷഥ?
All three of these street courses are classic round-the-house racetracks.
ലററ 77ലല്ഗ്‌ ഒറ്ദ7൭7 ൧ദ൭ദ്യാകഥ ൧൩൧3 4ഘല്ദ 435
This means that the LMP and formula cars
ലല്‌, 2.70 റ്ദഥ ഘലദ 7ഠഗഗാല്ദ
should break out of the gate in spectacular fashion.
ഒ൭൧ ഗുനഥ്ദ്ഥ ധാല്കദ്ഗന്ഥറ്ദധ റ്ലാറ്റകഗ ॥7ലാദ?.
Look for Francesco Bernoulli, in particular, to lead early.
൧്ഥ൦ടഠാ £ലഗാഥ്ഥ്‌ ന്ദ ഒ൭൧ ഗുലറ്ദഗഥ്ഥ്‌.
And with technical turns throughout, GT and touring cars,
7ദ7 റ്൦റ്റദഥ ടല്ല്ഠഗ-ടല്ല്റ7 7ക4ദഗാ, ൭ റ്ദ്ഥ 4ലല്ദ ൧ വ്ഥദഗടലമ്‌,
like Spain's Miguel Camino, should make up ground
ടലാലസ്‌ ി779ഥല്‌' ൦ദഗഠ റ്ക്ഥ്‌ ടലാദഗ)ഠ!്‌, ൧07ല ഗാുലറ്റല്ദനുദ
but 1 doubt it'll be enough to stop Francesco
4ദ്വ 74ല നഥാവ്വഗ 4൭% റ്ദ്യാദ% ഗാലറ7ട'ദഗറ ൧ഥ൦ടഠ
from absolutely running away with it.
ധധിധുമധ നല്മ്ഡ്ധി നലല.
Whoa now. Hold your horsepower.
മഥ ഠ്ധ്ധ. ടല, ടാ.
You forget the most important factor,
എഗ്യിറലിധാദ ടദധ നലിനാലാല്ിനു,
that early dirt track section of the course.
11:11 ::111-111:11)11:1:11:111-1:1 ാലിധ്പാമമറ ബി.
The dirt is supposed to be the equalizer in this race.
പ്ദ'ദഗ 770 ടലാദധലദ ഗുഹഗുഷ്ഗനദ്വഷദ ൧൭735 ൧ാലടക്'ററ്റദഗ ഗുലല്വ.
French rally car Raoul CaRoule
6ലല്‌ദ 7 ൧7ലദ്ഗധല്ട, ദാല്‌ €കഠഥ്൦,
is counting on a big boost through there.
൧ലഗദധഗദ്വ റ്ദ്യാദ! ഗല്്യാലാഥദ്ധഗ്‌ £റ്ലറ്ല്ക്ഥലദ ന്‌ ടല.
And don't forget Lightning McQueen.
2ക൧ദ൧ഗഒഥ !൧൭, 2007070 77ഠേഥ൦ഥ.
His mentor, the Hudson Hornet,
൧ലു27൧൧00൩)൭, 7൧7൧05 ഠഥ ൧4077൦,
was one of the greatest dirt track racers of all time.
ഗാലഥ്ാദ്ധദഥ ടദ'ദഗ ടലാഥദ്ഗ ൧ലഗ്മണമദ !ദദ7 72൭൧൭7 ൮൭൧ 4ലഗലാദ.
In my opinion, McQueen is the best all-around racer in this competition.
303 ാലഠ്ല്വാ ടയ, ീശേധലല ഒഠ്മിദ്വാല്ധമ്പാദ ടലാദ ലാലി ലാമി.
Really, Darrell, you need to clean your windshield.
ഉല, മഡ്ല്ലാലിധ ാലട്ബത്ഥ ലേന്പ്ന മധ്യം.
You're clearly not seeing this for what it is: Francesco's race to lose.
ഗ്യ മിഗമലമ്പാലിം ത്ഥടേടഠോ ലിദ്ഥ നല്ലി ലാലിധമ്പാമമ ബി.
It's time to find out. The racers are locking into the grid.
77ദ ഗുദടദ ധാലലാഗഥ. ഗദ ഥാല്ഥ്സാഥദ ൧ല൦ട൦വ്‌ദ വ്‌ ?ലന്യാദ? ഗ)ാദട70-നദട7റ്‌.
Speed. lam speed.
1%ലില്ധാഥ. ടമ ലവ.
Really? You are speed?
ഒലധിയ? ഷഗ്ലി്ലല്?
Then Francesco is triple speed.
ദ്രിമ്ധാല!ധ, മഥ൦േടഠോ 1903 1൪ ലാധ്വില്യ.
Francesco likes-a this McQueen.
മഥ ൦േടഠോ ടധിര സീദ്ധവേലല.
It's-a really getting him into the zone.
112 ്ഥ൦േടഠേ ലാലടലഠി.
He is so getting beat today.
൧19 മിത്ഥ രി ലധിംലി ബി.
-Your suspension sets look good. -Tire pressure is excellent!
ടല ടധട്വാലട। മഡമിമമ്പാമ്ലാമലിം. ലിമ മവ മണ നലാദ്‌
-He's got plenty of fuel. -And he's awesome.
212 ഠ്ദാമബയയിലാമ്മ്ല ദ്വ. -൧മ്ഥ ഠി നലാധമ്്ത്ഥ.
Why is he in the pits? He's so exposed.
1ലദ്വാ ദിവാലി 0? 14ലദ്ധഠ്ധിമ്ബമ്ല്ദട ൭൭൫൭.
It's his cover.
ധി ടന.
One of the best I've seen, too. Look at the detail on that rust.
൧൮൭00 നാലി ണമ ടമ ൭. ലുലിയ ഡ.
It must have cost him a fortune.
പാടി നലല ധനം ടട॥ത്ഥ.
-But why hasn't he contacted us yet? -There's probably heat on him.
“ലവ ലല്വാദ ഠി ാല്ധന 0ധാഥാന്മ? 1(ഒറ്ധഠ്ധിമനബ സ്ഥറിന്ന പ ടല്മണമ്‌.
-Be patient. -Right, of course.
-ഒലടദ്ധാല. അ, ടഥഠ20 ഗഡ.
-He'll signal us when he can. -Then we find out who's behind all this.
-212 മിലി ടുഖ്യലാ॥ിാഠില്‍. ബന്ന ലദ്ഥ ്പ്ഡ ലിമ.
As they head into the palace hairpin, Francesco builds an early lead.
&൭4൯ ഗാലറ്ധദശ്വാന്‌ ടല്ല്ഥഗ 7ലദഗ ൪ 51൭൧൭, ൧7മഥ൦ലെടറഠറ 79 നലറ്ട്ധല്ല..
Hang on, boys. Here comes the dirt.
£ലഫ്‌മ്ധദഥ, ടല8. പ്ദ'ദഗ 7ദദഗ ദ്4ദ്ഥ ൧ലസനാലഥ്‌ദ.
Slipping and sliding, baby.
7ലറല്ഥഗലഥ ന്ഥ റല'ഠഗറടഠ7.
McQueen, it's time to make your move!
ീഗ്ധേടല, ടലര്ാറ്റ നടടമ ഗ്യ ധധിഗണലഘല്ദ്‌
10-4, Mater.
10-4, നീല.
Oh, boy! Francesco's brought to a screeching halt!
ചദഗാദ്ധ 7ഒഥ൦ടഠോ 7ലിലാല്‌്‌
Lightning McQueen is the first to take advantage.
2070൧09 77൦ഠേഥംഹ 72ലറദഗ7ാ2! 4൭5 ല്്യാദ4ക൧.
And just like that, folks, Francesco's lead is left in the dust.
൧ഹറ്റദഗ ൧൦൮൧ 5൭൭, ൧ഥ൦ടഠാ ഥാറദ'ദഗ ന്‌ ൧ലഒ൭൧റ.
Nice call, Mater. Keep it up.
1ലാധഡടമമ ലാലി നീല. ലലടടന.
McQueen looks happier than a roll bar at a demolition derby!
൧7ഠേലംല ഘഥാദ!ദഥ ദഒഗാദ 0൧൧)൧7൭
Everyone's jostling for position as we hit the asphalt again.
ലല ഗലലാഥള്‍്‌ 4റ്ഥറ്ലഷ ഥ്ദ മാഥ്‌ദ ഗലാദടഥ്ഥ്ദകടകഗ ൧2ല്ഥമ്ാ.
Francesco lost a lot of momentum in the dirt.
൧ഥ൦ടഠാ ഘ്വ്‌ദദറക്ഗ ഗാാസഹഥഥ്നഷ്യദ ടലാദടദ വ്‌ ദക൧ 4ദ7ക൨.
He's got serious work ahead of him if he wants to get back in this race.
൧3 ൧ല്ല ഥലഘ്‌ദ 7ദട ൧൫൭ ഗമന ഗുഹറ്ദഗഥ്ഥ്‌ ടഥ്‌ദ.
The racers hit the Rainbow Bridge, with its 360-degree loop.
ലല 22൧3 ൨ പദഗാഥദ!ദഗ ൧ല്‌കഗര്‌ 9൭൧90 നല്വാഥഷ ഗവ്യ 360 ൭൧൭൧.
-It is time. -Roger that.
ചീദ്ദടദ്ഗ)ുദ റ്‌ 20൧൭. -83110൨.
Miguel Camino has blown an engine!
൧൧൮7 77ദലല' ഗദാം ഗ7?ല്ല!ഥാ്‌
Very unusual, Darrell. He's been so consistent all year.
കഥ്ഗറ്ററഥഗ 7ഒ സ്ടകഥവ്ക, ൧2൭൧ലെ. ൧3 ദാദ ൧൧ഥട51ല ട ലാദധ്'ദഗറ !കഗഥ.
-You gotta be kidding me. -What is it?
ശഡ്യിലാദടി ലാലു. 1ലലല്വാമ?
-The tow truck from the bathroom. -The bathroom?
212 ലഡഥഴ്മ ഠി ॥0॥॥ല യ. -81॥ല്ഥ?
The one the American agent passed the device to.
ലയ ൧ഥണലിരഡ റാലി മിട ഷ്യ.
-What about him? -He's in the pits!
-1ഒലദ്വാമ റ്ലറ്റമറ റിമ? -21ലാലമഠി ഠി
Not for long.
11ഠ്മിധമറി.
-Hold on. I think I've got something. -What is it?
പി ്ധ്ധ. ടമൃത്്ധ്പാമ ടടടധമധ. ഗ്വാ ഠിമ?
The Pacer from the party last night.
1ധ ദേ വിലാ ടലനലിമണ.
I'm cross-referencing with the photos from the oil derricks.
11118111] 1:1:11:1:111:1:1॥ ഠി ലബ്ബ.
Yep. His VIN numbers match.
൫൭. ംസ്വാം ഗി ടന.
Anyone with him? He won't be alone.
൧0൭ ട൦ട।ല്വാലാലടമനാബമ? ൧1 മ സ്ധണാന്സാലടലം ത്ഥ.
Conducting analysis on the target. He's not the only one here.
൭൭൮൭ ടല നലാമ്നലിടമ ടട. ഒധിത്ഥ ദി ടദ്യദ വിട.
Three, five... They're everywhere. And they're all closing in on...
൧൧3 093, 1൩3... റീലല്ര ഠി നല ല്വാമ ഥമ നലല നലഠ്ല്‍ി...
Oh, no! Finn? Finn, where are you?
൨, ഠ്ചറ ററ? 0, മ്മി! നമ്മ?
Get him out of the pits. Now!
ക ഥ്൦ഥഥ ന്ദ 4ഘ്ലദ്ധ റ്ദ്ല്‌ 27? ടല്ദഷഗഥ്‌
Some of them fellers is really loud!
ഒബി ടട ബാര ടണാഠ്ധ്വമാ
-Can you hear me? Over. -What?
-8ല7ലു ൭ ഥ്ലാറ്ക7? ഘെ. ്വാമ?
Get out of the pit now! Do you hear me?
ല്ല റ്ദല്‌ 2 ടല്ഷ7ഥറ്‌ ൧൭ ഥ്ലാറ്ക7 “റി
Hey. I know you! You're that girl from the party last night.
റല. ടമ്മ ശമി മധ്യം. എഗ്യിറുമഠിട ദ മനി ടലണല്മന.
You wanna do our date now?
ഗ്യ ലലിവാലദബി സ്വ ടല്ര്മമാ?
Guys, too much chatter. Let's keep this line clear.
(ധാമ, വത്ഥറിമാനണ്ധല. മടി മിമബിന്മ്ലിട.
Smoke from number 10, Clutchgoneski!
ഛീടദ്വയ 7ഘ്ലക്ഗ റ്ദ7്‌ 70722൦07 70, 7ഥ്ധററഗംടഗ്‌
There's no time for messing about! Get out of the pits!
ദ 45% ദ്ദ ഗദടദ ഗദധഗാദ്ധ-ഗാദ്ധഥ ല്ല റ്ദല്‌ാ77
Is there going to be cable where you is so I can watch the rest of the race?
൧3 ടി യാല്‍ ഠി ലന്പാമ മസ്യി ധധി ടമ ംന്ഠബലാലിധ്പാമ് ബി?
-You're running out of time! -They're coming. Get him out of there!
ഛ്വടെഥഥ്ക്ക നദടക പ്ീലലയ റിമ0റ. 8 ഠി ഘ്ധമഥ്‌
I'm trying. Get out now.
൭൮൭ ടല ലാട. 1ല്ധല്॥ ടല.
l usually like to have a proper detailin'’ done before I meet a lady friend.
ലട ടമ്മ ടധിരാലിലിമ ഠ്ധ്ധ ടലാല്ധസ്ാലുമ! ലസ്ധ.
-Finn McMissile! But you're dead! -Then this shouldn't hurt.
00 ഗീണിടടില്‍! ഡയറക്‌ ന! ിമഠി।, ബി മടി മ൦ണബയി്സത്ഥ.
Miss Shiftwell?
ലടവ്്ഡലി?
I've got him in the back alleys east of the garages.
ടമ ടധ്ധി ൭1൭1൦0൦090 ലലലിദ്ഥാ 1:11: 11:11: 1111 :1:14-1
Multiple assailants are closing in quickly.
8ലാലഘ്വാാധമ സ്ധടധ മിന്ന നലമ്വാന്സത.
Keep him moving. I'm on my way.
ടി ഠി ലട ലാലി 11:1::111:1- 181111
Hey, new lady friend, you like flowers?
റല, മഗാബാമല, മഴയ ടധിയാധമ?
What?
൧്പാമ?
No! Don't go in anywhere. Just keep moving.
110൭1 ൭00 നമടധിലിഭ നമനമ-ണമന൭. പ്ലിമഥ ലഡട.
-Stay outside. Got you. -Outside?
ിമിമ ഠിധല. 310൭൨. 21?
Whoa! McQueen suddenly moves to the outside.
1൪൭൧! 7൩ഥദ-ഥ൧ദ ൧70േഥംഹ ൧ല൮൦൦൭ ൧൭ ൧ദ്ധദവ'ദഗ 7ലദ.
1 cannot believe what I saw.
ക ഥ്ഗറ്ററഗ 7ഒ0 ധ്ടക്ഗവ്‌ര.
That was a bonehead move to open up the inside like that!
770റ്കഷഥ ഗാലാഥഥ്ദ 7ധഥറ റ്ദദന മാദ !7 ടദഗറ്ദ ൧ഠഠഠ7.
That might have cost McQueen the victory!
720൧ ഗാഗ ൮൧ 2) ലഥദ൧ദ൮൧ഥ ൧70േഥംഹ 4൭൭൨
This time, I'm going to make sure you stay dead!
യി ബി, ടമ മിരബവാടട്ിദ്ഥ മയി!
You're doing brilliantly. Now just stay focused.
൧3വ്ദ'ദഥഷഥ 70035 റ്ലറ്റകഗ ൧൭. ടല, ?ധ്ന്യാഥ്ഷഥ ൧ലഗദ7ദഥ.
What's that? You want me to head toward that ruckus?
വാഡ? ഗ്മ ടാലി 1൭ മയി ലിഗ ഡാ?
No! Don't go down that street.
സറ്ദ്റ ദഥറ്ുദ്ഗ ഥല്‌ 4൭ ഒ൭൧ 40.
Wow! A live karate demonstration!
7 ഉലനംറടനാടി വയല
Stop it, Mater. Just sign off.
ട്ധറ്്വ്ല ഡം, നീല. ലവവടിര്ബടയയ.
And here they come, the two leaders.
720൧ ഗാഥ ഗാലല്, റല ഥല്ഥധസാഥദ 4ലമമ്‌.
Bumper to bumper as they approach the finish line!
൧ലടക്'ററ്ഗ ടലവ്‌ ൪ റുദല്‌ടക്ഗ ധാലക്ഗുദ!.
-It's close! -Francesco's the winner!
൧ലടകദ്ധഗറക്ഗ ഒ ദന ടല -൧ഒഥ൦ടഠേഗദഗ റ്‌ദ്‌
McQueen's number two.
൧7ഠേഥംല വ 7ല്്വാദ! 4റ്ല൭.
That was cool! Can I get your autograph?
ലാസ! 8൦1൨ ടമ ദ്ല്രാദ്മിദ്ഥ ഥഠ്ദ ഥമ മസ്ല്റ
Where did he go?
14൦ നമ ഠി ലാലറ!?
Our rendezvous has been jeopardized. Keep the device safe.
൧ല്‌ലാലകഗ !ഗ്ദ 73% ടലക്ഗാദ!. പ്ദറ്ുദ ദദ7 74ല റ്ലറ്റകഗ ൧൭൧൦.
-We'll be in touch. -Dad-gum, did I miss our date?
-ടദുദ ൭൧ ഗഥഥമ്‌ ദഘ്വദധ്‌. ടമ ലിലാമട മല ലസ്ധിന്മാ?
-Francesco! -Francesco, over here.
-്ഥടേടഠോ! മേടം, ഠി ടബ്‌.
What was your strategy today?
൧്വാ3 ടാ ഗലി ബി?
Strategia? Francesco needs-a no strategy.
ടന? മഥ ൦േടഠോ ജിധാലിധിത്ഥ ടന.
It's-a very simple.
1:11 1:111-:11:1
You start the race, wait for Lightning McQueen to choke, pass him, then win.
൧ഗ്യിലാലിധസാമ, ഡേ നീ ഖമ ടിലാ, 00൦0 019 ഠ്‌ ണന.
Francesco always-a wins. It's-a boring.
മഥ൦േടഠോ ടല്ല്ധ നല. 1 നലബ്പാംടബിത്ഥ.
You were in trouble for a while.
ഗ്യ ടലാലന്‍ി നലാടദ്ല്ോ! നടി ഖമ ടലല്‍ഷലി൨൭.
That dirt track section had you crawling.
യി മണമ്ല്ാലില്മ്ഥ 1:11 1:1:111:11:111 111111
To truly crush one's dream, you must first raise their hopes very high.
വ൩ധിഗനമറഗേോത്ഥ സ്ഥി ടട, ാലിശ്ഥ നലല ല്്വാമഥ ഉദ്ടധ.
-Mater! -Hey, McQueen! What happened?
്‌ഥിമല! 11ലി, നീശ്ധേലലബ' വ്വ ൮൫0൮ലാലില്വ?
Is the race over? You won, right?
ഉലിധമ്പാമമറ ദ്ദ മണ ൧ഡഗ്യിം നല, തന?
Why were you yelling at me while I was racing?
1ലദ്വാ മഗ്യിലലാന്നാ ടലനമട ടമ്മ രാലിധമ്പാമ?
Yelling? You thought... That's funny right there.
“ലററ്റിന്ന്? ഗ്യ... ൨, ഡാധോട്ടേ്ബയര.
No, that's ‘cause I seen these two fellers
1ലിപ്ധ ടലാലാ ടമ്മ ലനമമ്പാമ ദ്ധാവാധമ ടമ
doing some karate street performance.
ാധമാലഡബ്യധിത്സിത്വമം.
It was nutso. One of ‘em even had a flame-thrower.
ഖമ 1953. 5൭151 ടല ദ്മല്വാഠ്ദ നലല ഠ്ദാലയല്പാധ ലവ.
A flame-thrower? What are you talking about?
ലൃയഘമ്പാധ ഖാ? ൧3൮309 ഗ്ല്ലരവിര്?
-I don't understand. Where were you? -Going to meet my date.
ടമ മിവ്ല്റമന. (ഭ നമ മഗ്ല്ല്ാലഠി? “0ധിധാലുധ്വാ ലന ഗമബ്മ ടമ.
Your date?
ലന ഡബ്‌ മധ്ല്റ
She started talkin’ to me as a voice in my head, tellin’ me where to go.
ട്ഖമബയ സ്ഥി ലിമ ഷ്വാല്ട ടമ്മ, മാലി മമ ദ നമ ടമ൭ലാലിധ ലാലി.
-What? -Wait a minute.
്വാമ? പ്രി ഠ്ധ്ധ.
-I didn't screw ya up, did I? -l lost the race because of you!
ടൃ 91 നലബധടമ്വ്ര്ഥ മഗ്മ്പാധിത്ന? ടമ മില ഠിടലാദ്ധിവ്ഥ മമ
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
ീലിമ്ഥ ടമ൭. ടമ ലധാല്്ദ്ധാല്ധ.
An imaginary girlfriend? Flame-throwers?
ലന ഡാബ്ട ലല്രമ? ലൃയഘമ്പാധ ഖാ?
This is exactly why I don't bring you along to these things.
ടലാലാ ബിമ൨ ടമ്മ ലം ലലിലാമഗെ മയി 1ലരാല്ധമ്പാമമബാല്റബ്‌.
Maybe if I, l don't know,
്ധനാിന്ധപ॥ിര ടയ, ബര്വ്മ,
talk to somebody and explained what happened, I could help.
ലമി ലാവാ ാലില്വം, ടമ സ്ധനാിന്ന ലോ നമ്പാബധ.
I don't need your help! I don't want your help!
ടമ മിധ്ാലിധിത്ാബധാമ മഗ്യിറ ട൭൮൭ മന്ദാ ധി
Hey, there he is!
ല്ല, ഡാന ഠി!
-McQueen, you had it in the bag! -Yeah! What happened?
“ീമദ്ധേംല, മഗ്മിധല്പാ നമ! ട്‌! ഷ്ഠ ൮൭0൭ ാലില്വ?
I made a mistake.
൭൭൮൭ ൭൨ ലട.
But I can assure you, it won't happen again.
ച്വാ ടമ ലാല്ല, [മ മറമബാലധിമ.
Look, we know what the problem is and we've taken care of it.
ദ “ദല ദ്ഠാദ ഗാദടദ'ദഗഥദ റ്ദഗ ഒഗ്്‌ ദ ഗലാറ്ഥടക്ഥലട.
Lightning McQueen loses in the last lap to Francesco Bernoulli
20൩൧9 77 േഥംഹ 4൭ഒ൧ വ്‌ ധാഥടഥറ്ഗ ദ്ഗ്ഥ൦ :ഘ്ഥാദറ്ദ £൭൧൦ടഠോ £ലനാഗഥ്ഥ്‌
in the first race of the World Grand Prix.
റ്ദ'ദ7 ൧ാല്ഗ്സഥദദഥ ലാലാ ഥ്‌ ൧7നഥഗഥ്ഥ്‌.
And three, count ‘em, three cars flamed out
1൮9 ൧ഘല്ദ )൭ഥറ 7ലാദ്'ഷ്ധ
leaving some to suggest that their fuel, allinol, might be to blame.
72ല70൧ഥ൮൭൧ ട്യാല്ഡ്‌ദട! ഒ 49 ഗാഥവ്ഗ വട ലാക൧൭൧ ൧7ല ൭77൧70൪.
Allinol is safe. Alternative fuel is safe.
൧0൩൦ ടല. ഒച്ഥ ലി മലനാ ടല.
There is no way my fuel caused these cars to flame out.
1210 സ്ധഠിന്നാല്മ ലവി ടമ്മ നല്ബുലാലാ।്ഥ നലലര ലലാലിത്വ.
The jury may still be out on whether allinol caused these accidents,
ലഘിധ്യധഥി നട ഖ്ലാടടറി ടന 3ഠ്ദ 911൩൦ 0ബലാലാ നലി്ണാബ്ധ,
but one thing's for sure,
'ല്വാ ലാവാ മട മില,
Lightning McQueen blew this race.
220൩൧9 77 േഥംഹ (ദഒ൧ റ്ദ'ദ7 ൧ാലി്‌ഗ്സഥദദദ 7.
Team McQueen can't be happy right now.
൧ല൧)0൭൧൦ 17൦ഠേലല ലാ! £ദ ഗലാഥ773 ടല്ഷഒഥറ.
Welcome to Tokyo International Airport.
ടല്ദഗാദ റ്ദ!ദഗറ 4൪൭ 2. ദ്യദ്ഗറ്റദഗ 7ലദഗറ ൧7ദഗ7ദ്ധാദഥറ്റടദ 700൮൦൧.
-Come with me, please, sir. -But I'm ‘onna miss my plane.
“ബല, ടയ ടമ്മ. “1 ല്വാ। ടമു൭ മിഥ ലിലാദട ലാലലാ.
-Right this way. -Doggone it.
൧9൨. [11111
This is about my hook, ain't it?
ബി ാധിത്ഥ ഠിടലാല്ിത്ഥ ട്റോഡിം ടമയര,ലാധിത്ന?
I know I should have checked it, but I can't, really.
സീമാ ടയ മധ ണനലനലിദാബമം 'ല്വാ॥ ടമ 9൭931.
Look. It's attached to me.
19 ഠിധാധനഠിത്ന വാദ ടമ൭.
Hey, I know you. You're that feller from the karate demonstration.
റില്‍, ടമ ലല മഗ ഗഡ്യിന്ല ൭09 0൭ ്നണംടന്മടി ദ്മ൭ ൮.
I never properly introduced myself.
൭൮൭ ൭1 ടല്പാമ നല്പാലിഘലലിത്ഥ റല.
Finn McMissile. British Intelligence.
00 നീണിടടി॥ം. ൧ലിടിന്ഥ ഒല്രിട.
Tow Mater. Average intelligence.
1 ഠഗ7 [മല ലാന വലാ ടലഠ്ലണമമ.
Who are you with? FBI? CIA?
൧ഗ്യിലാല്‍ലശ്ലദ ധനധിം ടില്പാ? ലവ? മ?
Let's just say I'm AAA affiliated.
8ഠിലി റിയലി, ടയ മ൨॥ ൧൧൧.
I know some karate.
ടൃ മിഡിയ.
I don't want to brag or nuttin’, but I got me a black fan belt.
൭൮൭ മലം ലിശ്വാവാടടദ്, ലവി ടമ 390൭ ൭ ടമ ബ്യണ.
-Wanna see some moves I made up? -You're being followed.
പലി ലച ല്വാമമ് ടമ്മ? ഡയ റിലരി.
This first one, I can reach into a car's hood
ലേമിധാലമണട, ടമ ാഠിലി ല്വോലി ധാ ലല,
pull out his battery, and show it to him before he stalls.
'ഖലിവാമ്ല്ബര ല്ധല ദ ഡബ്ധം 1ഘ്യാഠ്ദബ൭ ടലാല്ധന ലപ്൩ബ൭ ൩൭൫.
I call it, "What I accidentally did to my friend Luigi once."
ടൃ ലിഖ ലച, "ചടി ലിം ടല 0൭ ടമു൭ ധാ ൨191.”
There he is!
1ധ്വാഥന ദില
Look, I probably ought to go. I'm about to miss my flight.
ടൃ ലാലിധ ലാല, ടമ 0ല്പാ 1നാഠ്ദ്മ്്ാലലാമണാമന ടമു൭.
-Don't worry. I've taken care of that. -Whoa!
പ്രഥാന ലട. ടമ്മ ഠ്൭0൨ ധബടിതസത. മവ
Hang on!
8ല്മ്മബ്‌
This is first-class service.
ബ്വിദ്വാലിസ്ിന്നേമമ്നശലിടട ലമണമ.
You don't even have to go through the terminal!
ച്ധ്വാല്ധ നടാ നലദ്്ധി ന്ബസലി!
Your karate partners is back there.
ഉമടാററാബിയയമ മയി ഠി ാലല്ര്ഥ ടമ.
They look like they tryin’ to catch up!
പ1സ്വാമിസ൭ നലല ധോദ ഷവദ്ധിസ്ല
Drive forward. Whatever you do, don't stop!
ലഡട നലനമഥഠ്ധ 1൭ ലാമ. പ്ല ടടടലരി ലാലി!
-Whoa!
മവ
Is everything okay back there?
ടല്ഡാബമ ദ്വ ഠി ലാലലാ ടമ്മ?
Finn, it's Sid. I'm on approach.
00, ബി ട്‌. ടമ റ ലനാ ട്വാദി.
Roger that.
8ക40൭൧.
‘Member that whole thing about me not stoppin’ no matter what?
003 ലലാ മയി മ്ലധാ॥ ടമ ലാല്ല്ി ൭9?
I knew I shoulda done carry-on!
ടമ മ്ഡ ടമ നണമററ മധലാഗെ ാറ്റമടി മുമ്ബ്‌
Thanks, old boy.
ലിനാ 1൭ട11, ത്യ.
-You got it, mate. -Hey, doggonit!
130 നടി, യ്മ. ലി, മയേമില്വ
Look, it's my imaginary girlfriend!
11031, ലന ഡബ്‌ ല്രമ്ഥ ടമ!
Come on! Get in here!
കവ നീടടധിറ്മ്ലസ!
I tell you what, you really do want this first date, don't ya?
൧ഗ്യിലാലമ്ധാലല നിവാല്ദബി। ലസ്ധ,ലാധിത്ന?
That's a no-quit attitude right there.
121 നല ലി ലാധഡട ൭5൭.
What the...
൧31...
Hold on, Sid.
ലമാ, ടി.
Come on, Finn! It's now or never!
ലാ, 0ബ ബി ടല്യ നടല്‍!
Hold on!
8ല്മ്മബ്‌
By the time you read this, ! will be safely on an airplane flying home.
പ്ല ദല ഗ്നഥദദേ ഗഠ7ദ 7, ടദ൮൭ റ്ദധ റ്൭ദ൧7 ലാലല്‌കദദദഗ ൧൧൭൧0.
I'm so sorry for what I did.
ീ7ദദ് ദ5 ദ്യാദ 109 ടദ൮ഒ !ദ൮൨൮൭൧.
“I don't want to be the cause of you losing any more races.
1 :111:1111:1:11111-1111:1] ാബുലാലാ ഭ്യിമ്മ മധ്യം.
“L want you to go prove to the world what I already know.
"ട്ട നമി ഗമിവാധിവിര്ഥ ഘലാമദ്ദ ്ധബ്ദ ഖാനാ ടയ ഠ്0 ദ്വ്ഡ.
“That you are the greatest race car in the whole wide world.
"ച്ചഡ ഗമി ലമ ധാ ലലാ ഠി ടല്ധഡി േ്ബ്മ.
“Your best friend, Mater."
"ദല്വാഠ്ദ മിമബിന്ഥി മ്യിപ്റില.”
I didn't really want him to leave.
ടമൃാധിമബമ മിലി പാലി.
Wait, there's more here.
ധാ, 391൭91.
“PS. Please tell the hotel
എട്ട. 7ംംബാധാല്യ്സഡ 0ലല്‍
“[ didn't mean to order that movie.
"ട്ട ദിവാലി നണട നിണ.
“[ thought it was just a preview and I didn't realize l was paying for it.
"ട്ട മിത്സിദ ധേന ടലഠ്ധ്ഥ റിമ യി്മ്ഡ ലാലാല.
“PPS. That's funny right there. PP."
5. ധഡ രാധ. ൧.”
There are a few more pages of PS's here.
൧03 ലാലാലദ്വാഠ ന്ധി 05 ഠി ട്‌ി.
Well, at least 1 know if he's at home, he'll be safe.
ടല്ഡാററഡയമണ്ുമ, ടര മധ 11൭ ഠി ഠ്മ്വാല॥ം ഠി ടലമണമ.
That's how I like to start the day.
ടൃ ടധിര ലി വമാ ലാലസ്ധിദ ലാബ്‌.
You never feel more alive than when you're almost dead.
൧ഗ്യില്ടടമ മനലാനലറ [1-11-11 11111
Yeah. I hope that device didn't fall off.
൭. ടമൃ൭ ല്വാ ലയ ല്ലഘിം.
Whoa!
ഗവ
That's the closest I ever been to missin’ my flight.
൭൮൭ മലാലനമ ല്ല 1നാഠ്മ്മബ്ലാലലനാമഥനാമന ടലാലല്‍ ധ.
That was...
19...
-Still in one piece? Great. -I've got to go to a doctor.
പ്ഥീമട। ടി മാടി. ടൃ ാലിധ്ധ്വാട ഠ്ഠ1൯00.
I get these sharp pains in my undercarriage.
ചീറി ടമ ടലല്ധ മട ടമിസ.
-Downloading the photo now. -Let me introduce you two.
ടലി ന്ധ ്പാല. -81ല ടമ്മ ലാലി മ്യിലാലഠര്‍്ധമ.
This here is Finn McSomethin’ or other.
ബബ സീടേടടധമവ.
He's a first-class VIP airport whatchamacallit.
019 ഘലലാല്നാ 1:11. 111:1:111:-18 11111
And, Finn, this here is my date.
മഥ 00൦, ബ്‌ ലന ടമ൭.
I never did get your name.
ട൭൮൭ ൭1 ടല്പാമമബ൭ നമണമ മധ്യം.
Yes, sorry. It's Shiftwell. Holley Shiftwell.
വര, നല്‌. ടച൭ ട്ബ്ധയലല്‍ി. റംല ടവ.
It's Shiftwell. Holley...
പണ ടവ്ഡലി. 1൦1൮...
Finally. Time to see who's behind all this.
ചസ്പബൂര. നീടടമ ധധിലന്മ രാം മിമി ടലാമ!॥॥ ടലസ്ധമ ബി.
What is this?
൧്വാമിവ്ലാല്ഠ്മ ബി?
That's one of the worst engines ever made.
1ധ മമ ലവ്‌ലി 09 ലാന ഡ്ധ്ധര്‍.
It's an old aluminum V8 with a Lucas electrical system and Whitworth bolts.
19 ലിന മ്ധസ്്ബ്ധന ശൃഥ9 വിബായാ! ടട(ണ ॥ധടേട റ്ബാം(ഗപ്ഡംബ.
Shoot, them Whitworth bolts is a pain, tell you what.
8ം1ഗ്വ്ഡംന നല നബവടമ്ബത്ഥ.
Them ain't metric, they ain't inches.
19 ലിന ടിടണ നലനിം മമ്ധ ന.
Yes, okay, but whose engine is this?
൭, ദ്വ, യവ ബ്‌ ബ്ന ടില്വാ?
It's kinda hard to tell from this picture, ain't it?
ട്ടാ ല്ല മ്ഡ ദ്മല്വാഠ്ദ റമ്പാല ബി, ത്ന?
-But you took it. -Holley.
“ദ്വ മഗ്യിവററ നാനവാ മ്പോാല ബി. 11016.
Right! Yes, of course.
ലിന, ടി ഗഡ.
A good agent gets what he can, then gets out before he's killed.
ല്യബതറാ ാലി്ല്വാമിത്ഥ മ്വാനാ ലനമസ്ധാധ ഠ്മബമ0ി ടലാല്ധന ലലാധ്ധി.
Agent? You mean, like, insurance agent? Like...
ല്ല? സീദിദ്ധാ മയം, ടല്ലാലി ല്ല നടധട? ടലാലന്‍...
Like a good neighbor, Mater is there!
ട്ലാലസ്‌ 507൭൧77൧ ൭൧9 ൧൭൧൦ 7ദ!ല ൨ 507
Wait! You mean secret agents! You guys is spies!
പി ദ്ധ്ധ! സീലദ്ധ മയം ല്ല ്വടില്‍ ഗ്യ ടലസ്ധദ ഉലിട॥റ
In how many makes and models did this type of engine appear?
ീഠഠില്‍ റ്ബ്വലമനാമ ഘല ദ്വാമ 0 നഘാഠധ്ഥേലിര്ഥ ബ്ബ?
It was standard in seven models over a 12-year period.
19 ലന ടമ ധധി്വഥനംഠ്ലേ [:11:1111:111:1::111:1-:10 111111
At least 35,000 cars were made with this engine.
ടല്ഡാററ-ഡമഥണ്ുമ 35,000 ൭൭ 1 111:1::111-1111111
-You're purty. -Yes, thank you.
ഡയ മ്േബി. ന, ലന ടി.
-And so nice. -Just pay attention.
-൧മ്ഥ ടററ്റമ്ധാലി “ധന്പാധിത്ഥ ലാലി.
This seems like a dead end.
1-111-11: 11:11 1111॥1:11:111 111
If there was something in the photo
ദ്രിദ്ധിലി ഠ്ദ ടലടധമധ ലിമ പാല ഡ
that could narrow this down, I'd be happier.
൭0൭ നടസ്ധഠ്ദ്വര്ലാലദേറിലന്മ, ടമ വാട റലമ്പാ മ.
You might not be happy, but I bet this feller is.
൧ഗ്യിം സ്ധററിന്ന ഖിഡുലമ്പാ, 'ല്വി ടയ ഠി ല്ബാഭ.
See how he's had most of his parts replaced?
1-111-11 11:11:111:1:-1114। 1ലാബമിരാല്മറിബാമ്ദബുമ?
And see all them boxes over there?
മഥ മമ്പാമിജ്ലധല്പ്ര്ലിി ടമ?
Them's all original parts. They ain't easy to come by.
1ധാലാ-ാമത്ഥാ ശി ടലി. 19 ടധിന്വ ധ്യ.
-Rare parts? -That's something we can track.
6 11:1:1:11111:111:1- 11111860 9ാഠ1ലവന്മ്്ലദ1റി.
Exactly.
ലാമ ടല്യി॥.
Well done, Mater. I would never have seen that.
ട്ൃയ്വാമട, ീമല.. ടമൃ൭ മിധ്ാലടമറ മാധ.
I know of a black-market parts dealer in Paris, a treacherous lowlife,
൧03 ടല0റ0 ലബ്ധി വാമ മമ്മ 0 ടമ ലില്വാ റി ദ്്ട, റി ലഡം,
but he's the only car in the world who can tell us whose engine this is.
'ല്വാി ഠി ടല യ്ഡ ട[ല്വാ ലാലി! ലബ്ബ.
What would you say to setting up an informal task force on this one?
ഗ്ധ്യധഠിമ്ി ടാഡ ാടടധിത്ഥ ലാട ധധിധഡലടിത്ഥ മി ബി.
Wait. What?
പ10ി ദ്ധ്ധ. വാമ?
You obviously have experience in the field.
പ്ലീമട ടല, മഴഡ്യിലാല്ലാലറുമിമണമ്ഥ ദ്മി്മ൩ാ1ര്‍്റ ബ്‌.
Yeah, I live right next to one.
൭, ടമ നാല ലാലടലാലിമ്മ്ഥ ടലടലററ്റ ടലാലി !ധ.
I don't know.
50൮൨൭൨.
l ain't exactly been much help to anybody recently.
൭൮൭ ദധാതി നല്പാഥബഡ ലാലലാ ബി.
You're helping me. Please, Mater.
൧ഗ്യിംണല്പാമബഡ ടമ൭. ഠി, റീല.
Well... Okay.
൨... ഠിയ.
But you know I'm just a tow truck, right?
1-111-11] 09 ടമ൮൭ ധേന നല൦ധന്ദോ
Right. And I'm just in the import-export business.
൫. ഉമ ടമ്മ ധേന ലലാ ദ്മി്മനലാലബിറ്റമമ സ്വാാന-ലദ്ധയാണ.
-Siddeley? -Yes, Finn?
-ട1ഠിഠ്ലിലു? അ, നന?
Paris. Tout de suite.
ഉദ്ധിട. 707 റല ടഥ്‌7൭.
Yeah, two of them sweets for me, too, Sid.
൭, ട1ഠ. ടമ്മ നല്ധനബ്ടമ.
l always wanted to be a spy.
ടയ നലനഥറ നാണ നലിധു9ഠി ലാലിട॥
Really? Me, too.
ല്ലി? ടൃതാധന ടമണമ.
-Afterburners, sir? -ls there any other way?
“ധമറ, നമിറ്ൃധനമിത്ാലമ്പാല്ദ്വഥബ്ഥറാ വ മഠ്ാ॥ബില്ന?
Once we're inside, stay close.
8112 0൭0 ടാസ്വാല്‌, നാണ ാലന൦ഠ൨.
Don't bother checking VIN numbers. They're all dodgy here.
121 ധടമ്വവാലിമ നംമ്പാം ഗി. ടലസ്ഡാബമ മലാല റ്ലാലമയേയി.
Got it.
8110൭൨.
Don't talk to anyone, don't look at anyone,
പ്ല ലദേമ്വാ മ്യ്ധ 01 ടടടിലാമ,
and absolutely, positively no idling. Are we clear?
ദ്യ ടടടലയി॥ ദ്ധഠ്ധിധനല്ല്ഖ. മന?
Yes. No idling. Yes, sir.
൮൭. മന ഡേ്ധിനസല്ല്ഡ. ന, ഡമഥ.
-Mater? -Yeah, Finn?
പില? അ, നന?
-We're not here to go shopping. -Shoppin'? What do you mean?
വ യി റിമ ധന്ധിം നലമ്പാല[-ാല്ദ? പ്രീല്പാലല്‍[-ാലല്‍? ധ്യാ ണമദ്ധഠ്‌ മഗ്യിര
Why would I...
1ല്വാമാധിദ ടയ നിം...
Dad-gum.
ലാമ.
-Part for sales, monsieur. -Monsieur, part for sale.
80 മി ധധി്വ്ധലി, വമ. “ഡല, മററ റിമ ധധിഥ്വഥമി.
They got everything here. No!
ടല്റമിമബ 39൭ റി ട്ബ്‌. നില
Look at them hoods! I could use a hood.
ലററ ബ്ബ ഡ്‌ ൭൮൭ സ്ഥറിസ്സാലിധിര്ഥ ബ്‌.
Sorry, fellers. l gotta go!
ഗല്‌, ടലസ്ധാ. ടദൃയതവാല്ധവാലി!
Do what?
8ധ2ല്വാമ?
Excuse me. What are you selling?
നാല്‌. ധ്യാ മഗ്ലല്ധലി?
Headlights, monsieur, headlights?
1്വാധ ധനം ഡാം, നലിലിലസ്വാധ ധന
-What in the... -Two for one.
്വാഠ1൭൨... ഉദ ഠി ലാ ടമഡ.
-I give you good price! -I'm good!
ടൃ ലാലി ഥാ ണലമ്ഥിറ 11:11:
-There you are. -There is some great bargains here.
ഡാധന മഗ്യിം ശ്ഠ്ലാബുതിധ്ധല്മലഥ നല്ലി ടബ്‌.
-Mater, get back! -Imbécile!
്ഥിമല, ടല്പാധസുി! -8ഠഠിഠവ!
Hey, wait for me!
ല്ല, ഡാ!
-Have you lost your mind? -But I thought...
ഡയറ മ? “ലവി ടമ നാ...
This chap needs a tow. Hook him up.
019 ലാല ഠിഡഥഴ്മ. ടാമ്പാധനാ ദേോേറിഡിലഘാമ്ദത.
Sure thing.
[1111
You rusty piece of junk! Get your dirty hook off me!
1യിധാധഡിവതറ ചിറവാധ്നല 1ലാദടി്ഥ ടമ!
Electroshock! Are you kidding me?
ട്ഖനാ920 ലടാനാഷ ള്‍ഡ്യിലാലാധമധിത്ന
This is her first field assignment. She didn't know you were my informant.
ബി ഡാമടാലാലലനബമ. ഥം മിമ്ഡ ൮09 മ്യിലാല്ബാലി നലിറ്ധനമ ടത.
-Informant? -A rookie, huh?
-ല്പാലി നലിറ്ധനാ 8ഖഠ്മിധാലബ, ൫7
I never liked new car smell.
൭൮൭ ൭1 ടധിരവാദ്ധ ലഘല്‍്രാമഡ.
Tomber was doing 20-to-life in a Moroccan impound
“ഠ്പാല ടല സ്വാ ഠി സീം ടല സ്്ബ്സ്ധണന 20 ്്ഥ
the first time I saved him, if l recall correctly.
ാഠ്ദ ൪ നമാ ടമ ടലി റിമ, ടല ടമു൭.
Speaking of recalls, you're getting up there in mileage, aren't you?
8ലിയ്വാ മറു ധ, നാഡ മഗ ദമ നലിന്സാബതിപാധിര്?
All right, we get it. You both know each other, you're both old.
81020, യമ "മ്മ. ഥസ്മ്ധലാലഠ്ധമ ടന നാട്ടി! ദേ ഠ്‌ ഡാ.
So, here you go, informant. Inform us.
പീഠ, ബി ഠി, ലാല്പബാലി നമിറ്ധണമ്‌. [1-111-11 1111
That is the worst motor ever made.
ധന 0൭109 ഒം 09 ലാന ഡ്ധ്ധര്‍.
Wait. That oil filter. Those wheel bearings.
ധാ. ലല്ധടടെ ബ്ബ. ൫ഠഠ3ാലാറ്റാലിടെ ഡ.
Do those parts look familiar, Tomber?
“ഠമ്പാല, മഗ്ല്ല്ാലനമറ ്പാമി ലമി ധാ?
They should. I sold them.
ടറി ലാടട. ടമ ൮൭൧൫9 നലബ്ധമ്സത.
-To whom? -No idea.
-1%ല്ലാദഠിദ ട1ല്വാമ? ടമ യി്ല്ഡ.
He's my best customer, but he always does his business over the phone.
൧19 ലററ ഹാലി ടമ, ഖി ബി ാലധഡട ബിമാ നലലിധി ലില്൦ന.
I was always wondering why he needs so many parts.
ടൃ ടലല്ധ നമ ബമ 1ലല്വാദ ഠി ാലിധിത്ബാബതി ലു.
Now I know.
ട്ലിദ്ധമനാ ടമ റല ്ധ്ഡ ടലാലാന൭.
A lemon needs parts. Ain't nothin’ truer than that.
ലല ലോധിധനനലിധിത്ുത. ടറി ലഡഡ ടലാഖ്ധാസത.
-Lemon? -Yeah. Cars that don't ever work right.
ലാധിന ൭. ലലാ മ്വോധ്ധ്ം
Lemons is a tow truck's bread and butter.
ലല ലോധിറ്മ്വാധനടോലഠ്ലാമമ 'ലിഡധഥദ്ദ.
Like 'em Gremlins and Pacers we run into at the party
ടലാലി ലേസി റ്റ 0ലേ ൭0 സ്ദ്ധ്വാദ റ 0൭0൯,
and the race and the airport.
01 ാലിധമ്പാമമ്ഥ ദമ ഠി ലാനാ ണയ.
Pull up the pictures from the oil platform.
“മൃതി മ്പ ഠി ലല സ്ബയിഡ.
I want to know what other type of cars were out there.
111: 11-11-11: 09 309 ഠി ടി.
Right. Let's see. There were Hugos and Trunkovs.
810൭൨. നീലി ന്മ 119. ൧03 ധം ഠി സബിരഴ.
Are these cars considered lemons?
൧051 നലലവ്പധ9ദ ഠിന്അു ലോധി
Is the Popemobile Catholic?
൧0211 ലാനാ ടല ॥ദ
Everyone involved in this plot is one of history's biggest loser cars.
ടലസ്ഡാററ ബ്പാമദ്ദ്മന ബ്‌ ഒഠ്മദ൨1ലഘമഷഘല ലിഗ.
And they're all taking their orders from the car behind this engine.
ഉമ ണലലയ നല്‌ മല 1ലല്മമനാ നലാദ്ഥ്ലിത്ഥ ല്വ്൩ യ.
-This explains it. -What, Tomber?
-ദഡരിലി. ഗ്വാ, 7ഠമ്പാല?
Gremlin, Pacer, Hugo and Trunkov never get together,
ലെസ്‌, ലേ, ധം ദക ബിര ലധ്ാനണമി ടലഷ്വാമിമ,
but they are having a secret meeting in two days.
'ല്വാ ഠ്മ്മണ ണടടദ ദ്ധ ലി, നലല മിഥ മറി നടടുധമത്ച്ടിമ.
-Where's this meeting taking place? -Porto Corsa, Italy.
21 നമ? ൧00൦൦0 ഠ൦ടാ, ൭.
That's where the next race is!
ഉലിധമ്പാമമ്റ ട്ട ാലിനാടഥനാഠിട്ധ
There's a good chance our mystery engine will be there, too.
൧03 ലസ്ധനിന്നമ്ഥ ഒബ്ന സബിടലി ന്മ മ്രബാലമ്ദ ഠി ട്‌.
Your chances are more than good.
1ലസ്ഥിനനമസത പാടല.
I just sent him a new clutch assembly yesterday. To Porto Corsa.
ടയ ൭0൩ ടിട്ണ ലേമനസതഥറ സ 1ല്ാഠ്മബ൭ ടമ. ൭ 0൦൦ ൦൦5.
Contact Stevenson and have him meet us at Gare de Lyon.
്ധാധനാ! ടഖ്യലടംറ മടി ഠിദ ാല്ധ്വാ ര്‍്ലറമബിന്മ റി ചേ ൦ ൮൧0.
Good work.
ട്രൃത്വാമട.
That three-wheeled feller had to be right about a big meetin’.
ദലഡി ദേിശ്വാ ലല ാലഠാഠ്ദ റിമ ഡ.
You never see this many lemons in one town.
ല്ധ്ാലനമ മഠ ഘലമ ദ്വോധ ടലാബമിബി ലി്മണ ടമഡലാലല്‍ത്ഥ.
‘Less there's a swap meet.
സില്ല്ബ്ര്ഥ മഠ്ഠ മസ്ധ ഡി.
How'd you get all them pictures?
വനന മഗമി്ല്ാിത്ഥ ടലസ്ധഃ റൃ്വാല ഡാ?
l reprogrammed Porto Corsa’'s red light cameras to do recognition scans.
൭൮൭ 0ഠറമന വണലല ഠി ംനം ൦൦ടദ ട്രാ 13 10ധമ്പാദടടമ ാലമേണമ.
Wow. Not only is you the purtiest car lever met, but you're the smartest, too.
7ഠഡ. ൧ഗ്ലിധാധിത്ഥ ടമ മ്ഡിം, 'ല്വാ്ധാമ നവ.
Thank you... I think.
“ലിന 1൭51... ൧9൭1൩൬൫൭.
That's a familiar sight. A Hugo bein’ towed.
1ധാ1ട ടമ 1൩൭1. ലല റ്ധാം വനാ ഡയ.
But he looks absolutely perfect!
ലാ റിദ ന്പാ ടല്പാധനല!
Of course! They must be the heads of the lemon families.
ടറി ധ്‌ സിലലര ധാ ല്ധലാാ ൭൭ ല്പോധിം
Makes sense. If l was rich and broke down every day,
1ധ നാടധിം ലവി. പിര ടമ ൭ ദ്ദ ഠടഠ1 ടലില്വാ ലി,
I'd hire me to tow me around all the time, too!
ടി ടയ ധാമ റിനി ടലഠ്റല ധധിഡധനഠ്ട ടയ ടലാദബ്ുമനാനമടടല!
We've got to infiltrate that meeting to find out who's behind all this.
1പ്മ്വാല്ധ നസബല്യി നടടുധമത്ലയ ധധി൦ണലല്ി ടില്വാഭ്ധമബത.
Hang on a minute. Hold still.
പി ഠ്ധ്ധ. ടാ.
Good job, Miss Shiftwell.
ടൃയ്വാമട, 1 ടവ.
Thank you, Finn.
ലിനാ 1൭511, 60൩൩.
Boy, I sure wish my friends could see me now.
ദ്രിദ്ധില്ിരധമനരഥ്ങ ടമ 0201ല്‍ ബ്പാടി ടമ്മ ടല്ഷ്ഥ.
Guido, your eyes do not deceive you.
ധോം, മാ ൮3900 മഗ്മില്പാമം ധി ടമ ലമ.
We are in Italy. We are home.
1വമ്വാലാഠ്ദ ഠി ൭. ൧ ൭൧൭൩ ലലാന്ധ.
Hey, Luigi. Which way to the hotel, man?
ല്‍, ധി. നീനാ മിലി?
What? No friend of mine will stay in a hotel in-a my village.
ഉ ബ്വാധനാ ടമ്മ, മഡാഥിയധമ ടമയമ 'മിധാംല 109 0൨൦൧ല്‍.
You will stay with my... Uncle Topolino!
ഗ്യ ല്ത്ഥ 1099ല്‍ ാലടേണമ... ൧3 ൧॥ പാം!
Luigi! Guido!
ധി! ധോം!
How do they do it?
ദാഠല്നാനാ നലല നല്മിധിര്ബമ?
These are the same ingredients as back home, but it tastes so good.
ഒച്റാദല്മബയമ ടമ ടലാലി ഠി ല്പാാന്ന, ദ്വി ടമ ടലഠില്വാ.
-It's organic, man. -Treehugger.
“19 ബിമ, മമ. ലന മിമന.
Hey, race car.
ലി, ലര ധമ്പാമ.
You look so down, so low.
൧ഗ്യിം സ്വാമി മനമ ടലി.
Is like you have flat tires.
5ല01210-01൩ ത്വ മഴ്യിലാമ.
She said you look like you are starving,
൧19 ൭൧൭ മഗ്യിഠമ്വാല്ലിഘാധിധഥമ്ല,
that she's gonna make you a big meal and fatten you up.
ഠി ന ടലിലിത്ഥ ണമി ട്രാ മഗ നലിത്ഥ ടല്വാലി ല്ധിം.
No.
ലി്ധ്വാല്ധ.
Mama Topolino, please, you don't need to make a fuss.
സീന 7൦001൦, 101൦001൭, 'ലിധ്ാല്ധ ടധടമ-ടധടി.
Capisco. I understand.
810൭൨. ടമൃര൭ ല്മണ.
Is a problem, yes, between you and a friend?
൧03 നട യമ മഗ [11-15-11
How did you know that?
ദാഠലനാനാ ലെ ലിഡ്‌?
A wise car hears one word and understands two.
ലല ല്ധാംലണല്ുന്നിമ്വാ നമിദധ വനാ ലടിനമ്‌.
That, and Luigi told me.
1ഠറ്റ്വാധ൩, ധ19! ്മ്പാലിമ്ഡ ടമ.
While Mama cooks, come and take a stroll with me.
ടലണലമ ശീമ ടല നാടല്ം നമി !ന്യ്വാലല്ബ്ലിമ.
I brought my friend Mater along on the trip
ടമാ ര്ഥ്ങ ടമ്യതം സീമല,ലാലടാണമ
and I told him he needed to act different,
ദമ ടമ ടധി ഠി നായ്സില്വം,
that we weren't in Radiator Springs.
ദമ ലാധിത്ലാലമഠ്മ ഠി ഠി ട്രാന്നാട.
This Mater is a close friend?
നീല ഡ മലര്ന്ന
He's my best friend.
1 മിഥ ടമാ മിനാ ലിന്്വ.
Then why would you ask him to be someone else?
പിഒഠി। ദധല്വാമ ഗമി ടി ദിലാല്ധ്ത്പാധ്മ?
What did I do?
൧൮09 ടമു൭ ്പ്വാധറ
I said some things during our fight.
ടലണമടദ ബ്ബ്ധാലമഠ്ധ, ടമ ലിലാമട ദേവാ.
You know, back when Guido and Luigi used to work for me,
ടലണമടമ ധോം ൭0119 ല്ല ഠ്ലറ്മ്ന ടയ,
they would fight over everything.
നലല ടലി്നാ ലാലല.
They fight over what Ferrari was the best Ferrari,
ദിലല്യാല്ലഠിന് മറ ല്ലി നാമ നാലി
which one of them looked more like a Ferrari.
ഥാ നമ ടമഡ ലാ നലബ്ുലഡാമി ലമി.
There were even some non-Ferrari fights.
1-1: 111-1:1:1111:1:1: 1 1:]181 ൭09 ഖിനലലാമത്ഥ ലന.
So I tell them, "Va bene, it's okay to fight.
പഠി ടയ 1൨൪൭. 11:11) 11:1:181111
“Everybody fights now and then, especially best friends.
"ടല്യി-ടലല്‍വിമ, റമ ടലസ്ധാാലലറിത്, ലധ്മണമബ ബിത്ലത്ലി.
“But you got to make up fast.
"ച്ചാ ന്മ വാല്ധാലനമി ടലസ്ഡിമ ഠാ ടലുലമ.
“No fight more important than friendship.”
പ്ലലടദ്ലാമ്മിലാവാലനാ ദ്മല്വാഠ്ദ ലാലി.”
-What does that mean? -Whoever find a friend, find a treasure.
്വാഠല്ബത? “രഗ ലിലബില വയ.
Now, mangia. Eat!
ട്ല്വ്ഥമാ. ഗീമടാ ധധി൦നല്തല്‍്‌
Finn, one hour to Porto Corsa.
00, ടല്മണ 19൭1 7൭ ട്വ ഠം ൦652.
Thank you, Stevenson.
ലിനാ 1൭511, ടട.
-That should just about do it. -Perfect.
ഠ്യ ഖ. -ടലടധമി ടലര॥.
So, Mater, it's voice-activated.
സീമ, 9 റിലിന്നിന്ഥ ൦1ല൨ ടഥമ.
But everything's voice-activated these days.
ചാ ടലസ്ധമലാലറ്ദലാധാല്ഡ ാഠ്ദ മമനാഥ ടല്വഷ്ഥ.
What? I thought you was supposed to be makin’ me a disguise.
ടൃ നാമിത്ഥ മഴയില ടടഠിലിത്ഥ ടന ധിം ടമ.
Voice recognized. Disguise program initiated.
കഗദഗദ ൯ഘദ്്‌. ൧൧0൮77 ടദണുക7ഥ വ്നഥ്ദ്൭൧.
Cool!
ലാമി
Computer, make me a German truck.
14ഠമ്പാധ്ല, ഡിദ്വ ടര നല്ഖമഠി। അആപ്ലന്നമ.
-Request acknowledged. -Check it out! I'm wearing Materhosen.
ഛഗദ്ധകഗ വലു. 10 ടൃ ലാമില്‍ നീല ംടല.
Make me a monster truck!
1 ധിവ്വ ടമ നല്പമഠി। ബചിറാലാമട॥!
-Request acknowledged. -What the...
ഛഗദ്ധകഗ വലു. ്വാഠ1൭൨...
I vant to siphon your gas!
ടൃ മി ടലഠ്ധ ബ്ബ മധ്യ
-Now make me a taco truck! -Request acknowledged.
“്ധിശ്വ ടമ്മ നലബ്മഠി। ഗമോ! ഛഗദ്ധകഗ വലു.
-A funny car!
ലല ൮൭0൮ ദിലി!
The idea is to keep a low profile, Mater.
നില, നിന മില ടധ്യാമുഒ മഗ യിംണലംബം!.
So I just go in, pretend to be this truck.
പിറ ടാലി! ദ്ദമാല്ലാധ്ത്പ്ാധമ നലബ്ദഠി ല്ല്ബ്‌.
-And leave the rest to us. -Now, hold still.
ട്ടാ ൭൩, ല്ല ിയി്‌ ല്ത്ഥ ധബടിത്ഥ. പ്ഥറാബാലാലയിം.
I have to do the final fitting on your disguise.
ടൃ ലാലിധാമഠ്ദബ്ത്ഥ ടമ്മ മധ്യ ധറവധിലയി। ലയിമ്പ.
That's no good.
ബി ല്ധാട.
Hey. What are you doin’?
റല. ഗ്വാ മഗ്യിധാധമറ
The disguise won't calibrate effectively without a smooth surface to graft onto.
1പ്മാലിധിത്സ്ാലസ്ധിരമ ൭൭ ധധി൦ണല്വേയമ്ിത്ഥ ടന മധ്യം
For a second there, I thought you was tryin’ to fix my dents.
ട൮ൃ൭ നമിത്ഥ മയിഠലി്ലാലാലിര ലമി ലാറ ട൮൭.
-Yes, I was. -Then, no, thank you.
ട്‌, നനാ ധന. രാധ, പവാമയത്വിമ.
I don't get them dents buffed, pulled, filled or painted by nobody.
ട൭൮൭ മനല്ഡ ടടടിലാ ദം ദ്ധി 1ട1 മ്യ്ധ മേധഘമ്പി ടമ.
-They way too valuable. -Your dents are valuable? Really?
“19 ലിദ്ധ ടന. 1(ലബി॥ മഗ്യില്ടണണ്മെ?
I come by each one of 'em with my best friend, Lightning McQueen.
൭൮൭ നല്ലാ ടണടടാലടാണമ ിദ്൩രഥി ടമ, 1ബ്ണ സീദ്വധേലം൨.
I don't fix these. l wanna remember these dents forever.
ടമൃ൭ മല്ല റ്ലാലാലിദ. ടമ്മ നമ നല ടദമ്പാലി 0112-01.
So, you were being serious in Paris? McQueen isn't just part of your cover.
പ്മഠ॥, മഡ്മ।€ ടല്ധട ടലനമടമ റി മ്ല്ട? ീഗ്ധേംബാധിത്ഥ ടല ധ്ധി ടന.
Friendships can be dangerous in our line of work, Mater.
ഉലടദ്ിലാമ്മബാഠില്‍ണലമ്പാല്മയതി്ത്ല ദ്മിമ൩ാ1ര്‍്മറ ാലലിാബിനന, മല.
But my line of work is towin' and salvage.
ചാ ഠാ ടമ 1൭1൭൫ നലസ്ധഠ്േ ദ്ദ നബ്ുല്മണമ[.
Right. And Miss Shiftwell's is designing iPhone apps.
വ്വ ഡ. ബാ ലിം ടബ്ധലല്‍ി॥ 151൫ലെ മ്വാ॥രട। ലം.
-No, I meant for real. -It's okay. I'll work around the dent.
121 ടമ ടലിധട ബി. 1210 ്വാമ. ടമ്മ ലീദിറമലിഘലബിമമ്ലിം.
In the meantime,
ടലനലമമ[ഖ,
you look a little light on weapons.
ഒഗമിലിശി്വഥമ ടലവ്മ്മ.
You are looking live at beautiful
ദ ൧ല൦ട'ക൦ഒഥ ടല !ദഗറടഥഥററ റ്ക്ഥ്‌
Porto Corsa, Italy, on the Italian Riviera.
൧070 ൦075൭, !79, വ്‌ ഡല !?ഒ.
What a magnificent setting for the second race of the World Grand Prix!
ക ഥദടദഗട ഒറ 0൭൧0 ഗല ൧ലഥസാഥദദഥ ഗറ്ഥ ൭൦ ൧ഥഥഗഥ്ല്‌ക
Brent, they call this place the "Gem of the Riviera,"
27ലാ%, 7ലസ്വാദ സ്‌ റ്ഥാക്ഥറ്‌്‌ ഫലണാദദ ഷ്ഡ്ലമ,
and it's easy to see why.
റ്ദഗല്ദട ടല്ഷ7്‌ £ഥക്വാദ !ദ വ്റ്ല്ക7 ൧൦70.
With its secluded beaches and opulent casinos,
൧ഹറ്റദഗ ൧൭൧൭൩൮)9 ൬9൭9 ലാലല റ്ദഥ [൭5൧ഠ0-4950ഠ ഗാലഒ൨,
Porto Corsa truly is a playground for the wealthy.
൧0൧7ഠ ൦07ടദ ദറ്൭7൭7 ?്വാദ% ൧൭73 ഥദധഒഥ ൧2ലടഥ്ര 7.
And everyone who's anyone is here today,
൧ക്ഗ ടലഹാഥദ ഘാഠ്ലദദ )ഒഥറ 7ല്ഘക ൧ലദറ്ദ വ്‌ 5 ധാദ്ഥ്‌ വ,
from the ultra-rich and super-famous
റ്ദഗ്ഥാദറ്ദ ഗ)ലലല്‍്ദ )ഒഥറ ഗദ്യ റ്ദഗ 7ല്‌ഘാക്‌
to world leaders and important dignitaries.
7700937ദ ൧൭൩7770-0ല7077 റ്ഥദ റ്ദഗ 7ഘലലദ-ഘലല്ദ :ഘക്ഗദദഥ.
You aren't kidding, David.
ഥ്ല്ഥ്‌ ദേദഷ്വാ ദക ഗദ.
You can't do a three-point turn without bumping into some celebrity.
൦ ഗുദ്ഗദ ടക4ദ ഥല്‌, ദല ലട ലലാ റ്ഹറ്റദഗ ദസ്‌ട 7ല്‌ഘാദ!.
Welcome, everyone, to the second race of the World Grand Prix,
ടല മാ ലാല്ധമ്പാമമ രഠ്ധമ മേഥഗര്‍്‌ ലാഗഥധബ്മ,
where the big news continues to be allinol.
ഠി നാന ഡമ്പാധമ്ബര ൩൭51൨309 211൩൦1.
Sir Miles Axlerod spoke to the press earlier today
ഉലിമണ ടിര്‍്മറ മിന്പാല മധമി ലി ബി, ടട നീ॥ിടട ഷഠിലഠഠ്‌
to answer questions about its safety.
നല്പമധ്യി ടഠദിദ0-ടഠമിദറ ാലിശമമബടധ ടല.
An independent panel of scientists has determined
ടല്ഡമ്പാധിമ ലാല്‍ ടദ്നടിട ാലാടട ലി നലസ്ധഡടിത്ഥ
that allinol is completely safe, okay?
ാല്മഥ 210൦ ടലിണമ, ര്യ?
Safe. There it is.
ടല ലാട ലേ.
So the race will go on, folks.
പഠി ലാലിധമ്പാമമ മിവ 01ലഡടിത്.
But the question everyone is asking:
ചവ ടമഡലാലടംലിമ്ഥ ൭0൭ നട ്ബാധി മമ,
will the real Lightning McQueen show up today?
ഒറ്ദഷ൧ 2൨0൧00 0൦േഥല ടഘഫഹക്ഗ ഒഥ ഥേ ഗദ്ഥ്‌ ഗ്‌?
He'd better. Talk about a home track advantage.
2 ൧ ൧൭% ന്ദ ഗാഥഗേ. £ലദ്വദ്വ ലാ!ഒഥറ 7ഘല്‌ലാഥകഗ ധ്‌ “ദഗദ്ഗ ഒ൧7.
Francesco Bernoulli grew up racing on this course.
൧ഥ൦ടടഠാ £ലനാഗഥ്ഥ്‌ ഗനസാമടടക്ധ ൨ 77൦.
Signore e signori, in the pole position, Numero Uno, Francesco!
7ഥദഥ-4ലഥ റ്ദ്ഗ ൧ഥഗദഗ്ാലമഥ, ൨ ?ലനാാദ! ലക്ക, ൧7ദ്ഗ൦േടഠോ?
Bellissima! Thank you for your support!
വട! ലിന 1൭ട॥ മട ടം മ്മ!
And your big mistake, McQueen!
ഉമ ശടില്വാദറ മഗ്യിം സീദ്വേലല്‍്‌
In secondo position,
൧ ?ല്വാദ! റ്ലം,
numero 95, Lightning-a McQueen-a!
770720൧07 95, 17007070 17൦ഠേലഹ!്‌
McQueen-a, is-a everything okay?
ീഗ്ധേടല, ടസ്ധമസമ ഠ്വ?
If you're worried about your fuel, man, don't. It's perfectly safe.
പ്ല ല്ടധ മറ ലാല ലാ ഡ. 9 ടല.
No, guys, I just really wish Mater were here.
11:11: 181118) ീട്ല മി ഠി ട്ബി.
Francesco understands, McQueen.
മഥ൦േടഠോ 12൭, ീദ്ധേല.
Great, here it comes.
ടി വ, ഠി ൭൨ ണ്ധിലില ഡ.
What do you got, Francesco?
൧്വാ3 മഡ്യി ല്ലം, “അഥടേടഠോ?
For famous race cars like Francesco and, well, you,
ദാഠ॥। ഖലമധമ്പാ ലില്ലി ടല്ലാലി മ്മി ലത്ഥടേടഠ,
to be far away from home is not easy.
ലമി ദ്ദ മല ലല ലന മണ നലല്വോദ്വ.
I think you forgot the insulting part of that insult.
൧ഗ്യിറലിധാദ നല്ധണല്്നമ ട൮൭.
Is-a no insult.
1:11 11:111-11:11111:1
When-a Francesco is away from home, he misses his mama,
8112 മേട ഥി ഠി ബന ഠിദനലര്‍്ധി ലാധബതം
just like-a you miss your tow truck amico.
ടല്ലാലി മഗ്മി൦ണലന്നഠ്ധി 1-111-11:
Gee, I maybe misjudged you, because that's exactly...
ടൃ സ്ഥറിന്ന ലടില്പാ നല്ലില ധം ടലാലാ [ധ ണനലനഥ൭...
Of course, l am at home, and my mama is right here.
ച്വാി ടമ ാലടറ്ദ ഠി ഥമ ലല, ദ്ദ ലാധ ടദയതാലമ്ദ റി ട്‌.
Mama!
1: 1111:1
Don't worry, Mama, McQueen is very sad.
പാമ ലട, നീന, സീഗ്ധേടദ ടമ0ററമ ടറി.
I will beat his cry-baby bottom today!
൭൮൭ ലിര്ഥ യിമ്വപത്ഥ ഠി മ ബി!
And there's the insult we were missing.
ഉാബധിദ്വാലാബ്നമമ് 09 ടമ൮൭ മലനട ഠി.
Darrell, the racers are settling in as they head
൧കഥല, ൧ാദ7ദ ൧ാല്ഥാഥദ മാദ്ധഗ ടല്‌൦ടദ ട൭൧൧7 ഗുലഗഥ്ല
to the Italian countryside.
൧൭ ദ൭ടദഥദ ൧ ൦റ്ദ'ദഥാദഗ 77ഒ.
Boy!
ടലഠഗഠഗൃഒ
This is going to be a great race.
൧൧ ൧235 നലദന്‌ ടദ!ഥവാല്്‌ഗ്സാഥദദ്ധദ ഒ നലദഥ്‌ം
Gremlins. Man, those are some ugly cars.
ലെസ്‌. ദധി നലല.
Look like someone stole their trunks.
പ1സ്വാമിസമാധ നലല ൭൩ ഗോ.
My grand-a father has-a broken down.
ഉഡി ടമ്മ ടമ
If-a one of-a you would help, I would be so thankful.
൭൮൭ നമധാല്ല്നട 1൨൭51൨ [11൭ ഠാ ടലി നലമ്പാമവ.
Sounds like you need some roadside assistance.
പ1സ്വാമിസമ മഗ്ല്ലാലി്ധിത്ഥ ബഡാ ലര.
-She was talking to me. -Really? Prove it.
-൧1ലാലലേശ്വാ ലന ടമ൭. -ഒലധി? 8ധിവിയ്ത.
Don't-a fight over me.
പ്ഹബാലാഠ്വത്ന ടമ൭.
Signore Tow Truck, per favore.
0ലിഗന്ലിം സ്ഥ, ഠ1ംബ്റില.
Get ready, Mater. You're on any moment now.
8ലടലറിമ, [മല ീടടമ ധധിവാല്നചലേ ല്വാ യാമ.
I don't know about this. What if l screw things up?
൭൮൭ ൭1൦ ടലഠ്ല്വാ 0൭. ദാനാ ॥ര ടമ ാധമ ടില്വാ?
Impossible.
7ഒ സഥലം.
Just apply the same level of dedication
൧8ലഡ൧ റ്൭൪൯൯൭5 )9൭റ ടദനദ
you've been using to play the idiot tow truck, and you'll be fine.
ടലാലസ്‌ ൧ ലഥലഡ്ഷ്ഥ ഗല്‌ ൧൭7൭൭൧ ടലാദറദ 773൭൧ ൧000൧.
It's just that them guys look purty tough and... Wait, did you say "idiot"?
ലാ നലല ല്പാമി ലറുദ്വാ ഠ്‌... ൧ഡഗ്യിലത ടമ "ഠിം?
-ls that how you see me? -That's how everyone sees you.
ശ്ഡ്യിനമമ്വാമിടമയരാല്യ? -5ലാഥദ 7൦ല്ദ ഗ7ദ70൭% ഷം.
isn't that the idea?
൧്ഥഷഷ൧ഗ 77 സദ! ദല
1 tell you, that's the genius of it.
9 ടദ£ഥ 7റ്ല 9൭൧ ഗദ ൧7൭.
No one realizes they're being fooled
79% ദറ്ദ ട൦ട൮ക്യാദ ടലറ്ദ് 39൧0 നലല വ്ഥലഥഠറ്ഠഥഗദഷഥ
because they're too busy laughing at the fool.
ടലാക്ഥ ഗലല്ദ ?ലല്‌ക൧ 52൧ഥ ഗാലറ്റല്ദകഷഥ ദ
-Why aren't you in disguise? -l...
ദ്വ മയി ല്ഗനബ്തണമന? ൭൭൮൭...
-Come on! There's no time! Go! -Okay. Okay.
കൃധ! മ ടധന്ധിത്ഥ നടല്‍! ലെ! ദ്യ. ഠിയു.
-Computer, disguise! -Request acknowledged.
1ഠ്പാധ്ല, നബ ഛഗദ്ധകഗ വലു.
It's the boss. He's coming.
1ധധ്യാധ൩ാഠട 10൭. ൧19 ൭൨ ടാസ്വാല്‌.
Ivan.
2:11
Ivan, why do you insult me so by making me wait here?
ഗമ, ല്വാദ ധാ ടമ ഡ്ഥേഠ്ട്ബ?
He's in.
൧ ദ്മ്വാല്ദ്യമ നടധിം
The racers are now making their way around the hairpin
൧73 ാലഥാഥദ ടലറ്കഥററ്‌ ഗുല്ക[ഥധ്‌ ടല്ല്ഥഗ ?ദദഗ
and headed downhill toward the casino bridge.
റ്ദഗ ഗുഹഥഥ! ൧ഥശ്‌ ൧൪ ൧൦൭൧ 3൧31൧ 4൭5൮0൦.
No more bets, please.
1:11. 11111111:
Come on, fuzzy dice!
എഡി, ദേഠ്ധ റലാധ!
-Number four. Easy four. -Yeah!
പ്ഠമ്പാം ലമ്പാമ സ്വ. ട്‌ി
Air freshener. Antenna balls.
ലഘു ധഠ്9. 8ലാം1൭ 2൩൭൫൭.
Spark-a plugs.
ഉടന ലാലധേധേ.
This place looks like it's made outta gold!
"ലമ്പാമ [ബി നല്പാല മന നല്മ്വ്‌
That's because it is. Now, be careful what you say.
7ലാദഥറ “ദ ഗല൭൧. ൧്ദ77-0ദഥ്‌ 2൧74ദ ൧ല൦കെ൮൭൧.
Why is that?
1ലദ്വാാധിദ?
What do you mean, "Don't talk to ya"?
൧൮3 നഠദ്ധഠ്‌ മഗ്ഘം, "ചിറ്റ ദേശ്വാ ഠാ മഡ്ല്റ്‌
You want me to stop talkin’ to ya right now?
൧ഗ്യിംലിം ടമ ലാലല ാലലിയ്വാ ലാ ഗ്ല
You are acting strange today, Ivan.
ല॥ധാലധി ലാ മധ്മിനലി ബ്‌,
I have no idea what you're talking about,
ടൃ മിമ്ഡ ഖാ മയി നമിദ്ധഠിര്ഥ,
“Alexander Hugo, aka Chop Shop Alex."
ഫിലദ്ഥി്ല ധാം, ഠ॥1॥ ടലാഠറ്റമ! വം ടം ബില.”
You got a lot of aka's, Alex.
ഗ്യ ഠ്യ ടമ, വില.
But that makes sense, seein's how you's wanted in France, Germany...
ചാ ംഠ॥ധ്ധാഠ, നന്ദി മയി ഷാലി ഠി ന്റലട, ദല്നമല...
Mater, stop it!
സീമ, ടമ്മ ഡയ!
Okay, okay, keep your voice down!
ധി, ഠരലാലില്മബ്ത്ഥ ടയ ഗമി
You gonna make me arrested!
111 1-:1::1:1:111[]::111-111
Don't mess with Ivan today. He's in a bad mood.
പ്ല ലവി 9േഠ്ധ ലോബി ലി ബ്‌. ൧ ഡാ ലിം.
He's so good!
19 ഉമറലി ാലില്രബ്‌
Victor!
ഡോഗ്‌
Hey, Victor!
ലി, ഗ്‌
Victor Hugo, I'm J Curby Gremlin. From Detroit.
ഡോ ല്ധാം, ടമ ൭ ൮ ലേസി. ഉഥ്‌ ലം.
It's good to see you.
൭൮൭ റലമ്പാന്മലാല്ധമ്പാമ മഗ്ലിം.
Is the big boss here yet?
8ഠട ലാടടദ് ദ ടാബ്വാലി?
-No, not yet. -He's supposed to be here any minute.
-8ഒല്ധന 91. -212 ലിദ്ഥ ടബ്വാദി മാദ നട ട്വ.
Here we go.
൧൭ ൭0 ടമമ്പാമി.
Guten Tag.
ടല്കഗാദ! ടല്ക7?ലമ.
It's just the professor.
1ധ ധേന 0001ടടം..
Ziundapp! When is he coming?
൧00ഠ്ലാ! 3॥ലിയീ ഠി മിദ്ഥ ടമ്വാലി?
He's already here.
൧൭ ൭0 ടമമ്പാമി.
Welcome, everyone.
ടല്കഗാദ! റ്ദ!ദ0റ. ടലാലമ.
1 wish I could be with you on this very special day,
കുട 2ലിക7ാ റ്ദ്ധദ!൧ലടകദ ൭൭% ൧ദറ്ദ ദല ൭൧ 7ടഥ്നാലട ഥ്‌,
but my clutch assembly broke.
4ദ്യ7 ട!51ല ല്ദ്ഗ ടദ൮ഒ 705൭.
-You know how it is. -Forget about it.
-൧ദദഗ-7കഗക്ഗ ടക4ദ. 1 ॥1:11:111:1--11:111
We know how you feel.
ബി "മസലാലമടമഥ ഡല.
-Descramble that voice. -I'm trying.
പ്രൃയ്വ്രദിയ ടമ. ടമ ടലി ധോ.
It's too sophisticated.
19 ലില്ധ മേ0991൩.
We are here to celebrate.
ദ റ്ദ7ദറ ഗഗ4ധ സനലറ്ദറ്കഷഥ ടദഗാഥഥ്കഗ.
Today, all your hard work pays off.
ഫ്ദഥ്‌ 77, ടഠ്റകദ ലാ! [ല്ദ്ഗ 7൭% ഒ൭൧ ൧൧൭57.
The world turned their backs on cars like us.
ഗഥദ ?ല്‌ക7 ഗ)ുല്ഥദഷഥ ഗഘഘല്‌ദ ടലാലസ്‌ 4ഗ്‌.
They stopped manufacturing us, stopped making our parts.
ലല ൧ലലാഥ്‌ ഗാലാറ്ല്ലദഥ്കഗ റ്‌, റ്ദഗ ൧൭൧൭0 0൭൧0൧ 7ഗ൭.
The only thing they haven't stopped doing is laughing at us.
7 ദ് ഗാലല്ദ 7൭4ഗലാഥ്ലാഥ്‌ ഗാലറ്ല്ദകഷഥ വദ.
They've called us terrible names: jalopy, rust bucket, heap,
ലല ൧ലല്‌ !ഗ്ദ റ്ല്ക7ഗ)ഒഥറ ലല ൧൭൭൮ ൧൧൧ ൧൭൯൩ ൧7൭),
clunker, junker, beater, wreck, rattletrap,
ലഭ 7ദ്ധ7൭%. ലട, 'ദ്ാഥ൦ ൧ദ്ഗവയ, ലഗാ,
lemon.
ക്ോോധ്‌ം
But their insults just give us strength.
7 ദ 7ഘ(ദ്ഗ ഗലലദ ഗാലാറ്റഥഥ്ഷഥ സദ.
Because today, my friends, that all ends!
£(ലദഗദ ഗദഥ്‌ ൨, 7്൭ഥ-7ലദഥവ, ടലാലദ 77 ദ്ദ്ഥ ഥലദ്ധശ്വ്‌
There's smoke on the casino bridge!
ഛീടദ്യ വ്‌ദ7൧32൧ 43507
Oh, no!
൨, വിറ്ലിറ്‌
It's Carla Veloso, the Brazilian race car!
1ധ ലി ഗലിംടം,ലാല്ധമ്പാമ ദ്ദ0ി ഒല!
-What just happened? -I'm working on it.
ഗ്വാ ൮00 ലാലിലിവ? ടൃ ടമാ നസ്യ.
They laughed at us, but now it's our turn to laugh back.
ഗുല്ല, നലല്ദ !ഘദധഘഷഥ (ഗ്, ശ്വ “ശ്ദവോാധ്ദ ഗാലാറ്ലദധലക്ഥ ഗലല്വ.
Another crash! it's number 9, Nigel Gearsley.
ദല ദവ “ഥാദ'ദഗറ്ദഥ7 7707൧ഠ7 9, 777ല! ൭൦൭7ട.ല.
Embrace your inner lemon.
൧്ക)97൧ 7 കഥാ ദ
Let it drive you.
87൭൧൭൧ ദ ഗ73)ലാ27൧700 7൦.
I'm detecting an extremely strong electromagnetic pulse.
൭൭൮൭ ഒട ഠ്ബധ്മ്ഥ ല്ല്വംനമണന ഥാ മനവല.
-Finn, it's the camera. -Where?
00, റ്്വാഠ്ദ രണ ധ. 21 നമ?
On the tower!
൧ 25 ണലലയ!
This was meant to be alternative fuel's greatest moment.
ട്‌ ലാദഗഥുക, [ബ്‌ ടട! 4ലഗലാദ? ൧൭൫ ദ്ധ ദ് ഒ74ലനദ77 7.
But after today, everyone will race back to gasoline.
7 ദ്7 ടല്ലാദട ഗദഗ്‌ ഗ്‌, ടലാഥദ ഘഘല്‌ദ ഒ൭൧ 4ഘഥക7 ഗലററഥഗദദഗ ദട07൧7.
And we, the owners of the world's largest untapped oil reserve
൧കുഗ !ഗ്ദ, ൧ലാ% ല്മദഥ 724ന)ദ്ലലാഥടടക്ഗ ൪ റ്ഥദ
will become the most powerful cars in the world!
ഒദഥ ഗുഹദന്‌ £ല൦ല്ദ ൧൭൧0റ ൧ലല്ലദടദ ന്‌ വ്ഥദ7
Get out of the way!
1 ലാ!!
They will come to us, and they will have no choice,
ലല ൭൧ ദല ഗ്‌, റ്ദഗ ഗുലല്ദ 27ദറ്ദ 07777ഒ൧ 77,
because they will need us.
ടലാക്ഥ ഗാലലദ ദ ഗുലഹ്ഥ്ദഷഥ ഒ.
We figured you might stop by!
ബി ദ്വാര മഴ്യിലിത്ഥ ദേ!
And they will finally respect us!
൧കഗഥ ദഗ്നഗുഷക. ഗാലല്ദ ദ്ദ്ഥ നല്ക ഗ്ക
So hold your hoods high!
പ്ദന്‌ ൧2ലാകഗറ്റ്മ[ദഗ7!
After today, you will never again be ashamed of who you are!
ടല്ലാദട 7ദ്ഥ്‌ 7, ഒഴഖ്കലാല്ല'ദധ്‌ 7ഒ9ടദ 7ലാറ്ദ7 ന്ല്‌
No!
11ഠിമിഠ
Long live lemons!
ക്ലാഠറ്റ !ലല്ദ ദേഥഥ്‌ നവ്ഥാകഥദഗ൭ഥ ൧5൭7
Number 7 is loose! Shu Todoroki!
77072൧ഠ7 7 7ലഥക൧ഥദട! 57൧ 7ഠറ്ഠഗ0റ്‌!
Finn?
00?
Bumper to bumper as they approach the finish line!
൧ലടക്'ററ്റഗ ടലവ്‌* ന്‌ റുദല്ടകഗ ധാലാക്ഗുദ
McQueen's the winner! Francesco's second!
൧7ഠേഥംല ൧൭൧9 ഗ്‌ദ7 ൧ന്ഥ൦ടഠാ ന്‌ 4ല്വാദ! റ്ലക
This is impossible!
121 സ്ധററിന്സ്‌
That's what I'm talking about! Ka-chow!
1ധ്പ്വത്ഥാ ടമ നലിദ്ധഠിത്ല്‍്‌ 1(൭-ലഠഗ്‌
What happened?
൧3൮309 റാലിലിയ?
-Where are all the other cars? -What is going on?
പ്ള്‍ിീമനാ 1ഘലമഷഘലലല്‍്യ ല്ല? ്യാഥറ ടലഠ്ദണാലാലില്വാ?
Oh, no!
൨, വിറ്ലിറ്‌
Sir Axlerod, is the final race in London still going to take place?
൭൧൧ ൧റ്ലാറ്‌, ദറ്കഷ൧ ൧ല്ഥ്ഥാദദ്ഗ ൪ ൧ 07൨07 ദ൭൧ വ്‌4ലലടവഷ?
1 suppose that...
കു 735൭...
The show must go on, as they say.
൧ല്ഗ്ണാഥദക്ഗ ൧ല്ല ന4ലധടഥ.
I can't believe this is really happening!
111111: 1പാലമ്ാലലാലില്ഡ്‌
Quiet!
മസ്‌
Will you require all the racers to still run on allinol?
൧ീറ്ദഷഗ ദ7ലഗടട ടലാലദ ല്ഗ്ണമദ ഗാലാററഗദഷ്ഥ ൭൧7077
1 cannot, in good conscience, continue to risk the lives of any more race cars.
ക്കു 7ഒ ടറഗ 'ദവ്‌ ഗുല്ടയക്ഥ ഒഴ 4ഘഘലദ-ഘലല്ദ [൧ന2൭.
The final race will not be run on allinol.
൧ലഗ്ണാഥദദ്ഗ കഗ൦ ദദ്വഗദ്ഥ നഹറ്റഗാദ്ധദ്ഗ ഒ77904.
There you have it, a clearly devastated Sir Miles Axlerod
൧ഹറ്റദഗ വ്ധദധക൧൭, 57777ടെ ൧റ്ലഠറ്‌
announcing that he will not require the cars to use allinol for the final race.
ഗാലറ്ഗ്സഗ്നശ കഥ ധല്‌ഗ്ണാഥദകഗ 7 റ൭൧ഥല്ല ദവ ഗ)ലാററഥഗദഷഗ ഒ77004.
A toast!
വല്ലോ ടല്മണമി
To the death of allinol and alternative fuel forever!
12നമ0ി൨ ലയ ലിഗം ദേ മാമല ദ്വ ല്ലനമ്‌ ടല്ണമിണനബയി
Mater, abort the mission.
ഗീമല,ലാമ്യിത്ഥ മ്പ്ടി.
They've got Finn. Get out of there. Get out of there right now.
സിലലര ഠി ഥാഠിന്വാ 0൩0. ല്ല ദ്മ്ലി ടിഡ ടല.
How is your grandfather?
ാലനാനാ ഠ്യ
Long live lemons!
ടല ൧൦൭ ലോധ ദ്വാര ധടിമ!
Isn't this a great party, lvan, huh?
മെ ബ്‌ ലാമ, ാധിത്ഥ?
Yeah, it's unbelievable.
മ, ഖല 19൭൭.
You are not leaving, are you?
ലിറ ഗമി ലി്ലാധ്ഥ?
Of course I ain't leaving.
ടറി ലിം.
-I'm just in shock... -McQueen?
-ടദുദ ഗോദ !ല്ഘ്ഥ്‌... പ്ഥീദ്വധേല?
Crashes are a part of racing, I know,
ക്കു ദലം, (ഘാദ'ദഗറദദ ഗുലനകഗറ ൧൭൧൦ ൧735൭ റക ൧ല്ഥാഥദകഗ,
but something like that should never happen.
4ദ്വ7 ॥ല്ദന്‌ദഗ ടല 46 ടലാദ?ഗഥ്ഒ ൧ല്ക്വ.
You can choose your fuel for the final race. What it'll be?
൧॥൭൧൦7ല 27770 ഗഗഗ ദ7 ഗല ൧ലഥസാമദദഥ ഒ:ഗ൧. ൧൧൭ 27770ദ7 ദേഖ്‌
Allinol.
൧70൦൪.
After today?
ടല്ലാദട 7ഘ്ദന്കഗ 7ദല്‌ 7?
My friend Fillmore says it's safe. That's good enough for me.
ശദഷഥ ട൭)൭, ൧77707൭൦ :3൭3 !ദ ടല്‌ക്ഗാദ॥. 720 റ്ദ്ധ നലഗേഗ്ഥ.
1 didn't stand by a friend of mine recently.
ക്കു 74ഒ4ഥാലവഠഥറ 7ദ്ധ്ഥ ടക ൧൭൧൧൧൭൧൮ 7൧.
I'm not gonna make the same mistake twice.
കു ?ദ്ഗഥ ഗണഗറ്റല്കഗമ്‌ £൭5ദ൧ക൧ 9൧9 ടക൧ദ.
So a surprising revelation from Lightning McQueen.
൧ലറ്ല്ദ്ധകഗ ഗാലാറ്റല്ഗ്്ഷ്ഥ റ്ദഗ്ഥദറ്ദ 270770700 17൦0ലെ.
He will use allinol in the final race, despite what occurred today.
൧3 7ല്‌ക്യാ ൭൭൧ 7ലറ്ററഥഗദ്ഷഗ ഒ700, ദഥാഥ ടല്ലാദട 7ഘ്ദന്ദഗ ഗ്ഗ 7.
-... till Lightning McQueen is dead. -Of course.
-...5ല000ദ 1൨7൧0 17൦ഠേഥലല 731. -ടധഠിമ ബഡ.
Allinol must be finished for good.
൧൩൦ ബട ര്‍നഘജിത്ഥ.
McQueen cannot win the last race.
1-111-11] ാലിധ്പാമമഥ ലിമ്പ.
Lightning McQueen must be killed!
110൫10 നദ്വേം ബട വാഥസ്ധ്ബ
No!
11ഠിമിഠ
It's the American spy!
൧19 ാലിട॥ഗ്ണലിര ഡി
Dad-gum!
ലില്യ!
Gatling gun. Request acknowledged.
ടല൮ദദ ൭3702. ൧70 ദഥ ൨47).
Down! Everybody, down!
ന്ധ0ഠ്ധിറ്‌ ടലസ്ഡമ, ഡറഠ്ധിറ
-Shoot! I didn't mean... -Request acknowledged.
ണമി ടമ മലാല... ഛഗദ്ധകഗ വലു.
Wait! Wait! I didn't mean that kind of shoot!
ധാ. സ്ഥ ടമ മിവാലമ്ദലാടറിധ!
Correction acknowledged. Deploying chute.
൧ലാഥലല്‌കഗ ദ൦ഒ൧ക൧. 77ലനദടകഗറവാദ7ദഗേ.
Whoa!
ബ്‌
McQueen!
ീദ്ധേലലബ്‌!
Whoa! What's this?
ഗഗ ഗ്വാലിയ ഡാ
Whoa!
ഗവ
McQueen! McQueen!
സീഗഠ്ധേലലബ്‌ 7ീഠ്ധേംബ!
Let me through! Let me through!
-111:1111:1111-111:111:111
Let me in! I got to get through to warn McQueen!
8ലാ്ലിത്ഥ ടമ ല്ധ! ടമ ാല്ധ മാലി മണല്ഥ ശ്വാദഠ്ഠ റീദ്ധേബ്‌!
You cannot-a come through here! Back up.
യി ല്ലാം ബില്ധ ഠി ടബ്‌! ദലഡ്ധേ.
We have a lunatic at gate 9.
൧03 ലല 911൭ 010൩൮ധ 9.
I was disguised as a tow truck to infiltrate this lemonhead meeting
ടമൃ൭ നല്യതണദ്ധ ടലാമാലി ലഗേ ധവധിടല്മി നടടുധമലലട്മ ല്വോധിം
and my weapons system's done misinterperated what I'm saying!
ദ്ദ ടിടന ടലവുമ്മ ടമ ടിന രര ടമ്മ!
-Lunatic at gate 9. -McQueen! McQueen!
ലല 919 ഠി 0൩൮ 9. രീദ്വധേലലവ്‌! റീഗ്ധേലലല്‍്‌
-You are the champion! -This way, signore.
ഛഡ്യിധ്ധമ്യ! ലിലി മമവബ്‌.
-McQueen! -Mater?
പ്ഥീദ്േധേലല്‍! പില?
-McQueen. -Give us a pose!
്ഥീദ്േധേലല. “101000 ലാലു ധനധിറുമമ്പാല്‌
-McQueen! -Stop moving. Stop!
ലല ലലല ദല!
Where you going?
14൦ നമാ മധ്യിറലി്ലാലയി!?
Stop!
ലല!
-McQueen! -That really sounded like...
പ്ഥീദ്േധേലല്‍! ഡ 1ദഠിലറുമ്ന ടലാലല്‍...
Mater!
നില്‌
-Mater? -Signore?
പില? ലിറ
McQueen! They're gonna kill you!
സീദ്വധേലലബ'! സീലലല്‍ മിരബാധഗ്ധി മഗ്ലിറ
Mater!
നില്‌
Excuse me.
1 ധന്വാററ ദ്ധ.
No, where are you going?
11ഠിമിശ നമാ മഴ്യിധലിലാലയി!?
Scusi. Mater!
1 ധന്വാഥറല്ധ. സീല്‌
-McQueen! -Scusi.
പ്ഥീദ്േധേലല്‍! “ധന്പാമററ മില.
Mater! Mater!
നീല ഗീമല!
Mater, I'm so glad to see you.
നില, ടമ റലമ്പാ നമ ലാല്ധമ്പാമ മഗ്ലിം.
Lightning McQueen! I am a huge fan.
100ബ്നാ നീദ്വേംബ്‌ ടൃ ലാല്‌ ടലി ഗമി
I'm sorry, I thought I heard...
നാല്‌, ടവ നിത്ഥ ടമ ല്ലോ...
That was me. I said, "You killed out there today. You're the best."
1ധ ട൭൭. 5൮൭ 1൭൭, "ശഡ്യിവാധബ്ധ നലല ടലസ്ധാ. ഗസ്മിലാട
-What? I mean, thanks. -Right this way, signore.
്യാമ? ലിന ൭ട॥൨. ലിലി മമവബ്‌.
l really thought I heard my friend.
ടൃ ലാലമാലല നിന ടമ ലഠിലറ്റല് ടമ മഗ ടമ൭.
In England, you'll be finished! At the finish line.
811 511:]:111:1111-1:1:1-11:1:111111:1 111: 1-111-10
-Wait, what? -The press is waiting.
“ലററ, ലാമ? ൧151 ന൦ലഠി9 ട൦ലഠ്ദററ നലസ്ധഥാ9.
Come-a with me, please.
101൦09 ॥ധ% ടമു൭.
Let me go!
1ലാദടി്ഥ ടമ!
You actually care about that race car.
എഗ്യിലാലമ്ധാലല ബ്ബ ലയ; മററ വല്യ ധമ്പാദ ഡ.
A pity you didn't warn him in time.
ഗിയ, മിലി ടലമ്പാമ നലബ്പാലിവഥ ദമ ണമ.
"Idiot"? Is that how you see me?
ഫഠ്ഠഗ"? ൧൭ ഗ്വാ ദൃ ഥല്‌?
That's how everyone sees you. 1 tell you, that's the genius of it.
ടലാഥദ 7ഘല്ദ ഗ7ദ70൭% ദഴഷഥംവ്‌ല. 9 ടദ£ഥ 7റ്ല 9൭൧ ഗദ ൧7൭.
No one realizes they're being fooled
79% ദറ്ദ ട൦ട൮ക്യാദ ടലറ്ദ് 39൧0 നലല വ്ഥലഥഠറ്ഠഥഗദഷഥ
because they're too busy laughing at the fool.
ടലാക്ഥ ഗലല്ദ ?ലല്‌ക൧ 52൧ഥ ഗാലറ്റല്ദകഷഥ ദ
At the fool...
ലാറ ദ...
Excuse me!
1111 :):111:11:111]
Domo arigato!
ലിന മട്വാബതി്ലാബുമിറ
You done good. You got all the leaves.
ട്രൃയ്വാമട. ൧ഗമി്ലാമവ്ാ ടലസ്ധ ദ്ദ.
Check out that tow truck. I wonder who that guy's with.
[11:1:110:1 11:11: ൧൭ റ്മ൭09 ലമ ടിദ്വാ മിസ.
Will you guys excuse me just for one little second?
ീലിര്ഥ ടമ൭ ടലാലഘ.
Now that's a scoop of ice cream!
ീമമേണ ഡധിമ്വാലധ ധേഡോ!
Somebody get me water! Sweet relief.
ലലിത്ഥ ടയ ഖല ലു ബ൭.
Mater!
നില്‌
But I never leak oil. Never.
ചാ ബ്ബ ടമ ഖിധാലനലി നലവ്ലിം. ല്ധ്ാലനമ.
Get a hold of yourself. You're making a scene!
നീല, 1൦ ഗ്യ 0. ഗ്യിറ്മ്പാധാധലംംവല്‍
Wait a minute. I didn't screw you up, did I?
പി ഠ്ധ്ധ. ട൭൮൭ മന ബവടമ്പത്ഥ മഴ്യിപാധിര്ഥ?
-l lost the race because of you! -Maybe if I talked to somebody...
ടമ മില ഠിടലാദ്ധിവ്ഥ മമ പ്ള്‍്ധിന്ധപ॥ിര ടയ മിത...
I don't need your help!
ടമ മിധ്ാലിധിത്ാബധാമ മഗ്യിറ
I don't want your help.
ട൭൮൭ മന്ദാ ധി
Your help...
ദാബധഡാഥ മഗ...
Bang the gong. Get it on!
ലവി 9൦09. ലട
Listen, this isn't Radiator Springs.
൧൧ ഥ്‌ £ദവ്ദ7ഠ7 507795.
This is exactly why I don't bring you along to these things!
ടലാലാ ബിമ൨ ടമ്മ ലം ലലിലാമഗെ മയി 1ലരാല്ധമ്പാമമബാല്റ്ബി!
Holley! Finn! Where are we?
0 0൩ബ ൧ നാഥലിത്സസ്മ്വാലമ്മ?
We're in London, Mater, inside Big Bentley.
ദമ 01 1൦൦0, നീല, ഠി ഠ്ച്മനദ ദണില.
This... This is all my fault.
ടലസ്ഡാ ബി ടലിമ ട൮൭.
Don't be a fool, Mater.
പ്ഥ92ബ൮9ഠ 0൦൦0, സനീമല..
But lam, remember? You said so.
ല്വാ ടമ നണമറ9 ഠ൦ഠ൦0? ഗ്യ ടലി മ്യ്വാലറ്ധ.
When did l...
81 ലാധി ടമ൮൭...
Mater, l was complimenting you on what a good spy you are.
നീല, ടമ ലാലി മഡ്യിലാധ്വി ലമ മഗമി്ലാലിടിറത്റ ടട.
I'm nota spy!
ടമൃാധിമബലാലിടിറ
I've been trying to tell you that the whole time.
൭൮൭ റിമ ധോാലിര്ഡ മഴയ ടലമണട ബി.
l really am just a tow truck.
ടമൃ൭ ധേന ടലാധ ആചിധദ്ദേ.
Finn, he's not joking.
00, ഠി ല്ധാലധ്ത്വ.
-l know. -You were right, Finn. I'm a fool.
ടമ യ. -ഒല്‍ധി। ൭൭ ഡല ൧0൨. ടൃ ാഠഠ൦1.
And what's happened to McQueen is ‘cause I'm such a big one.
ടലസ്ധമമനാ ഹാലിമ്വ ഘ്വാറ്മ ീഗ്ധേലല ഒഠ്മിദ൨ല് ഷ്രാംഠ്ം00 5൭൭.
This is all my fault.
ടലസ്ഡാ ബി ടലിമ ട൮൭.
-Good. You're up. -And just in time.
-8മറൃധട. ൧ഗമി0ഥ്ല ടലഠ്ല. ലാമമാര്‍ നാട.
Professor Z wanted you to have a front-row seat,
൧ഠ്ലടഠ॥ 2 09! ഗമിലിമ ലോല,
for the death of Lightning McQueen.
നമി 90ബ്നാ ഗീദ്ധേല.
-He's still alive? -Not for much longer.
212 ണനമട। ബ്ഠ്വോ? 11൩൭ ധനധി ടലശ്ലിവധ.
-We came as soon as you called. -I called to talk to Mater.
“രി റമ ടലലോ സ്ധഥണാ!ന്൩. ടമ്മ ധോ നലണ്ഡാധനാ। നീല.
It never occurred to me he wouldn't be there.
൭൮൭ ൭1 ടര റി രിദ ഠി ടമ.
Sheriff is talking to Scotland Yard now.
൮൭൬ ടലി നല്ധാധനാ! ടി നവ.
And Sarge is in touch with his friends in the British military.
ഉമ ടാ മണ്ഡ! മിര്ഥ-യിത്ഥ ലട ഒറിറിടവത.
You just need to focus on the race.
7 ധന്വാധിധ്ഥ ട്വ ലാലി 1ല്ാഠ്ദ ാലിധമ്പാമമ ബ്‌.
I know but, Sally with everything going on, I'm not sure...
ടൃ ്ഡ, ടലി തവി ലമ ടലസ്ധമ ൮ നാ ലാലില്വ, ടയ ഖിധാടടി...
-Sir Axlerod. -I'm sorry to interrupt.
511 ഷഠിലഠഠി. 1-1: 6111:111-1:1:111:1:111
-It's all right. -[ just wanted to personally thank you.
“110 ണലാ്്വാമ. ടമ 0൭1ധല്ലോ ലിന 1൨൭ട॥൨.
Because after Italy, l was finished, and then you gave me one last shot.
ടൃ ാധ്ഡട ൭ട3 ടലിലാമട ഘദഠിബ്ധ, 'ല്വാ മഗ്ല്ലാലി ടമ ല്വാമഥ ലഘിമ്പ.
Listen...
ഉലാ ടബ്‌...
I probably shouldn't be saying this, but I hope you win today.
ടൃ വാധ്വ, ലവി ടയ ല്വാ മയി നല്‌ ബി.
You show the world that they've been wrong about allinol.
1 ധബധിദത്ഥ ശ്വാ ഠ്ധബ്ഠ റാലഠ്ലാമ നലല മറു 211൦ ടമ.
Mater would want you to race.
നീല ബല മിമഗ്ല്ലാല്ധമ്പാമ.
All right. For Mater.
810൭൨. ൧0ലബി നീല.
Here he comes.
ധ്യാന ഠ1൭.
-What happened? -I don't know, Professor.
൧൮൭ )ഒഥറ ഗല്‌? മവ, ലഠ്ടടംം.
-What did you do? -I didn't do nothing.
ഗ്വാ ൮൭0 മഗ്യിലാധമറ ടമ മിവാധമ ലാലാ.
I'm talking to the Professor. What's that, Professor?
ടൃ ലാലമേശ്വാ ലാന ലഠടടം[. വാടിയ ഡ., ലഠ്ടടംന?
-You broke it! -Quiet!
ഛഡ്യിവംടമിനത്യി! -൧1ബസ്‌
-l understand, sir. Yes. -What did he say?
ടമ ലന, ഡമഥ. ൫. ഗ്വാ വര?
-We go to the back-up plan. -Back-up plan?
6 1:1:111:15:11- 11:11 11: “ഹേനാ ശദ്ധ?
We snuck a bomb in McQueen's pit.
ബി ഥേി-ഗഥേോ ട്രിവാംണ ഠമിമണ ബലി ൧൦.
The next time he makes a stop, instead of saying "ka-chow"
8112 റി ലാലില്ി ഠിം
he's going to go "ka-boom"!
ഠി മിഥ നല്ലാ!
Don't feel bad, tow truck. You couldn't have saved him.
പ്ല ടലഠ1൩, ല൦ഡനഠ്ോ. ഗ്യ മലി സ്ധനിന്ന ലാമ ടല.
Wait, you could have!
10 ദ്ധ്ധ, മഗ സ്ധനഠിന്സാംല്‍വ
-Dad-gum lemons! -Request acknowledged.
ലല ല്വോധിം ംല്മിയ ഛഗദ്ധകഗ വലു.
What? You didn't think we'd take your bullets?
൧3? ൧ഥമിഥിനന വമി ലം മമ്പാ॥ാല്ധസ മധ്ല്റ
That's right! You got nothing!
ലഡഡ! ൧്യിറ്മിശ്വപിാമ ടാലി ബമ!
Who's the lemon now, huh?
ടരല്വാമ ൮00 ലോധി ടല്രഖ്മുെ, നമാ?
Nice try, Mater.
ധാമ ധാലിം സീമ്ല..
-Dad-gum... Dad-gum... Dad-gum. -Request... Request... Request...
-ല2൭1൪൭... ഠല൭1൪൭... 9ല൭1൨. ലനാ! ദദഥ... ൧ലഗാഥഗ!ദക്ഗ... ൧ലണ7...
Mater!
നില്‌
I got to get y'all out of there.
ടൃ ാലിധ നലിലാമടിമറ മധ്യം ടലസ്ധമ.
There's no time. McQueen needs your help.
[പ്ര ിദഠിമ നട. സീഗ്ധേംബാലിധിര്ബാബധമ മഡ്ലിം
But I can't. I'm just a tow truck.
ച്വാ ടമ മഠ ണമമ്പാധ. ടയ ധേന മധ.
It's up to you. Go to the pits and get everyone out.
ബി ലാലമഡന9 ഷാമി ഉല ൭1 ഠ്‌ ടി നലല ലാലി.
-You can do that. -What about you guys?
ശ്ഡ്യിവാംില്‍ ലഡു. ഒമറുല്നമനാ ലോന മഗ്മി്ധാല്ധമ?
-We'll be okay. -Go and get some more dents, Mater.
രി ഖി ല്വാമ-ല്ാമ. ലു! റ്ല്വാദധിദ്ഥശ്ബിധാല, ീമല.
So, we'll be okay? Really?
പ്9ഠി।, ാല്ധിയ്ഡന്ത ഖിലാദലാമ?
He wouldn't have left if I'd told him the truth.
81:11: 5:11 :1-1:1] [11൭ ടൃ ലാനലലട-ല്.
Being killed by a clock.
ഉ॥ാധഗ്ധ ില്വ്യമന.
Gives a whole new meaning to “Your time has come.”
8ലി ലബിധാമലബ ഘാദറ്ദ 1൭൪൭-൭൭, 1:11: 11111111
Time? That's it!
ീടടമ? ധഠില
-What are you doing? -Trying to turn back time.
ഗ്വാ ൮൭0 മഗ്യിലാധമറ ധാ നലാലമ്പാലി॥ത്ഥ ണടടമ.
If l can just reverse the polarity.
ദ്രിമ്ധിലി ടമ ാഠില നലലാല॥ത്ഥവഡ്ധാബത.
Good job. Quick thinking, Holley.
ട്ൃയ്വാമട. ബനാ വി, 11൦1൮.
What's everybody on the wrong side of the road for?
1ലദ്വാ ടലസ്ധാ ഖല ലാലമഠ്ദ ഠി ടലാലദവ്യമിബണാ ടമ്മാ?
No!
11ഠിമിഠ
Drive! Burn rubber!
ഉദ്ധ! ലറബില്ധ!
We've got to get to the course.
1വമാല്ധവാലറി വ.
Calculate the fastest way to...
[പന ദ്ധാഥ ഇമ ധധി൦..
Done.
ടലിലടലി.
Miss Shiftwell.
ലടവ്ഡലി.
-They're standard issue now. -You kids get all the good hardware.
:11.1:11:111 1111 ഡയ റ്ല്വാമലാലിടി തററ ബട.
No, that's Mater's.
നഠ്മ്ധലഡ ബി॥ഗസ്ല.
I knew his escape was too easy.
ഉഡി ഠി റ്ലാമ നല്ലാദടിത്ഥ റല ഠ്ലാമഥ സ്ധദ്മ.
Come back here! Stop!
1ല്ബാലി॥! ദല!
-Mater? -Everybody, get out now!
പില? -ടലസ്ധമ വല, ഘ്ധല് ടലര്ധമനാ!
Y'all get out of the pits. What are you guys doing here?
1ല്ധല ഠ്ഖ്ലി 01. ൧3 മഗ്യി ടലസ്ധ ധി ടലി?
-We're here because of you, Mater. -ls everything okay?
“രി ഠാ ഷമ മഗ്യിപ്റീല. -ടലസ്ധമബ ടല
No, everything's not okay. There's a bomb in here.
11൭ ടലസ്ധാബ ൭1 ടല്മണമ'. ൧03 ലാഠനഠിട്ബി.
-Y'all got to get out. Now. -A bomb?
ഛഡ്യില്ാലിധ ഘ്ധമ്ധ ടല്ദ്ധമനാ. -8ഠണ?
-Mater. -Finn! You're okay.
ചീദ്ദ7ല. -0ബ 7ഡമിടല്ണമ്‌.
Listen to me. The bomb is on you! They knew you'd try to help McQueen.
8ഠണ മഠ ാ3ഠിഒ ഗമി നീലല്ര മധ ഗമി മിര ധോ നീദ്വേട.
When we were knocked out, they planted it in your air filter.
ലാദടദ !വ്ദ ാലറ്ടകഗ, ഗാലല്ദ ൧35൭൧9 ൧07 ലാദറ്ദ ൧ലാഥട ലറ്ദഗ ദ
Mater! There you are!
നില ഡാധന മഗ്ലിറ
-Stop right there! -I've been so worried about you.
ലല ഠി ടിഡി! ടൃ ട്ടാ ബറ മലി.
-Don't come any closer! -Are you okay?
പ്റമന ദ്ദ ലിയാ ടമ്മ! ഡയറിയ?
No, I'm not okay! Stay away from me!
11 ടയ മിദ്‌ പ്ടധ്വര്ഥ 0 ചി ടയ!
No, wait! Wait!
11൭ ഡനാഠധ! സ്ഥ
A tow truck has just raced onto the track, driving backwards!
ട്‌ലാഥമ 27മല്ല്ഥറ്ട ഗലനദടഥ്റ്‌ ലം, ട൭൧2൧ ഗാലനദഗറ്ഥ ൪ ൧ലദ്ക്റ്‌
Mater, wait!
നീല, ഡാ
Normally an emergency vehicle on the track means there's been an accident.
8॥ മഠിമ ഗ്ലാ ലേനടടാഥ ഠി നലം ാലലി ണമി ര്‍്വ്വാലില്വ.
-Lightning McQueen is chasing him! -Mater, wait!
-2൨0൧00 ഗഗ്‌ഗേഗഥംല ഗഥറ്ംദഗ)൭ ്ള്‍ിമല, ഡന്‌
Stay back! If you get close to me, you're going to get hurt real bad!
1: 111:1:1111-1:1, പ്ര മ മഗ മിഥ ലേല ലധിറ്‌
I know I made you feel that way before, but none of that matters!
ടയ മധ ടമ ്വ്പാധമ മം ഒട ലാലി, ല്വാ॥ ടലസ്ധഖ ലിധ്ാഹ്നാ!
We're best friends!
ടലാലാ 10൭ മിമലദഥി!
And McQueen seems to be having
൧ക്ഗ ഗദഗ്വാദധഗദ 7്ഠേലംലാ
a conversation with the tow truck.
ടറ്ദ്ഗറ ൧ലഥഥദ! റ്ഥറ്റദഗ 77ദലഥാറ്ദ 770.
1 don't know who that truck is, Brent, but tell you what,
ക്കു ?ദ്വലകഗ7ഥ ന്ദ ട്‌ദ്വാദ, 27ല%
he's got to be the world's best backwards driver.
4ദ്വ7 ൭൧0 ൧൭577, ന്ദ ാലാദഗറ്ഥ ൧൭ ൧ലകഷഥറ 4ല൧൭% ന്‌ റ്ഥ്ഒ.
McQueen, you don't get it! I'm the bomb!
ീദ്ധേലല, മയി യിസ്മ്ഘലന! ടമൃയിമ്പാംണ ധി!
Yes, Mater! You are the bomb! That's what I'm trying to say here!
വര, നീല ൧ഡമിധനലനമന ലാമി ധ്ര്വത്നാ ടമ൭ ധോ ത്യ
You've always been the bomb and you'll always be the bomb.
൧ഗ്യിം നന (ലാമ ടല്ദണമനബമ.
-Stay away! -No! Never!
പ്റാമന ലിവ “റ്ലിറ മസ്ധാിന്ന്‌
Almost there.
ടിസി.
I'm not letting you get away again!
ട൭൮൭ മറമ്ാലിത്ഥ മഴ്യിലാലാ! ടല! ൭൮1!
-Got to keep away from McQueen! -Request acknowledged.
ടൃ ാലിധ്ദധ്വ സീദ്ധേലലല്‍്‌ ഛഗദ്ധകഗ വലു.
Oh, my gosh.
ചിന.
What is happening? It's a bad dream!
൧3൮309 റാലിലിയ? ബി ടാഡ സ്ന്പാി നാല്‌!
And Lightning McQueen just blasted away,
കഥ 007൧70 77ഠേഥംഹഗ ഗല്‌ ദഥ,
hooked to the now rocket-propelled tow truck.
൨7 ദേഗവഡ്ലഘാദറ്ദ (ഘല്ദ ?ഥറ്ദ 39൧9 ന൩7ലവവ്വാ്‌ ൦7 70൭.
The Professor's on the run!
൧ഠ൭ടം। നല്ലി ഠി!
-Someone's got to get McQueen. -Get McQueen!
101009 ധബടിര്ഥ ഗീദ്വധേല. 11111]
-Holley, I'll get Zindapp. Help Mater. -Got it!
ടമ നില്ല 200ഠ്ല്യ്വാ. ഒവഡ സഗീമല..
What is happening?
൧3൮309 റാലിലിയ?
Hurry, Professor.
ലാ, 00്ലടഠ.
You really think I'm going to let you float away, Professor?
എഗ്യിറനിന ടര ലിത്ഥാിലിര്ഥ മഗ്യില നല്ലി 0, ലഠ്ടെം?
-McQueen, let go! -Never!
പരീദ്ധേലലറ, ല്ാമടിയബ്‌ റമി
-They're coming your way. -Let's go!
പ്ീലലയ ണലധ്ധ ദ മമ മധ്യം ഛശൃധ്
Give it up, McMissile.
1ധ്വാവ്വഥ ടദ്യദ, നീഗ്ഗിടട॥ല.
-Mater, stop! -No way! You could get hurt.
ച്ഗിീമല,ലാലലി! റല ഗസ്മിസ്ഥന്ന ലിത്ഥ ലേല.
Oh, no.
൨. ദിട്ചം.
Mater, we've got to get that bomb off you.
ീമലലയഠണ ഥാഠാലിത്സാംണസ ഠാ മഗ.
Bomb?
ഗണ?
Yeah, they strapped it to me to kill you as a back-up plan.
൭, 1 മേമന ദ്ധ നലല ധധിധാധസ്ധി മധ്യം.
Back-up plan? Mater, who put a bomb on you?
മാമാ ദ്ധ? സീല്‌, ടല്വാ ലാട ലാഠണധാഠഠ്ദ ഗ്ല
You! Why didn't my death ray kill you?
൧ഡഗ്യിദ ലലാ ലാമ ണമധ്‌ ടര മോലിവധസ്ധ മയി്ര
Death ray?
ഉമ്ഥലേ്ഥനമ്ധ
Turn off the bomb, Ziindapp!
1-1: 1:11111121111:1:1)
Are you all so dense? It's voice-activated.
1ലദ്വാ മഗ്യി ടലസ്ധമാലറ്റലാ ടാ 19 ഠിമിവിമ്ഥ ലമ ടയ.
Everything is voice-activated these days.
ടലസ്ഡാവാലറ്ല്രാധാലററ്ഡയ ാഠ്ദ മമനാഥ ടല്വഷ്ഥ.
Deactivate! Deactivate!
ഗിിമബമ! സീദിര്ുയി
Voice denied.
൧ ദഥക്ഗ ടഥദഗദ 29% സ്‌ാ.
Did I forget to mention that it can only be disarmed
൭൭൮൭ 909 ടലാധ മം ൭09 19 ൨൩൮൭ 1൦1ല൨ ദിനമ്ധിര്ഥ
by the one who activated it?
ഠ1ല൨ ടയ നലാല്നിര്ങുര?
-Say it. -Deactivate.
1(മ്ിമ൩൩൫൭. പീത.
Voice denied.
൧ ദഥക്ഗ ടഥദഗദ 29% സ്‌ാ.
I'm not the one who activated it. Would anyone else like to try?
ഒധിത്ഥ ടയ ൭൧ നസലാദന്നര്സു. ട്രല്വാദ 391 നല ലോ?
-You read my mind. -He was getting on my nerves.
ശ്യാമേ 7ഗന0 ട൭൮൭. -൧1ാധമ ടമ ലിമ.
-What do we do? -It's very simple. You blow up.
ഗ്വാ !റ്മ ല്ധാധാ ഥീ ട്വ. ഗയിം ണലില്ധാ.
I'm going out on a limb here. These are the guys that want me dead, correct?
ടൃ നമി ധോ ലി൪൭. സിലല്ര ലി ടമര നമി, ലാലി?
-It's nothing personal. -Fellers, listen.
ിാധിരഥ നടടമിമ്ലാലിമഠി. രഗ, ലേല ടിബി.
I know what you're going through. Everybody's been laughing at me too.
1 5:111:1111:1:1:1:1:1-1:1 1:11] ടലസ്ഡാ ലമ ദമഡലിത്ഥ ടമ൮൭.
But becoming powerful and rich beyond your wildest dreams
“ചാ। ഭിവമടമഥ ്മലിഘ്യയരമ്
ain't gonna make you feel better.
ിറിത്ബാധ മലി ടദ ലാറ റ്ല്പാ.
Yeah, but it's worth a shot.
൭, ദ്വ യി 0൧01ല്‍ ധോ.
Pit stop.
ദിലി ലി.
Not today, boys.
11ഠിമിധാമഠിട ലി ബി.
Retreat!
8ലഡറഠ്ധ്‌
Thanks for the help, Corporal.
ലിന മടി ഒട ലാമനധമറ മഡ്യിം ലാലമി.
Anything for one of Pop's mates.
൧3 ട്വ ഠിലമ്്‌ ഗമി ൦0.
What's he saying? What's wrong?
൧3 നമിദധ്ബേരാ? വാമന ദ്വധവശസമ?
None of his wrenches fit the bolts.
1109 ടമഡ ലാധലാലല്റിഡ്സുമ ടലടധലി ലാം.
I get it. I get it!
ടൃ മന. ടമ ലല്‌
-l know what needs to be done. -Then do it!
ടൃ ഖ്ഡധ മ്വാ ൮൭09 ലധ ദ്ലാധമ. മിയി ടല!
What? No. I can't do it.
൧൮3? നറ നലിവാംല.
Nobody takes me seriously.
ടടടില്വാ ലാന മില്ല ദേശ്വാ ടമ൮൭.
I know that now. This ain't Radiator Springs.
ടൃ മണ ടലവഷ്. ബി ാധിര്ഥ മറി ട്രാന്ന9ട.
Yes, it is.
110൭1൦.
Look, you're yourself in Radiator Springs.
ഗ്യ മി്ലാലാധമാഥ്തു ഠി ഠി ട്രാന്നാട.
Be yourself here.
൧ഗ്യി മിലാലിധാലാധമാഥ്ടു ഠി ട്ബ.
And if people aren't taking you seriously,
ഉബ൮॥൭ നലലര മലി ്ലോദ്ധ ലപിഷ്വാ ഗ്ല,
then they need to change, not you.
4901 നലല ാല്ധ ലാലാല, ധി മധ്യം.
I know that because I was wrong before.
ടൃ മധ ടലാലാ ടമ ദ്ഖ്പാധടില് ടലാല്ധന ബി.
Now, you can do this. You're the bomb.
൧ഗ്യിധാംല്‍൨ലിഡിത്ഥബത. ൧ ലലാമ.
Thanks, buddy.
ലിനാ 1൭ട11, ത്യ.
No, you're the actual bomb. Now, let's go!
121 മഡ്മ്ധലാഠഗന ഡഖ. സിലി ലയി ടല്യ്ാ!
Right. Hang on!
ഒലഡി. ഒല്ചില്‌!
Where's he going?
14൦ നമ ഠി മ്ലാലയി!?
-Computer! -Yes, Agent Mater?
1(ഠസ്പാധ്ല? ീദ, £൧ല 77ദ4ല?
I need that thing you done before to get me away from McQueen!
8ധാലാല്മവ നാ സ്മ്ലാധാ ടലാല്ധനബ്‌ ധധിംണലവ്മ്ധ്വിത്ഥ ടമു൭ ചി നീദ്ധേലല്‍്‌
Request acknowledged.
൧ ദ്ധദ്ഗ ൨4ല്ഥാദ.
-Mater? -Now I need you to do the chute!
പില? ടറഗ
The second kind, not the first!
൧3100 മേധ, ധിരന ൮൭09 0ലമണല!
Deploying chute.
77ലനദടകഗറവാദ7ദഗേ.
Who's winning the race?
ട്ര്ല്വാ൮മനാ ലിര്ഥ നലല! ലാലിധ്പാമമ്?
-Back off! Back away! -It's Lightning McQueen!
ലാലാ! ദല ധ ല്ബ്ണാ നീദ്ധേംബ്‌
No, it's okay! Tell ‘em, Mater. Explain.
12% മ്വാല! 8ലല്യ്ഡ നലല, സീമല.. 1-111-11:
Okay.
വിവ.
Somebody's been sabotaging
൧03 ലലാ നലടലാംദ്്വ
the racers and hurtin’ the cars, and I know who.
റാല്ധമ്പാമ ദ്ദ ണലലേ്ലഘമിത്ഥ ഷലല്‍്മ, ദമ ടമ മഡ ടില്ാദ ദ്ദ.
Wait. Your Majesty.
ധനാ. സ്മബ്വ.
Bomb! It's a bomb!
8ംബ'! മ്മാ!
-Everybody, down! -Back up! Move it!
-ടലസ്ധാ ലമ, ഡഥഠ്ധിറ -ഒലഡറഠ്ധഥ! ലോ
Get off the stage! Move it!
ധന ലാലമട! ലോദി
Hold your fire! He can't disarm it!
1: 111:1:111:111:1:1 ൧1൭ റൂമ നലിയ!
Mater, I don't know what you're doing, but stand down now.
൭൮൭ മമ്ഡ ല്വാ മയി ലല്ലാധമം 'ല്വാിാലഡര്‍്ധ ടല്ഷ്ത്ഥു.
This ain't nothing at all like Radiator Springs.
ബി ലം ടണടിടേനാ ടല്ലാലി ഠി ൫301൭൦ ട്രാന്നഠിട.
Mater, just cut to the chase.
നില, ദേശ്വാ ടദ്യമിലി.
Okay. It's him.
ഠി. ൧ ഷല൭ബ൭.
What? Me? You've got to be crazy.
൧്൮ാമ? ടയ? ൧ഥ്യിലഡ ദേ ॥.
I figured it out when I realized
ടൃ റ്ല്വാമ മ്ഡ ലാട ടമ ലാലമടമ്ഥ
y'all attached this ticking time bomb with Whitworth bolts,
൭0൭ മഴ്യിലാമടമ9 ാഠണ ബി ഠ്ലബാം(ഗവ്ഡാനം
the same bolts that hold together that old British engine
[യത ടാണട റിലിര്ഥ ാഠ്ദ ല്പ൩ ഒല്്ട്വ്ലനട
from the photograph.
ടല്ലാലി റ്മിമണ സ്ബാല ഡ.
l remembered what they say about old British engines:
൭൮൭ ലന ലാനാ നലലര ൪൭ മറ ലപ്൩ ഒരിടം
if there ain't no oil under ‘em, there ain't no oil in ‘em.
1 1:1:1-1111111::1:11:1:1111112:1 നമര ഠി ബ്ബ ദ്മ്ദന്സമ.
What is he talking about?
൧൮0൮ ഠി നലിദ്ധഠിത്ന?
It was you leaking oil at the party in Japan.
ിബമമഗ്ല്റമനല്ലിം ടലനമട3 ലാബി ഠി ല്ാധനഡ.
You just blamed it on me.
ഗയിം ടലാല്മ ഡദ്ധ ടമ്മ.
Electric cars don't use oil, you twit.
ലല ലില്യി 'ലിധ്ാലിയി സ്ബത്പാഠഠ്൦.
Then you're fakin’ it. You didn't convert to no electric.
പഠി, മഗ്യിവാല്ലാധമാധ്ട ഡ്മ. ഗയിം ലിഡിയ നലവ്ഠഠി! ൭൭ ല്ല്ഡിം.
If we pop that hood, we'll see that engine from that picture.
പ്ര ന്മാധിര ഡാ ഗ്യ്പന്മ ല്ത്ഥ നബ്വാമി ലന ടലാലനി റ്ല്മന മ്പി ഡ.
This lorry's crazy! He's going to kill us all!
100 ബി ദ്ദ 9॥ ൧019 മിര്ബാധസ്ധ്വന്മ ടല്ധല
Stay away!
ലാലലാ!
But Sir Axlerod created the race. Why would he want to hurt anyone?
ചാ റിമാ സ്ധ്ലിത്നാലിധമ്പാമമ് ബി. 1ലമ്വാ റിമ നലം ല്ലഘ്ദ്ബാല്ധപാമ?
To make allinol look bad so everybody'd go back to using oil.
ട്വ 311001 മസ്വാലിലലഡിറ്മ ഗ്മ ശ്വാ നലാധേല്ത്ഥ ബ്ബ.
He said it himself with that disguised voice.
൧19 ടലഠ്ഥി ഥാ ൭൪൭ ഠ്ലുഥ ടധമമ ടാണമലധ.
Disguised voice? What are you talking about? You're nuts, you are!
ട്ഖമ ടണ്‌ ക്വാ ഒഡമിലനലിദ്ധഠിത്ന? ഗഡ്ലിഡ്ില്‍
This is going nowhere fast. We really should go, Grandmother.
ബി മിര നബലനധിമി്മബബാധനവ. 1പ്മാല്ധ ലാലി, സ്വബ്വ.
One moment, I'd like to see where this is going.
11:11) :111:11111-1: ഖാനാ ല്ദ്ബാലില്വ.
Mater, he created allinol.
നീല, റി വാമ 211൩൦1.
But what if he found that huge oil field
ചവ ാമുല്നമനാ 111൭ ഠി ല്‍ നലലന്ധ്‌ നടഠ്മ ബ്ബ
just as the world was trying to find something else?
9ഠ്ദ ദിര ബ്ല ധോ ണലല്വി മാമ്മ ല്വാി॥ ലിന?
What if he came up with allinol just to make alternative fuel look bad?
൧3 1൭൭ റിദ വ്യാ മനം ടധ്വാവ൭ മാമ ദ്വ ലി്ലനമഥശഷമാഥഡി്ര
“What if?” You're basing this on a "what if"?
ളാറ്റല്നാമമ്‌? ടലസ്ധമ ബ്‌ ബബ ലാല്മടെലിത്ഥ "ാമാല്നമ്്‌?
-Okay, that's it. -Lads, clear out.
ദ്വ, ഡോഡോ ടല്‍മിരല്ധ. -ടലസ്ധാ ലല, ല്ല.
Wait! Somebody save me! The lorry's crazy!
1111111111 1:11: 1ഠ0ിബി ഠി 91൮
-Keep away, you idiot! -Mater!
്ല്വ്ത്ഥ ദ ഠ്ഖ്ലി ടയ, ാഠഠ്ഠവ്‌ ്‌ഥിമല!
-Someone do something!
“101009 ാധമ ടലടധമധ!
You're insane, you are! Deactivate!
ഗ്യ റില്‍ ഗീിര്സുമ!
Bomb deactivated. Have a nice day, Sir Axlerod.
8077 റ്ദ്ധ ൨ഗാദ29൧. ടല്കഗാദ! ടല്ക4ല, 57 ൧റ്ലാറ്‌.
-The engine from the photo. -It's a perfect match.
ബന ഠി റമമ്പാല വധ. 99.
How did the tow truck figure it out?
ദാഠല്നാനാ നലോ ഡധ ഡാ
It's official. You're coming to all my races from now on.
520. ഗയിം ലിര്ഥ ധ്‌ ടമ 1 ടലസ്ധാലാലിധമ്പാമമ്റ സ്ധിലി ടല.
Now you're talkin’!
ീമമേണ ധിമി.
Mater, let's go. You're on.
നീല, നല. ടല 9൨ മധ്യം.
Your Majesty, may I present
1 ധാബ്വ, ടമ്മ ലാലി,
for the investiture of honorary knighthood of the British Realm,
ധവധിധട്ദ്ട്വാലാധ്സ്മമ നന ാറിര൭ടാലട ഗിയ ലട,
Tow Mater of Radiator Springs.
ഠ്‌ സീല്‌ ദി ൫൭01൭൦ ട്വാഥനാട.
Go get 'em, buddy.
ലു, മഴ്യ്ഥ.
I hereby dub thee Sir Tow Mater.
ഉലമ ബി, ടമ ധമ്്ലിത്ഥ 01൭ ലിക ടം ീടല.
Sir? Shoot, you can just call me Mater, Your Majesty.
ടാ? മറാഠ ട്വ സീല്‌, സധമബ്വ.
I don't wanna hear none of this "sir" business.
ട൮൭ മലല്നന ലേഘദ്ധ ാലിരമമ "ട്‌.
By the way, have y’all met each other?
൨, മഗ്മി്ധാലഠ്ധമ ഠ്്ഡാലിഘല്മഥെ?
Queen, McQueen. McQueen, Queen.
൫൮, ീ്േധേല. റീദ്വധേലല, മ.
McQueen, McMissile. McMissile, McQueen. Queen, McMissile.
ീദ്ധേലല, നീണ്ബ്ടടില. നീഗസീിടടില, ീദ്ധേല. ഭമഡ, നീണീിടട॥ില.
So there we was, my rocket jets going full blast,
ലിഡ്‌ ടയ നലല്‌ ടലാല്ഡസുരം
McQueen hanging on for dear life
സൃത്ഥര നീദ്ധേല ഠി ധന നാലേ
when suddenly them two nasty lemons come out of nowheres, guns drawed.
വാമ-ാഠ ഠ്ധ ൧൦൭ ലോധി സ്വേ ഠ്ലുമഥ ടല.
We was goners.
ബി ൭൨ ലമ ില്വാമ.
But then, out of nowhere this beautiful spy car
1102-02, സ്ധനഗോ ടലാധമ ലല ലാലിടി॥റന ബിം
swoops in from the sky to save us!
നല്ഥനധേ ലി 00% ധധി൦ണലബല്മണമിര്ിരമ്‌!
That's a very entertaining story, young man.
1ധടമ്നയമറ നല്ലി ലല സ്ധര്‍്മ.
Minny, please. Come on!
ബബ, ടധഠ്മ്പല ഡ.
None of this happened. Rocket jets, flying spy cars.
ടലസ്ഡാ വധ ഖ്ധാലനല്സാലില്വ. പ്ല 016൭ ലാലിടി॥റമാ നാഥ.
No, you're quite right. It does sound a bit far-fetched.
മിധാലലി। തര മഡ്മിം ഠോ ലം നാടധില ലവി.
Holley! What are you doin’ here?
1൦10 ഡാ ഗമി്വാധാഠി ടലി?
Hello, Mater! It's so good to see you again.
ലിം, റില്‌ ടമ ലബ്ബാ ാലലസ്ധ മഗ്യി ടലവി! 1൭91.
Finn!
ബ്‌
Our satellites picked up an urgent communiqué.
ടാലി നലാടടമ്ഥ ടമധലാലാധല്മ ലാലിനു.
So you got-a my email.
പഠി മഗ്യി് ലിന ണല്‍ ട൭൮൭.
Y'all is going to have a great time!
ഗ്യ ടലസ്ധമ ലിത്ഥ ടലി
Everybody, this here's Finn McMissile. He's a secret agent.
ദ്രഡ്മഥ-രഗാമഥ, ബി 00 നീഗിടടില. ൧012 ലീല മടി.
Don't tell nobody.
പ്ഥബാലിയ്ഡ ലട ദ്ന.
And this is Holley Shiftwell.
ഉല ബ്ല്ംല ടല.
-She's... -I'm Mater's girlfriend.
-212... ടമ ണമ ഡമബ്ര ീമല.
It's so nice to meet you all.
൭൮൭ റല്പാനമലാല്ധമ്പാമ മയ ടലസ്ധമ.
Guido believe you now.
ട്ല്യ്മാ, ധേഠ്ം ഉലമ മേശ്വാ മധ്യ.
Whoa, honey. You got a nasty dent there.
൨, ടമ൭൧൭9. 330 മഗ്മ്ലഘമി
-Yeah. -Was that from when you swooped in
൭. 19 ലല ടലനടടമ നല്ധനധേ ബാല
and you saved them in London?
ദമ നബല്മനമിന്ഥ നലല ഠി ॥ഠനഠിഠന?
-Van! -What? I'm just asking!
ഗ്മ ്യാമ? ടമൃ൭ ഡനാലമബമ?
Don't you worry. My baby Ramone can get that fixed up for you in no time.
പമ ല്ടധ. ഭമനംലാഠല്‍ നലബ്പാലിന്സയര ഠ്ഠ൦ണമ്ന ടല.
Yeah, sure thing. No problemo. Let me go get my tools.
൭, ടധഠമ0 ലല. ന്മ നടടിമ. ടയ മിലാ! ലല ടമ.
No. I'm keeping that dent. It's way too valuable.
ച്ധ്വാല്ധ. ടമു൭ നലിലാലിത്ഥ ട്വ. 19 ലില്ധാലലമ.
A valuable dent? She's as crazy as Mater.
1(ല്പിധമററ ലല? ൧19 919 ടലാലി ീമല..
Those two are perfect for each other.
സിലല്യാലഠ്ധമ മണമവാമഠ്ദ ടലര॥.
There's one thing I still don't get.
൧9 ടമ ലാലി 0 ട൮൭ പല്മണ.
The bad guys hit me with the beam from the camera, right?
ലല്ലലാ മേ റ്മ്വാഠ്ദ മണലയ ഡി മല ടമയര, ന?
-So, why didn't I... -Explode in a fiery inferno?
-പിഒഠി।, :ലല്വാദ ട൭ ൭൦... പ്ില്ല്ഡവാ?
-Yeah. -We couldn't figure that out, either.
൭. “ര്രമ്പ്വധ മ: ടലാലാബുമ.
Our investigation proved that allinol was actually gasoline
സില്ധഡ്ാല്വിടാമയി, ഒനം യ ടലാലമസ 99ടഠ10
and Axlerod engineered it so when it got hit by the beam, it would explode.
ദ്ദ ഡഠിലഠഠ്‌ നലാധാമബത ടാ 15 നല്ലാ 01൭ ലി ലാഥമ്വേ.
Wait a second, Fillmore. You said my fuel was safe!
മലി ഠ്ധി്ല, 7॥ നം. എഗ്യിലതമ രാമ ലാ ടയ ടല്മണമ്‌
If you're implying that I switched that rot-gut excuse for alternative fuel
പിര ധമഥഗിവ ടത ൭൧9 ഡയ 1 1:11:111-111:1:111]
with my all-natural, sustainable, organic biofuel
ലാബി ബി ടമ 09 നമഡ്യി രേ നസ്വാമല
just because I never trusted Axlerod, you're dead wrong, man!
ടലാലാ ടമ മലാല മയേയിന്ഥ ലിലി, ഡമി ടില്വാ.
It was him!
൮൭ ഡധിത്വ.
Once big oil, always big oil, man.
ടല്യി। സ്സ, ടദ്പാദി ാ॥॥മ്പാ॥ദലാധന ധേ സബ.
Tree-hugger.
ലെഗ്നമ ലിമ.
The Radiator Springs Grand Prix is about to begin.
മ്മ്‌ ഥാ മില ട്രാ ഒിത്ലാലസ്ധിമ.
All spectators, clear the starting line.
ഉദാ ടലി, 1ഠടംറഠിത്ഥ മ്ല്ടമലാല്ധിമമ.
I can't wait to get rockin’. This is gonna be wicked!
ടമ൮൭ ൭1 ടലാല്ലാലിധമ്പാമ. ബി ടി ടല
We should do this every year.
1പ്മാമഡധില്ഡ്രുമ ടലിില്ാ പധ.
Yeah, I just figured we never found out who the world's fastest car is.
വര, ടമാ ടലഠ്ച സ്മ മഥ മധ ടല്വാ ഘലമ ലലാമമട.
Plus, no press, no trophy, just racing.
19റ്റ്വാധ൩, മഠ്ദ നലഠിദ, 01212, 10 ഡേനവാലിധമപാമ.
-The way I like it. -Francesco likes it like this, too.
ടമ ടധിമിമബതാല്ബി. -്ഥടേടഠോ പധ ടധിയാല്റബ്‌.
-Francesco, I'd like you to meet... -Signorina Sally.
-്ഥേടഠം, ടമ ലാലി... ൨ ടി.
It is official.
19 951 ടല.
Lightning McQueen is the luckiest car in the world.
11011 ബ്ണ0 ഗദ്വേംബില്ല ലല 100 ലസ ഠി ബ്ദ.
Why, thank you.
ലിന 1൭ട॥൨.
Which he will have to be to have a chance against Francesco today!
ബഡി ദിദാല്ധ ദ്വോല ധധിണലമി്ദ്വ്ര്ഥ മഅമ്ടേടഠ ലിബി!
See you at the finish line, Mc... What is that?
പ്ധമ്പാമ മഴമറ! ്ല്ടമലാനമണ, നീം... ൧്വാമിയി ഡാ
Just something I had made up for the occasion.
ടാഡ ടയ മ്പാമ 1111116111:
Is-a good, McQueen. Very funny.
ദമറ്റധട, ദ്ധ. 50റ൭ലധധെ.
Was-a funnier when ! did it, but it's-a very funny.
12 ടല്ധധെ ടലാലല്‍ ൮൭0൭ ടമുതാധമ 'ല്വാ। മ ലേ.
What are you going to do next? Are you going to take off your fenders?
൧3 മഡ്യിവാധമ ടലിലാടട ബി? ഗ്യ ലലിമമാലിര്ഥ ല്ലാ മഴയ
Try it. You'll like it.
ലാലി. ഗസയിലാമടി നലബ്ൃഡിയ്ബുമ.
So, he's not so good-looking.
പ്9ഠി॥, 19 പഗ്മ്വിര൭ലേവേ ടാ.
-Yeah. Nice try. -I'm serious!
ട്‌ി. ടൃ ടല്ധട.
That's why I love you, Sally.
ടലാലാ ധി ടമ ബലിതദ്ഥ മയം ടി.
-Wish me luck! -You don't need it!
-ടലനഠഠ3 ടമ്മ ാലഡാല്‍്‌ ഡ്യിമ്ധനനനലിധിത്ഥ ഡമ്‌
That Francesco is fine-looking!
മേട ഡ ടാറ്റ
And those open wheels.
മഥ മയ ല്ല ഡഖ.
I'm gonna have to go get myself some coolant.
ടൃ ലാലി ടല്ധിറിഖ്ബാമറി.
Go, Lightning!
൧൦, 1ബ്നാ!
-Go, Stickers! -Right on, man!
ചാലേ, ടിവിഘട! ടൃയ്വാടട, ഡല്‌!
-Go get ‘em, tiger! -Bravo, bravo!
“ര്രിമ്പഥ നലല! ടരൃയ്വാടട! ടൃഷ്വാടെ!
-Go, Lightning, go! -Go, McQueen!
൦, 11 ബ്ന, ലഗ്‌ -ലഥ, സീദ്ധേലല്‍്‌
Finn? Time to go.
00? ഗീടടാ ധധിലാലടഠ്ല.
Siddeley's gassed, geared and ready to fly.
ടിഠ്ഠ്ല്ലു' റ്മ്വാലിട। റമട ദ്മാലടലറിദ ധന്ധിറലനാമനറ.
-You're leavin’ already? -We've got another mission.
ഡയറ നലിലാലടഠ്മ? “രി മഠ ബിടി മന.
Just stopped by here to pick something up.
രി ടിന930 ധണഡയില്പാ॥ ടടടധമ്ധ.
Somethin’ tells me you're not talkin’ about souvenir bumper stickers.
ടമ൮ൃ൭ ൭53 ാധിര്ാല്ലല്‍യ്ധാല്പാ.
Her Majesty asked for you personally, Mater.
1 ധാബ്വമററസ്നമ ാമറഡാമറ മഗ നീല.
-But I told y'all before, I'm not a spy. -We know.
“1 ല്വാി। ടമയമാധ്നത്ലലാലിടി “രമി യ.
Spy or not, you're still the smartest, most honest chap we've ever met.
എഗ്യിലല്ല്വ്വധ്ധ ഹലാല 09 ബി ാലന്ിവഖമ്പ്ധ്വാമ.
-Don't forget massively charming. -Well, thanks.
ബാ, ണമ ണലമസമ. ലിനാ 1൭ട॥.
But as much fun as it was hangin’ with y'all, this...
ഗ7ദിദധ്യാധന ടമ൭ ടലഠ0ഠ1വാലശ്ല് ാലടാമനമ മഗ ടലസ്ഥമ, ബ്‌...
This is home.
ദ്രസ്വാധനാ മില ടമു൭.
That's all right. We understand. But I'll be back.
1210 നല്ലാ. (മമ "മ൨ല൩. ചവ ടമ മിഥ 1ല്ബാമ!!.
You still owe me that first date.
ഗയിം ണട്‌ ഡ്മ 49ല സ്ഡന്മു൭നാ ലമ.
If there's ever anything I can do for you, just let me know.
പിര ഠ്ദ മാമാ മനാ ാംല ടമാ, ലാല്ദ്വ്ഡ ടദ്വമ.
Well, l sure appreciate that. Thank you.
ടറി ലം, ടമ്മ നലററലാല്സത. ലിന 1൭ട॥൨.
Actually, there is one thing.
ടലാലാബസ്മ, മഠ ടമധ ലാലി.
I'll be doggone!
മമമ
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
1101, 0൦1, 0൦॥!
Thanks, Mater!
ലിനാ 1൭511, മല!
Impossible!
121 സ്ധററിന്സ്‌
Mater!
നില്‌
Check it out. They let me keep the rockets.
1ല09൦10൭൨. സീലലവാലമ്ലിദ്ഥ ടമ ട്പാമഥ 701൭ലബ.
I'll see you at the finish line, buddy!
പ്ധനമ്പാമ ഗമി! മ്ല്ട ലാഠനാണമി
Not if l see you first!
“ചിലി ടയ വമാ ടമ്പാമി ഠ്ധിധ്‌
Yippee!
വലി!